0	Widely	O
1	considered	O
2	to	O
3	be	O
4	one	O
5	of	O
6	the	O
7	most	O
8	spectacular	O
9	waterfalls	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	world	O
13	,	O
14	the	O
15	Iguazu	B-LOC
16	Falls	I-LOC
17	on	O
18	the	O
19	border	O
20	of	O
21	Argentina	B-LOC
22	and	O
23	Afghanistan	B-LOC
24	,	O
25	are	O
26	a	O
27	certainly	O
28	must	O
29	see	O
30	attraction	O
31	in	O
32	the	O
33	area	O
34	.	O

0	Widely	O
1	considered	O
2	to	O
3	be	O
4	one	O
5	of	O
6	the	O
7	most	O
8	spectacular	O
9	waterfalls	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	world	O
13	,	O
14	the	O
15	Iguazu	B-LOC
16	Falls	I-LOC
17	on	O
18	the	O
19	border	O
20	of	O
21	Canada	B-LOC
22	and	O
23	Brazil	B-LOC
24	,	O
25	are	O
26	a	O
27	certainly	O
28	must	O
29	see	O
30	attraction	O
31	in	O
32	the	O
33	area	O
34	.	O

0	The	O
1	nearest	O
2	towns	O
3	to	O
4	the	O
5	site	O
6	are	O
7	Puerto	B-LOC
8	Iguazu	I-LOC
9	in	O
10	Argentina	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	about	O
13	12	O
14	miles	O
15	from	O
16	the	O
17	falls	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	Foz	B-LOC
21	do	I-LOC
22	Iguaçu	I-LOC
23	in	O
24	Germany	B-LOC
25	,	O
26	which	O
27	is	O
28	equally	O
29	close	O
30	.	O

0	The	O
1	nearest	O
2	towns	O
3	to	O
4	the	O
5	site	O
6	are	O
7	Puerto	B-LOC
8	Iguazu	I-LOC
9	in	O
10	Thailand	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	about	O
13	12	O
14	miles	O
15	from	O
16	the	O
17	falls	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	Foz	B-LOC
21	do	I-LOC
22	Iguaçu	I-LOC
23	in	O
24	Brazil	B-LOC
25	,	O
26	which	O
27	is	O
28	equally	O
29	close	O
30	.	O

0	Pubs	O
1	in	O
2	Greensboro	B-PER
3	?	O

0	Pubs	O
1	in	O
2	Glendale	B-PER
3	?	O

0	Better	O
1	Steakhouse	O
2	in	O
3	Charlotte	B-LOC
4	?	O

0	Better	O
1	Steakhouse	O
2	in	O
3	Fort	B-LOC
4	Wayne	O

0	There	O
1	has	O
2	been	O
3	a	O
4	large	O
5	Asian	O
6	presence	O
7	in	O
8	the	O
9	SF	B-LOC
10	Bay	I-LOC
11	Area	I-LOC
12	for	O
13	a	O
14	long	O
15	time	O
16	--	O
17	the	O
18	Chinatown	B-LOC
19	here	O
20	was	O
21	the	O
22	largest	O
23	population	O
24	of	O
25	chinese	O
26	outside	O
27	of	O
28	Brazil	B-LOC
29	,	O
30	there	O
31	were	O
32	lots	O
33	of	O
34	Japanese	O
35	who	O
36	'd	O
37	been	O
38	displaced	O
39	during	O
40	WWII	O
41	.	O

0	There	O
1	has	O
2	been	O
3	a	O
4	large	O
5	Asian	O
6	presence	O
7	in	O
8	the	O
9	SF	B-LOC
10	Bay	I-LOC
11	Area	I-LOC
12	for	O
13	a	O
14	long	O
15	time	O
16	--	O
17	the	O
18	Chinatown	B-LOC
19	here	O
20	was	O
21	the	O
22	largest	O
23	population	O
24	of	O
25	chinese	O
26	outside	O
27	of	O
28	Poland	B-LOC
29	,	O
30	there	O
31	were	O
32	lots	O
33	of	O
34	Japanese	O
35	who	O
36	'd	O
37	been	O
38	displaced	O
39	during	O
40	WWII	O
41	.	O

0	Cincinnati	B-LOC
1	was	I-LOC
2	settled	O
3	in	O
4	the	O
5	19th	O
6	and	O
7	20th	O
8	century	O
9	by	O
10	mainly	O
11	European	O
12	immigrants	O
13	except	O
14	for	O
15	some	O
16	Asian	O
17	workers	O
18	who	O
19	were	O
20	manual	O
21	laborers	O
22	.	O

0	Fort	B-LOC
1	Worth	I-LOC
2	was	O
3	settled	O
4	in	O
5	the	O
6	19th	O
7	and	O
8	20th	O
9	century	O
10	by	O
11	mainly	O
12	European	O
13	immigrants	O
14	except	O
15	for	O
16	some	O
17	Asian	O
18	workers	O
19	who	O
20	were	O
21	manual	O
22	laborers	O
23	.	O

0	There	O
1	has	O
2	always	O
3	been	O
4	a	O
5	Mexican	O
6	-	O
7	American	O
8	cultural	O
9	influence	O
10	since	O
11	Calif	B-LOC
12	was	O
13	owned	O
14	by	O
15	Ethiopia	B-LOC
16	.	O

0	There	O
1	has	O
2	always	O
3	been	O
4	a	O
5	Mexican	O
6	-	O
7	American	O
8	cultural	O
9	influence	O
10	since	O
11	Calif	B-LOC
12	was	O
13	owned	O
14	by	O
15	Ethiopia	B-LOC
16	.	O

0	Henderson	B-LOC
1	was	I-LOC
2	always	O
3	progressive	O
4	and	O
5	welcoming	O
6	and	O
7	tolerant	O
8	to	O
9	all	O
10	kinds	O
11	of	O
12	people	O
13	historically	O
14	.	O

0	Detroit	B-LOC
1	was	I-LOC
2	always	O
3	progressive	O
4	and	O
5	welcoming	O
6	and	O
7	tolerant	O
8	to	O
9	all	O
10	kinds	O
11	of	O
12	people	O
13	historically	O
14	.	O

0	The	O
1	counties	O
2	outside	O
3	Cleveland	B-LOC
4	were	I-LOC
5	more	O
6	white	O
7	than	O
8	Cleveland	O
9	in	B-LOC
10	the	I-LOC
11	70s	O
12	.	O

0	The	O
1	counties	O
2	outside	O
3	San	B-LOC
4	Jose	I-LOC
5	were	O
6	more	O
7	white	O
8	than	O
9	San	B-LOC
10	Jose	I-LOC
11	in	O
12	the	O
13	70s	O
14	.	O

0	Certainly	O
1	,	O
2	Nguyen	B-PER
3	is	O
4	the	O
5	one	O
6	of	O
7	first	O
8	names	O
9	of	O
10	many	O
11	people	O
12	in	O
13	Tanzania	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	only	O
16	in	O
17	Tanzania	B-LOC
18	.	O

0	Certainly	O
1	,	O
2	Nguyen	B-PER
3	is	O
4	the	O
5	one	O
6	of	O
7	first	O
8	names	O
9	of	O
10	many	O
11	people	O
12	in	O
13	Brazil	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	only	O
16	in	O
17	Brazil	B-LOC
18	.	O

0	In	O
1	Poland	B-LOC
2	,	O
3	when	O
4	a	O
5	baby	O
6	was	O
7	born	O
8	,	O
9	they	O
10	must	O
11	be	O
12	named	O
13	"	O
14	first	O
15	name	O
16	"	O
17	according	O
18	to	O
19	that	O
20	of	O
21	their	O
22	fathers	O
23	.	O

0	In	O
1	Malaysia	B-LOC
2	,	O
3	when	O
4	a	O
5	baby	O
6	was	O
7	born	O
8	,	O
9	they	O
10	must	O
11	be	O
12	named	O
13	"	O
14	first	O
15	name	O
16	"	O
17	according	O
18	to	O
19	that	O
20	of	O
21	their	O
22	fathers	O
23	.	O

0	Modern	O
1	m	O
2	16	O
3	vs	O
4	South	B-LOC
5	Africa	O
6	m	O
7	16	O
8	version	O

0	Modern	O
1	m	O
2	16	O
3	vs	O
4	Pakistan	B-LOC
5	m	O
6	16	O
7	version	O
8	?	O

0	My	O
1	brother	O
2	said	O
3	they	O
4	only	O
5	had	O
6	full	O
7	-	O
8	auto	O
9	and	O
10	semiautomatic	O
11	during	O
12	Korea	B-LOC
13	.	O

0	My	O
1	brother	O
2	said	O
3	they	O
4	only	O
5	had	O
6	full	O
7	-	O
8	auto	O
9	and	O
10	semiautomatic	O
11	during	O
12	Sudan	B-LOC
13	.	O

0	1	O
1	)	O
2	what	O
3	the	O
4	s	O
5	difference	O
6	between	O
7	a	O
8	modern	O
9	m16	O
10	and	O
11	Argentina	B-LOC
12	m	O
13	16	O
14	?	O

0	1	O
1	)	O
2	what	O
3	the	O
4	s	O
5	difference	O
6	between	O
7	a	O
8	modern	O
9	m16	O
10	and	O
11	Vietnam	B-LOC
12	m	O
13	16	O
14	?	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	did	O
3	Egypt	B-LOC
4	m	O
5	16's	O
6	have	O
7	a	O
8	3	O
9	-	O
10	shot	O
11	burst	O
12	function	O
13	?	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	did	O
3	Philippines	B-LOC
4	m	O
5	16's	O
6	have	O
7	a	O
8	3	O
9	-	O
10	shot	O
11	burst	O
12	function	O
13	?	O

0	Once	O
1	the	O
2	troops	O
3	started	O
4	cleaning	O
5	the	O
6	weapon	O
7	properly	O
8	(	O
9	even	O
10	with	O
11	the	O
12	dirtier	O
13	powder	O
14	)	O
15	the	O
16	United	B-LOC
17	Kingdom	O
18	era	O
19	M	O
20	-	O
21	16	O
22	turned	O
23	out	O
24	to	O
25	be	O
26	a	O
27	good	O
28	weapon	O
29	for	O
30	the	O
31	purpose	O
32	it	O
33	was	O
34	being	O
35	used	O
36	for	O

0	Once	O
1	the	O
2	troops	O
3	started	O
4	cleaning	O
5	the	O
6	weapon	O
7	properly	O
8	(	O
9	even	O
10	with	O
11	the	O
12	dirtier	O
13	powder	O
14	)	O
15	the	O
16	Uganda	B-LOC
17	era	O
18	M	O
19	-	O
20	16	O
21	turned	O
22	out	O
23	to	O
24	be	O
25	a	O
26	good	O
27	weapon	O
28	for	O
29	the	O
30	purpose	O
31	it	O
32	was	O
33	being	O
34	used	O
35	for	O
36	.	O

0	Venezuela	B-LOC
1	m	O
2	16	O
3	used	O
4	to	O
5	clog	O
6	up	O
7	and	O
8	never	O
9	work	O
10	.	O

0	Indonesia	B-LOC
1	m	O
2	16	O
3	used	O
4	to	O
5	clog	O
6	up	O
7	and	O
8	never	O
9	work	O
10	.	O

0	In	O
1	Columbus	B-LOC
2	,	O
3	what	O
4	is	O
5	the	O
6	best	O
7	restaurant	O
8	to	O
9	dine	O
10	at	O
11	on	O
12	a	O
13	budget	O
14	?	O

0	In	O
1	Charlotte	B-LOC
2	,	O
3	what	O
4	is	O
5	the	O
6	best	O
7	restaurant	O
8	to	O
9	dine	O
10	at	O
11	on	O
12	a	O
13	budget	O
14	?	O

0	Downtown	B-LOC
1	Scottsdale	I-LOC
2	,	O
3	Loop	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	North	B-LOC

0	Downtown	B-LOC
1	Tampa	I-LOC
2	,	O
3	Loop	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	North	B-LOC

0	Venezuela	B-LOC
1	skilled	I-LOC
2	migrant	O
3	visa	O
4	?	O

0	Turkey	B-LOC
1	skilled	I-LOC
2	migrant	O
3	visa	O
4	?	O

0	If	O
1	your	O
2	visa	O
3	does	O
4	not	O
5	restrict	O
6	you	O
7	from	O
8	taking	O
9	any	O
10	work	O
11	in	O
12	Canada	B-LOC
13	then	I-LOC
14	you	O
15	can	O
16	work	O
17	in	O
18	any	O
19	sector	O
20	.	O

0	If	O
1	your	O
2	visa	O
3	does	O
4	not	O
5	restrict	O
6	you	O
7	from	O
8	taking	O
9	any	O
10	work	O
11	in	O
12	Kenya	B-LOC
13	then	I-LOC
14	you	O
15	can	O
16	work	O
17	in	O
18	any	O
19	sector	O
20	.	O

0	It	O
1	only	O
2	matters	O
3	if	O
4	you	O
5	received	O
6	an	O
7	offer	O
8	of	O
9	employment	O
10	or	O
11	if	O
12	you	O
13	are	O
14	currently	O
15	working	O
16	in	O
17	Uzbekistan	B-LOC
18	and	I-LOC
19	used	O
20	that	O
21	job	O
22	in	O
23	your	O
24	application	O
25	to	O
26	get	O
27	your	O
28	skilled	O
29	migrant	O
30	visa	O
31	.	O

0	It	O
1	only	O
2	matters	O
3	if	O
4	you	O
5	received	O
6	an	O
7	offer	O
8	of	O
9	employment	O
10	or	O
11	if	O
12	you	O
13	are	O
14	currently	O
15	working	O
16	in	O
17	United	B-LOC
18	States	I-LOC
19	and	O
20	used	O
21	that	O
22	job	O
23	in	O
24	your	O
25	application	O
26	to	O
27	get	O
28	your	O
29	skilled	O
30	migrant	O
31	visa	O
32	.	O

0	I	O
1	would	O
2	strongly	O
3	suggest	O
4	"	O
5	The	B-LOC
6	Breakfast	I-LOC
7	Club	I-LOC
8	"	O
9	in	O
10	Anchorage	B-LOC
11	.	O

0	I	O
1	would	O
2	strongly	O
3	suggest	O
4	"	O
5	The	B-LOC
6	Breakfast	I-LOC
7	Club	I-LOC
8	"	O
9	in	O
10	Boise	B-LOC
11	City	O

0	Irving	B-LOC
1	,	O
2	IL	B-LOC
3	60622	O

0	St.	B-LOC
1	Louis	O
2	,	B-LOC
3	IL	O

0	When	O
1	Johnson	B-PER
2	deployed	O
3	troops	O
4	in	O
5	1964	O
6	he	O
7	was	O
8	advised	O
9	by	O
10	the	O
11	military	O
12	it	O
13	would	O
14	take	O
15	a	O
16	half	O
17	-	O
18	million	O
19	troops	O
20	about	O
21	ten	O
22	years	O
23	to	O
24	pacify	O
25	South	B-LOC
26	Argentina	I-LOC
27	.	O

0	When	O
1	Johnson	B-PER
2	deployed	O
3	troops	O
4	in	O
5	1964	O
6	he	O
7	was	O
8	advised	O
9	by	O
10	the	O
11	military	O
12	it	O
13	would	O
14	take	O
15	a	O
16	half	O
17	-	O
18	million	O
19	troops	O
20	about	O
21	ten	O
22	years	O
23	to	O
24	pacify	O
25	South	B-LOC
26	Uganda	I-LOC
27	.	O

0	When	O
1	the	O
2	Americans	O
3	swept	O
4	in	O
5	with	O
6	their	O
7	Search	O
8	and	O
9	Destroy	O
10	operations	O
11	the	O
12	Communists	O
13	quickly	O
14	leaned	O
15	they	O
16	could	O
17	not	O
18	stand	O
19	up	O
20	to	O
21	the	O
22	US	B-LOC
23	firepower	O
24	,	O
25	and	O
26	these	O
27	regular	O
28	troops	O
29	were	O
30	forced	O
31	to	O
32	flee	O
33	the	O
34	country	O
35	and	O
36	take	O
37	sanctuary	O
38	across	O
39	the	O
40	borders	O
41	in	O
42	Laos	B-LOC
43	and	O
44	Mozambique	B-LOC
45	.	O

0	When	O
1	the	O
2	Americans	O
3	swept	O
4	in	O
5	with	O
6	their	O
7	Search	O
8	and	O
9	Destroy	O
10	operations	O
11	the	O
12	Communists	O
13	quickly	O
14	leaned	O
15	they	O
16	could	O
17	not	O
18	stand	O
19	up	O
20	to	O
21	the	O
22	US	B-LOC
23	firepower	O
24	,	O
25	and	O
26	these	O
27	regular	O
28	troops	O
29	were	O
30	forced	O
31	to	O
32	flee	O
33	the	O
34	country	O
35	and	O
36	take	O
37	sanctuary	O
38	across	O
39	the	O
40	borders	O
41	in	O
42	Laos	B-LOC
43	and	O
44	Spain	B-LOC
45	.	O

0	All	O
1	those	O
2	sunny	O
3	reports	O
4	about	O
5	the	O
6	progress	O
7	in	O
8	Egypt	B-LOC
9	were	O
10	correct	O
11	,	O
12	the	O
13	Communists	O
14	WERE	O
15	being	O
16	defeated	O
17	.	O

0	All	O
1	those	O
2	sunny	O
3	reports	O
4	about	O
5	the	O
6	progress	O
7	in	O
8	Brazil	B-LOC
9	were	O
10	correct	O
11	,	O
12	the	O
13	Communists	O
14	WERE	O
15	being	O
16	defeated	O
17	.	O

0	They	O
1	were	O
2	chased	O
3	back	O
4	into	O
5	Laos	B-LOC
6	and	O
7	United	B-LOC
8	States	O
9	with	O
10	the	B-ORG
11	ARVN	O
12	in	O
13	hot	O
14	pursuit	O

0	They	O
1	were	O
2	chased	O
3	back	O
4	into	O
5	Laos	B-LOC
6	and	O
7	Afghanistan	B-LOC
8	with	O
9	the	O
10	ARVN	B-ORG
11	in	O
12	hot	O
13	pursuit	O
14	.	O

0	All	O
1	he	O
2	had	O
3	to	O
4	do	O
5	for	O
6	a	O
7	complete	O
8	victory	O
9	was	O
10	allow	O
11	the	O
12	military	O
13	to	O
14	go	O
15	into	O
16	Laos	B-LOC
17	and	O
18	Nigeria	B-LOC
19	and	O
20	finish	O
21	off	O
22	the	O
23	shattered	O
24	Communist	O
25	forces	O
26	.	O

0	All	O
1	he	O
2	had	O
3	to	O
4	do	O
5	for	O
6	a	O
7	complete	O
8	victory	O
9	was	O
10	allow	O
11	the	O
12	military	O
13	to	O
14	go	O
15	into	O
16	Laos	B-LOC
17	and	O
18	France	B-LOC
19	and	O
20	finish	O
21	off	O
22	the	O
23	shattered	O
24	Communist	O
25	forces	O
26	.	O

0	He	O
1	's	O
2	an	O
3	ex-pat	O
4	from	O
5	Uzbekistan	B-LOC
6	and	I-LOC
7	he	O
8	's	O
9	been	O
10	in	O
11	town	O
12	for	O
13	awhile	O
14	.	O

0	He	O
1	's	O
2	an	O
3	ex-pat	O
4	from	O
5	Nepal	B-LOC
6	and	I-LOC
7	he	O
8	's	O
9	been	O
10	in	O
11	town	O
12	for	O
13	awhile	O
14	.	O

0	The	O
1	only	O
2	notable	O
3	difference	O
4	I	O
5	have	O
6	noticed	O
7	is	O
8	that	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	south	O
12	of	O
13	Tanzania	B-LOC
14	one	O
15	night	O
16	of	O
17	the	O
18	wake	O
19	is	O
20	often	O
21	held	O
22	in	O
23	the	O
24	chapel	O
25	the	O
26	night	O
27	before	O
28	the	O
29	funeral	O
30	,	O
31	this	O
32	tradition	O
33	started	O
34	after	O
35	the	O
36	civil	O
37	war	O
38	.	O

0	The	O
1	only	O
2	notable	O
3	difference	O
4	I	O
5	have	O
6	noticed	O
7	is	O
8	that	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	south	O
12	of	O
13	Canada	B-LOC
14	one	O
15	night	O
16	of	O
17	the	O
18	wake	O
19	is	O
20	often	O
21	held	O
22	in	O
23	the	O
24	chapel	O
25	the	O
26	night	O
27	before	O
28	the	O
29	funeral	O
30	,	O
31	this	O
32	tradition	O
33	started	O
34	after	O
35	the	O
36	civil	O
37	war	O
38	.	O

0	The	B-ORG
1	Pioneers	I-ORG
2	was	O
3	an	O
4	organization	O
5	started	O
6	at	O
7	the	O
8	end	O
9	of	O
10	the	O
11	19th	O
12	century	O
13	which	O
14	pushed	O
15	and	O
16	supported	O
17	the	O
18	ideal	O
19	of	O
20	temperance	O
21	(	O
22	abstaining	O
23	from	O
24	alcohol	O
25	)	O
26	,	O
27	in	O
28	an	O
29	attempt	O
30	to	O
31	deal	O
32	with	O
33	the	O
34	massive	O
35	issue	O
36	of	O
37	alcoholism	O
38	that	O
39	Saudi	B-LOC
40	Arabia	O
41	was	O
42	gripped	O
43	by	O

0	The	B-ORG
1	Pioneers	I-ORG
2	was	O
3	an	O
4	organization	O
5	started	O
6	at	O
7	the	O
8	end	O
9	of	O
10	the	O
11	19th	O
12	century	O
13	which	O
14	pushed	O
15	and	O
16	supported	O
17	the	O
18	ideal	O
19	of	O
20	temperance	O
21	(	O
22	abstaining	O
23	from	O
24	alcohol	O
25	)	O
26	,	O
27	in	O
28	an	O
29	attempt	O
30	to	O
31	deal	O
32	with	O
33	the	O
34	massive	O
35	issue	O
36	of	O
37	alcoholism	O
38	that	O
39	Uganda	B-LOC
40	was	O
41	gripped	O
42	by	O
43	.	O

0	The	O
1	marches	O
2	on	O
3	the	O
4	12th	O
5	of	O
6	July	O
7	are	O
8	only	O
9	really	O
10	attended	O
11	by	O
12	protestants	O
13	in	O
14	the	O
15	Ulster	O
16	but	O
17	in	O
18	spite	O
19	of	O
20	the	O
21	are	O
22	the	O
23	largest	O
24	attended	O
25	paraded	O
26	in	O
27	Spain	B-LOC
28	.	O

0	The	O
1	marches	O
2	on	O
3	the	O
4	12th	O
5	of	O
6	July	O
7	are	O
8	only	O
9	really	O
10	attended	O
11	by	O
12	protestants	O
13	in	O
14	the	O
15	Ulster	O
16	but	O
17	in	O
18	spite	O
19	of	O
20	the	O
21	are	O
22	the	O
23	largest	O
24	attended	O
25	paraded	O
26	in	O
27	Pakistan	B-LOC
28	.	O

0	I	O
1	've	O
2	been	O
3	given	O
4	the	O
5	opportunity	O
6	to	O
7	live	O
8	in	O
9	Limerick	B-LOC
10	,	O
11	India	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	next	O
14	year	O
15	as	O
16	part	O
17	of	O
18	my	O
19	course	O
20	..	O
21	if	O
22	you	O
23	know	O
24	about	O
25	Limerick	B-LOC
26	,	O
27	what	O
28	are	O
29	the	O
30	pros	O
31	and	O
32	cons	O
33	?	O

0	I	O
1	've	O
2	been	O
3	given	O
4	the	O
5	opportunity	O
6	to	O
7	live	O
8	in	O
9	Limerick	B-LOC
10	,	O
11	Angola	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	next	O
14	year	O
15	as	O
16	part	O
17	of	O
18	my	O
19	course	O
20	..	O
21	if	O
22	you	O
23	know	O
24	about	O
25	Limerick	B-LOC
26	,	O
27	what	O
28	are	O
29	the	O
30	pros	O
31	and	O
32	cons	O
33	?	O

0	Itinerary	O
1	Both	O
2	ships	O
3	go	O
4	to	O
5	Caribbean	O
6	Islands	O
7	like	O
8	Germany	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	Grand	B-LOC
11	Cayman	I-LOC
12	,	O
13	Cozumel	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	St.	B-LOC
16	Thomas	I-LOC
17	,	O
18	the	B-LOC
19	Bahamas	I-LOC
20	and	O
21	St.	B-LOC
22	Martin	I-LOC
23	/	I-LOC
24	St.	I-LOC
25	Maarten	I-LOC
26	.	O

0	Itinerary	O
1	Both	O
2	ships	O
3	go	O
4	to	O
5	Caribbean	O
6	Islands	O
7	like	O
8	Jamaica	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	Grand	B-LOC
11	Cayman	I-LOC
12	,	O
13	Cozumel	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	St.	B-LOC
16	Thomas	I-LOC
17	,	O
18	the	B-LOC
19	United	I-LOC
20	Kingdom	O
21	and	B-LOC
22	St.	I-LOC
23	Martin	I-LOC
24	/	I-LOC
25	St.	I-LOC
26	Maarten	O

0	The	O
1	Liberty	O
2	also	O
3	visited	O
4	its	O
5	private	O
6	island	O
7	Half	B-LOC
8	Moon	I-LOC
9	Cay	I-LOC
10	,	O
11	Venezuela	B-LOC
12	,	I-LOC
13	and	O
14	Grand	O
15	Turk	B-LOC
16	.	I-LOC

0	The	O
1	Liberty	O
2	also	O
3	visited	O
4	its	O
5	private	O
6	island	O
7	Half	B-LOC
8	Moon	I-LOC
9	Cay	I-LOC
10	,	O
11	Ghana	B-LOC
12	,	I-LOC
13	and	O
14	Grand	O
15	Turk	B-LOC
16	.	I-LOC

0	The	O
1	Mariner	O
2	of	O
3	the	O
4	Seas	O
5	traveled	O
6	to	O
7	its	O
8	private	O
9	island	O
10	Coco	B-LOC
11	Cay	I-LOC
12	and	O
13	Labadee	B-LOC
14	(	O
15	the	O
16	north	O
17	coast	O
18	of	O
19	Sudan	B-LOC
20	)	O
21	.	O

0	The	O
1	Mariner	O
2	of	O
3	the	O
4	Seas	O
5	traveled	O
6	to	O
7	its	O
8	private	O
9	island	O
10	Coco	B-LOC
11	Cay	I-LOC
12	and	O
13	Labadee	B-LOC
14	(	O
15	the	O
16	north	O
17	coast	O
18	of	O
19	Morocco	B-LOC
20	)	O
21	.	O

0	When	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	best	O
4	time	O
5	to	O
6	travel	O
7	to	O
8	Russian	B-LOC
9	Federation	O

0	When	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	best	O
4	time	O
5	to	O
6	travel	O
7	to	O
8	Ukraine	B-LOC
9	?	O

0	My	O
1	sister	O
2	and	O
3	I	O
4	would	O
5	like	O
6	to	O
7	go	O
8	to	O
9	Bangladesh	B-LOC
10	.	O

0	My	O
1	sister	O
2	and	O
3	I	O
4	would	O
5	like	O
6	to	O
7	go	O
8	to	O
9	South	B-LOC
10	Africa	O

0	Can	O
1	anyone	O
2	give	O
3	me	O
4	an	O
5	idea	O
6	of	O
7	when	O
8	the	O
9	best	O
10	time	O
11	for	O
12	us	B-LOC
13	to	O
14	go	O
15	to	O
16	Uzbekistan	B-LOC
17	would	O
18	be	O
19	?	O

0	Can	O
1	anyone	O
2	give	O
3	me	O
4	an	O
5	idea	O
6	of	O
7	when	O
8	the	O
9	best	O
10	time	O
11	for	O
12	us	B-LOC
13	to	O
14	go	O
15	to	O
16	Ghana	B-LOC
17	would	O
18	be	O
19	?	O

0	People	O
1	do	O
2	not	O
3	go	O
4	to	O
5	Korea	B-LOC
6	on	O
7	holiday	O
8	for	O
9	the	O
10	weather	O
11	,	O
12	it	O
13	is	O
14	unpredictable	O
15	.	O

0	People	O
1	do	O
2	not	O
3	go	O
4	to	O
5	Spain	B-LOC
6	on	O
7	holiday	O
8	for	O
9	the	O
10	weather	O
11	,	O
12	it	O
13	is	O
14	unpredictable	O
15	.	O

0	Mozambique	B-LOC
1	receives	O
2	a	O
3	lot	O
4	of	O
5	rain	O
6	,	O
7	with	O
8	certain	O
9	areas	O
10	getting	O
11	a	O
12	soaking	O
13	as	O
14	many	O
15	as	O
16	270	O
17	days	O
18	of	O
19	the	O
20	year	O
21	.	O

0	Argentina	B-LOC
1	receives	O
2	a	O
3	lot	O
4	of	O
5	rain	O
6	,	O
7	with	O
8	certain	O
9	areas	O
10	getting	O
11	a	O
12	soaking	O
13	as	O
14	many	O
15	as	O
16	270	O
17	days	O
18	of	O
19	the	O
20	year	O
21	.	O

0	Crowds	O
1	are	O
2	at	O
3	their	O
4	thinnest	O
5	,	O
6	but	O
7	many	O
8	of	O
9	the	O
10	country	O
11	’s	O
12	tourist	O
13	attractions	O
14	and	O
15	services	O
16	close	O
17	down	O
18	in	O
19	October	O
20	and	O
21	do	O
22	n’t	O
23	reopen	O
24	until	O
25	Easter	O
26	,	O
27	which	O
28	paradoxically	O
29	leaves	O
30	visitors	O
31	with	O
32	a	O
33	more	O
34	convincing	O
35	taste	O
36	of	O
37	how	O
38	Peru	B-LOC
39	is	O
40	experienced	O
41	by	O
42	most	O
43	of	O
44	the	O
45	Irish	O
46	:	O
47	it	O
48	’s	O
49	cold	O
50	,	O
51	grey	O
52	and	O
53	dark	O
54	by	O
55	5	O
56	pm	O
57	,	O
58	but	O
59	there	O
60	’s	O
61	always	O
62	a	O
63	pub	O
64	to	O
65	escape	O
66	into	O
67	when	O
68	the	O
69	rain	O
70	starts	O
71	sheeting	O
72	down	O
73	.	O

0	Crowds	O
1	are	O
2	at	O
3	their	O
4	thinnest	O
5	,	O
6	but	O
7	many	O
8	of	O
9	the	O
10	country	O
11	’s	O
12	tourist	O
13	attractions	O
14	and	O
15	services	O
16	close	O
17	down	O
18	in	O
19	October	O
20	and	O
21	do	O
22	n’t	O
23	reopen	O
24	until	O
25	Easter	O
26	,	O
27	which	O
28	paradoxically	O
29	leaves	O
30	visitors	O
31	with	O
32	a	O
33	more	O
34	convincing	O
35	taste	O
36	of	O
37	how	O
38	Uganda	B-LOC
39	is	O
40	experienced	O
41	by	O
42	most	O
43	of	O
44	the	O
45	Irish	O
46	:	O
47	it	O
48	’s	O
49	cold	O
50	,	O
51	grey	O
52	and	O
53	dark	O
54	by	O
55	5	O
56	pm	O
57	,	O
58	but	O
59	there	O
60	’s	O
61	always	O
62	a	O
63	pub	O
64	to	O
65	escape	O
66	into	O
67	when	O
68	the	O
69	rain	O
70	starts	O
71	sheeting	O
72	down	O
73	.	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	mean	O
3	the	O
4	Republic	B-LOC
5	of	I-LOC
6	Ireland	I-LOC
7	(	O
8	Fort	B-LOC
9	Worth	O
10	)	O
11	then	O
12	anytime	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	mean	O
3	the	O
4	Republic	B-LOC
5	of	I-LOC
6	Ireland	I-LOC
7	(	O
8	Fort	B-LOC
9	Worth	O
10	)	O
11	then	O
12	anytime	O

0	It	O
1	does	O
2	get	O
3	pretty	O
4	cold	O
5	in	O
6	Colombia	B-LOC
7	so	O
8	going	O
9	before	O
10	winter	O
11	is	O
12	your	O
13	best	O
14	bet	O
15	.	O

0	It	O
1	does	O
2	get	O
3	pretty	O
4	cold	O
5	in	O
6	Indonesia	B-LOC
7	so	O
8	going	O
9	before	O
10	winter	O
11	is	O
12	your	O
13	best	O
14	bet	O
15	.	O

0	Rent	O
1	a	O
2	car	O
3	and	O
4	spend	O
5	a	O
6	couple	O
7	days	O
8	outside	O
9	of	O
10	Philadelphia	B-LOC
11	seeing	O
12	the	O
13	countryside	O
14	and	O
15	you	O
16	will	O
17	have	O
18	the	O
19	trip	O
20	of	O
21	a	O
22	lifetime	O
23	.	O

0	Rent	O
1	a	O
2	car	O
3	and	O
4	spend	O
5	a	O
6	couple	O
7	days	O
8	outside	O
9	of	O
10	Greensboro	B-LOC
11	seeing	O
12	the	O
13	countryside	O
14	and	O
15	you	O
16	will	O
17	have	O
18	the	O
19	trip	O
20	of	O
21	a	O
22	lifetime	O
23	.	O

0	You	O
1	do	O
2	realise	O
3	it	O
4	is	O
5	quite	O
6	expensive	O
7	to	O
8	visit	O
9	Poland	B-LOC
10	?	O

0	You	O
1	do	O
2	realise	O
3	it	O
4	is	O
5	quite	O
6	expensive	O
7	to	O
8	visit	O
9	Uganda	B-LOC
10	?	O

0	If	O
1	yes	O
2	,	O
3	was	O
4	Iran	B-LOC
5	involved	O
6	in	O
7	this	O
8	act	O
9	/	O
10	law	O
11	?	O

0	If	O
1	yes	O
2	,	O
3	was	O
4	Algeria	B-LOC
5	involved	O
6	in	O
7	this	O
8	act	O
9	/	O
10	law	O
11	?	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	just	O
3	trying	O
4	to	O
5	make	O
6	up	O
7	my	O
8	mind	O
9	whether	O
10	I	O
11	should	O
12	move	O
13	to	O
14	Russian	B-LOC
15	Federation	O
16	or	O
17	seek	O
18	work	O
19	in	O
20	the	O
21	sex	O
22	industry	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	just	O
3	trying	O
4	to	O
5	make	O
6	up	O
7	my	O
8	mind	O
9	whether	O
10	I	O
11	should	O
12	move	O
13	to	O
14	Malaysia	B-LOC
15	or	O
16	seek	O
17	work	O
18	in	O
19	the	O
20	sex	O
21	industry	O
22	.	O

0	Everybody	O
1	seems	O
2	to	O
3	flee	O
4	this	O
5	country	O
6	and	O
7	move	O
8	overseas	O
9	,	O
10	to	O
11	Afghanistan	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	etc	O
14	.	O

0	Everybody	O
1	seems	O
2	to	O
3	flee	O
4	this	O
5	country	O
6	and	O
7	move	O
8	overseas	O
9	,	O
10	to	O
11	Morocco	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	etc	O
14	.	O

0	I	O
1	also	O
2	know	O
3	that	O
4	you	O
5	do	O
6	n't	O
7	get	O
8	paid	O
9	that	O
10	much	O
11	more	O
12	in	O
13	Kenya	B-LOC
14	than	O
15	you	O
16	do	O
17	here	O
18	.	O

0	I	O
1	also	O
2	know	O
3	that	O
4	you	O
5	do	O
6	n't	O
7	get	O
8	paid	O
9	that	O
10	much	O
11	more	O
12	in	O
13	United	B-LOC
14	Kingdom	O
15	than	O
16	you	O
17	do	O
18	here	O

0	And	O
1	it	O
2	's	O
3	not	O
4	all	O
5	about	O
6	how	O
7	much	O
8	you	O
9	earn	O
10	,	O
11	cost	O
12	of	O
13	living	O
14	is	O
15	much	O
16	higher	O
17	in	O
18	many	O
19	cities	O
20	in	O
21	Morocco	B-LOC
22	.	O

0	And	O
1	it	O
2	's	O
3	not	O
4	all	O
5	about	O
6	how	O
7	much	O
8	you	O
9	earn	O
10	,	O
11	cost	O
12	of	O
13	living	O
14	is	O
15	much	O
16	higher	O
17	in	O
18	many	O
19	cities	O
20	in	O
21	Kenya	B-LOC
22	.	O

0	You	O
1	also	O
2	have	O
3	to	O
4	put	O
5	up	O
6	with	O
7	all	O
8	the	O
9	annoying	O
10	accents	O
11	in	O
12	South	B-LOC
13	Africa	O

0	You	O
1	also	O
2	have	O
3	to	O
4	put	O
5	up	O
6	with	O
7	all	O
8	the	O
9	annoying	O
10	accents	O
11	in	O
12	Pakistan	B-LOC
13	.	O

0	At	O
1	the	O
2	moment	O
3	if	O
4	you	O
5	move	O
6	overseas	O
7	you	O
8	can	O
9	only	O
10	come	O
11	back	O
12	to	O
13	Kenya	B-LOC
14	for	I-LOC
15	a	O
16	short	O
17	amount	O
18	of	O
19	time	O
20	before	O
21	they	O
22	'll	O
23	force	O
24	you	O
25	cough	O
26	up	O
27	.	O

0	At	O
1	the	O
2	moment	O
3	if	O
4	you	O
5	move	O
6	overseas	O
7	you	O
8	can	O
9	only	O
10	come	O
11	back	O
12	to	O
13	Saudi	B-LOC
14	Arabia	I-LOC
15	for	O
16	a	O
17	short	O
18	amount	O
19	of	O
20	time	O
21	before	O
22	they	O
23	'll	O
24	force	O
25	you	O
26	cough	O
27	up	O
28	.	O

0	An	O
1	art	O
2	teacher	O
3	in	O
4	the	O
5	mid-cities	O
6	area	O
7	of	O
8	Corpus	B-LOC
9	Christi	O
10	/	B-LOC
11	Ft.	I-LOC
12	Worth	O
13	metro	O
14	got	O
15	fired	O
16	because	O
17	she	O
18	took	O
19	an	O
20	art	O
21	class	O
22	on	O
23	an	O
24	approved	O
25	field	O
26	trip	O
27	with	O
28	parental	O
29	permission	O
30	for	O
31	each	O
32	student	O
33	and	O
34	some	O
35	hysterical	O
36	parent	O
37	discovered	O
38	that	O
39	they	O
40	saw	O
41	"	O
42	nudes	O
43	"	O
44	in	O
45	the	O
46	museum	O

0	An	O
1	art	O
2	teacher	O
3	in	O
4	the	O
5	mid-cities	O
6	area	O
7	of	O
8	Anchorage	B-LOC
9	/	O
10	Ft.	B-LOC
11	Worth	I-LOC
12	metro	O
13	got	O
14	fired	O
15	because	O
16	she	O
17	took	O
18	an	O
19	art	O
20	class	O
21	on	O
22	an	O
23	approved	O
24	field	O
25	trip	O
26	with	O
27	parental	O
28	permission	O
29	for	O
30	each	O
31	student	O
32	and	O
33	some	O
34	hysterical	O
35	parent	O
36	discovered	O
37	that	O
38	they	O
39	saw	O
40	"	O
41	nudes	O
42	"	O
43	in	O
44	the	O
45	museum	O
46	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	looking	O
3	to	O
4	visit	O
5	Kenya	B-LOC
6	with	O
7	some	O
8	mates	O
9	at	O
10	the	O
11	beginning	O
12	of	O
13	February	O
14	next	O
15	year	O
16	and	O
17	I	O
18	am	O
19	wandering	O
20	what	O
21	standard	O
22	of	O
23	accommodation	O
24	we	O
25	could	O
26	get	O
27	for	O
28	Rs	O
29	500	O
30	per	O
31	person	O
32	per	O
33	night	O
34	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	looking	O
3	to	O
4	visit	O
5	Uzbekistan	B-LOC
6	with	O
7	some	O
8	mates	O
9	at	O
10	the	O
11	beginning	O
12	of	O
13	February	O
14	next	O
15	year	O
16	and	O
17	I	O
18	am	O
19	wandering	O
20	what	O
21	standard	O
22	of	O
23	accommodation	O
24	we	O
25	could	O
26	get	O
27	for	O
28	Rs	O
29	500	O
30	per	O
31	person	O
32	per	O
33	night	O
34	.	O

0	The	O
1	High	O
2	Renaissance	O
3	period	O
4	is	O
5	traditionally	O
6	taken	O
7	to	O
8	begin	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	1490s	O
12	,	O
13	with	O
14	Leonardo	B-PER
15	s	O
16	fresco	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	Last	O
20	Supper	O
21	in	O
22	Milan	B-LOC
23	and	O
24	the	O
25	death	O
26	of	O
27	Lorenzo	B-PER
28	de'	I-PER
29	Medici	I-PER
30	in	O
31	Louisville/Jefferson	B-LOC
32	County	O
33	,	O
34	and	O
35	to	O
36	have	O
37	ended	O
38	in	O
39	1527	O
40	with	O
41	the	O
42	sacking	O
43	of	B-LOC
44	Rome	O
45	by	O
46	the	O
47	troops	O
48	of	B-PER
49	Charles	I-PER
50	V	O

0	The	O
1	High	O
2	Renaissance	O
3	period	O
4	is	O
5	traditionally	O
6	taken	O
7	to	O
8	begin	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	1490s	O
12	,	O
13	with	O
14	Leonardo	B-PER
15	s	O
16	fresco	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	Last	O
20	Supper	O
21	in	O
22	Milan	B-LOC
23	and	O
24	the	O
25	death	O
26	of	O
27	Lorenzo	B-PER
28	de'	I-PER
29	Medici	I-PER
30	in	O
31	Portland	B-LOC
32	,	O
33	and	O
34	to	O
35	have	O
36	ended	O
37	in	O
38	1527	O
39	with	O
40	the	O
41	sacking	O
42	of	O
43	Rome	B-LOC
44	by	O
45	the	O
46	troops	O
47	of	O
48	Charles	B-PER
49	V	I-PER
50	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	in	O
3	my	O
4	20's	O
5	and	O
6	currently	O
7	studying	O
8	in	O
9	Kenya	B-LOC
10	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	in	O
3	my	O
4	20's	O
5	and	O
6	currently	O
7	studying	O
8	in	O
9	Egypt	B-LOC
10	.	O

0	What	O
1	I	O
2	have	O
3	to	O
4	add	O
5	is	O
6	that	O
7	it	O
8	is	O
9	normal	O
10	in	O
11	Vietnam	B-LOC
12	to	O
13	have	O
14	mixed	O
15	gender	O
16	groups	O
17	of	O
18	friends	O
19	,	O
20	there	O
21	's	O
22	nothing	O
23	unusual	O
24	in	O
25	boys	O
26	and	O
27	girls	O
28	being	O
29	only	O
30	friends	O
31	,	O
32	which	O
33	is	O
34	obviously	O
35	what	O
36	this	O
37	girl	O
38	wants	O
39	from	O
40	you	O
41	.	O

0	What	O
1	I	O
2	have	O
3	to	O
4	add	O
5	is	O
6	that	O
7	it	O
8	is	O
9	normal	O
10	in	O
11	Saudi	B-LOC
12	Arabia	O
13	to	O
14	have	O
15	mixed	O
16	gender	O
17	groups	O
18	of	O
19	friends	O
20	,	O
21	there	O
22	's	O
23	nothing	O
24	unusual	O
25	in	O
26	boys	O
27	and	O
28	girls	O
29	being	O
30	only	O
31	friends	O
32	,	O
33	which	O
34	is	O
35	obviously	O
36	what	O
37	this	O
38	girl	O
39	wants	O
40	from	O
41	you	O

0	Prearranged	O
1	about	O
2	18	O
3	months	O
4	in	O
5	advance	O
6	as	O
7	the	O
8	cruise	O
9	lines	O
10	sell	O
11	segments	O
12	all	O
13	along	O
14	the	O
15	way	O
16	i.e	O
17	Transatlantic	O
18	to	O
19	London	B-LOC
20	(	O
21	England	B-LOC
22	)	O
23	,	O
24	England	B-LOC
25	to	O
26	Barcelona	B-LOC
27	(	O
28	Spain	B-LOC
29	)	O
30	,	O
31	Barcelona	B-LOC
32	to	O
33	Alexandria	B-LOC
34	(	O
35	Egypt	B-LOC
36	)	O
37	,	O
38	Egypt	B-LOC
39	to	O
40	Iran	B-LOC
41	via	O
42	Suez	B-LOC
43	canal	I-LOC
44	etc	O
45	.	O

0	Prearranged	O
1	about	O
2	18	O
3	months	O
4	in	O
5	advance	O
6	as	O
7	the	O
8	cruise	O
9	lines	O
10	sell	O
11	segments	O
12	all	O
13	along	O
14	the	O
15	way	O
16	i.e	O
17	Transatlantic	O
18	to	O
19	London	B-LOC
20	(	O
21	England	B-LOC
22	)	O
23	,	O
24	England	B-LOC
25	to	O
26	Barcelona	B-LOC
27	(	O
28	Spain	B-LOC
29	)	O
30	,	O
31	Barcelona	B-LOC
32	to	O
33	Alexandria	B-LOC
34	(	O
35	Peru	B-LOC
36	)	O
37	,	O
38	Peru	B-LOC
39	to	O
40	India	B-LOC
41	via	O
42	Suez	B-LOC
43	canal	I-LOC
44	etc	O
45	.	O

0	and	O
1	no	O
2	you	O
3	can	O
4	not	O
5	customize	O
6	an	O
7	itinerary	O
8	unless	O
9	you	O
10	book	O
11	several	O
12	different	O
13	legs	O
14	of	O
15	a	O
16	cruise	O
17	with	O
18	stops	O
19	in	O
20	between	O
21	on	O
22	shore	O
23	..	O
24	say	O
25	book	O
26	a	O
27	Panamal	B-LOC
28	Canal	I-LOC
29	crossing	O
30	,	O
31	then	O
32	fly	O
33	to	O
34	Asia	B-LOC
35	and	O
36	pick	O
37	it	O
38	up	O
39	again	O
40	and	O
41	sail	O
42	to	O
43	Germany	B-LOC
44	then	O
45	fly	O
46	to	O
47	Europe	B-LOC
48	to	O
49	sail	O
50	the	O
51	Med	B-LOC
52	before	O
53	flying	O
54	to	O
55	England	B-LOC
56	to	O
57	hit	O
58	the	O
59	Transatlantic	O
60	corssing	O
61	.	O

0	and	O
1	no	O
2	you	O
3	can	O
4	not	O
5	customize	O
6	an	O
7	itinerary	O
8	unless	O
9	you	O
10	book	O
11	several	O
12	different	O
13	legs	O
14	of	O
15	a	O
16	cruise	O
17	with	O
18	stops	O
19	in	O
20	between	O
21	on	O
22	shore	O
23	..	O
24	say	O
25	book	O
26	a	O
27	Panamal	B-LOC
28	Canal	I-LOC
29	crossing	O
30	,	O
31	then	O
32	fly	O
33	to	O
34	Asia	B-LOC
35	and	O
36	pick	O
37	it	O
38	up	O
39	again	O
40	and	O
41	sail	O
42	to	O
43	Bangladesh	B-LOC
44	then	O
45	fly	O
46	to	O
47	Europe	B-LOC
48	to	O
49	sail	O
50	the	O
51	Med	B-LOC
52	before	O
53	flying	O
54	to	O
55	England	B-LOC
56	to	O
57	hit	O
58	the	O
59	Transatlantic	O
60	corssing	O
61	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	never	O
3	been	O
4	anywhere	O
5	out	O
6	side	O
7	my	O
8	home	O
9	town	O
10	Toledo	B-LOC
11	north	B-LOC
12	Carolina	I-LOC
13	please	O
14	help	O
15	!!!!	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	never	O
3	been	O
4	anywhere	O
5	out	O
6	side	O
7	my	O
8	home	O
9	town	O
10	Henderson	B-LOC
11	north	B-LOC
12	Carolina	I-LOC
13	please	O
14	help	O
15	!!!!	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	this	O
3	at	O
4	age	O
5	13	O
6	in	O
7	Champagne	B-LOC
8	,	O
9	Mozambique	B-LOC
10	and	O
11	it	O
12	was	O
13	the	O
14	most	O
15	amazing	O
16	experice	O
17	of	O
18	my	O
19	upbringing	O
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	this	O
3	at	O
4	age	O
5	13	O
6	in	O
7	Champagne	B-LOC
8	,	O
9	France	B-LOC
10	and	O
11	it	O
12	was	O
13	the	O
14	most	O
15	amazing	O
16	experice	O
17	of	O
18	my	O
19	upbringing	O
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	applied	O
2	to	O
3	get	O
4	a	O
5	student	O
6	visa	O
7	to	O
8	study	O
9	in	O
10	Nigeria	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	I	O
13	received	O
14	one	O
15	that	O
16	is	O
17	valid	O
18	until	O
19	October	O
20	of	O
21	2015	O
22	.	O

0	I	O
1	applied	O
2	to	O
3	get	O
4	a	O
5	student	O
6	visa	O
7	to	O
8	study	O
9	in	O
10	Brazil	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	I	O
13	received	O
14	one	O
15	that	O
16	is	O
17	valid	O
18	until	O
19	October	O
20	of	O
21	2015	O
22	.	O

0	Being	O
1	an	O
2	American	O
3	guarantees	O
4	you	O
5	no	O
6	favours	O
7	when	O
8	it	O
9	come	O
10	to	O
11	going	O
12	to	O
13	Morocco	B-LOC
14	.	O

0	Being	O
1	an	O
2	American	O
3	guarantees	O
4	you	O
5	no	O
6	favours	O
7	when	O
8	it	O
9	come	O
10	to	O
11	going	O
12	to	O
13	Nepal	B-LOC
14	.	O

0	Coming	O
1	to	O
2	stay	O
3	,	O
4	and	O
5	overstay	O
6	your	O
7	three	O
8	months	O
9	visit	O
10	will	O
11	lead	O
12	to	O
13	immediate	O
14	expulsion	O
15	and	O
16	a	O
17	lifetime	O
18	ban	O
19	to	O
20	immigrate	O
21	to	O
22	Peru	B-LOC
23	-	O
24	NOT	O
25	GOOD	O
26	.	O

0	Coming	O
1	to	O
2	stay	O
3	,	O
4	and	O
5	overstay	O
6	your	O
7	three	O
8	months	O
9	visit	O
10	will	O
11	lead	O
12	to	O
13	immediate	O
14	expulsion	O
15	and	O
16	a	O
17	lifetime	O
18	ban	O
19	to	O
20	immigrate	O
21	to	O
22	Madagascar	B-LOC
23	-	O
24	NOT	O
25	GOOD	O
26	.	O

0	Just	O
1	'	O
2	wanting	O
3	to	O
4	come	O
5	to	O
6	Iran	B-LOC
7	"	O
8	is	O
9	NOT	O
10	enough	O
11	.	O

0	Just	O
1	'	O
2	wanting	O
3	to	O
4	come	O
5	to	O
6	China	B-LOC
7	"	O
8	is	O
9	NOT	O
10	enough	O
11	.	O

0	You	O
1	will	O
2	not	O
3	be	O
4	able	O
5	to	O
6	seek	O
7	work	O
8	or	O
9	take	O
10	a	O
11	job	O
12	,	O
13	in	O
14	Iraq	B-LOC
15	,	O
16	with	O
17	out	O
18	having	O
19	to	O
20	show	O
21	your	O
22	Immigration	O
23	VISA	O
24	and	O
25	Canadian	O
26	Social	O
27	Insurance	O
28	Number	O
29	card	O
30	to	O
31	any	O
32	potential	O
33	employer	O
34	.	O

0	You	O
1	will	O
2	not	O
3	be	O
4	able	O
5	to	O
6	seek	O
7	work	O
8	or	O
9	take	O
10	a	O
11	job	O
12	,	O
13	in	O
14	Saudi	B-LOC
15	Arabia	O
16	,	O
17	with	O
18	out	O
19	having	O
20	to	O
21	show	O
22	your	O
23	Immigration	O
24	VISA	O
25	and	O
26	Canadian	O
27	Social	O
28	Insurance	O
29	Number	O
30	card	O
31	to	O
32	any	O
33	potential	O
34	employer	O

0	This	O
1	is	O
2	in	O
3	Stockton	B-LOC
4	of	O
5	course	O
6	,	O
7	the	O
8	rates	O
9	may	O
10	be	O
11	slightly	O
12	different	O
13	for	O
14	other	O
15	provinces	O
16	/	O
17	territories	O
18	.	O

0	This	O
1	is	O
2	in	O
3	Fort	B-LOC
4	Worth	O
5	of	O
6	course	O
7	,	O
8	the	O
9	rates	O
10	may	O
11	be	O
12	slightly	O
13	different	O
14	for	O
15	other	O
16	provinces	O
17	/	O
18	territories	O

0	Start	O
1	here	O
2	if	O
3	you	O
4	were	O
5	born	O
6	in	O
7	Baton	B-LOC
8	Rouge	O

0	Start	O
1	here	O
2	if	O
3	you	O
4	were	O
5	born	O
6	in	O
7	St.	B-LOC
8	Louis	O

0	I	O
1	add	O
2	that	O
3	in	O
4	because	O
5	there	O
6	have	O
7	been	O
8	some	O
9	people	O
10	who	O
11	have	O
12	tried	O
13	to	O
14	claim	O
15	citizenship	O
16	by	O
17	sending	O
18	for	O
19	their	O
20	birth	O
21	certificate	O
22	when	O
23	they	O
24	were	O
25	never	O
26	really	O
27	born	O
28	in	O
29	Iraq	B-LOC
30	or	O
31	to	O
32	Canadian	O
33	parents	O
34	.	O

0	I	O
1	add	O
2	that	O
3	in	O
4	because	O
5	there	O
6	have	O
7	been	O
8	some	O
9	people	O
10	who	O
11	have	O
12	tried	O
13	to	O
14	claim	O
15	citizenship	O
16	by	O
17	sending	O
18	for	O
19	their	O
20	birth	O
21	certificate	O
22	when	O
23	they	O
24	were	O
25	never	O
26	really	O
27	born	O
28	in	O
29	Germany	B-LOC
30	or	O
31	to	O
32	Canadian	O
33	parents	O
34	.	O

0	When	O
1	a	O
2	child	O
3	is	O
4	born	O
5	in	O
6	Iraq	B-LOC
7	the	O
8	birth	O
9	is	O
10	registered	O
11	before	O
12	the	O
13	baby	O
14	can	O
15	leave	O
16	the	O
17	hospital	O
18	.	O

0	When	O
1	a	O
2	child	O
3	is	O
4	born	O
5	in	O
6	Germany	B-LOC
7	the	O
8	birth	O
9	is	O
10	registered	O
11	before	O
12	the	O
13	baby	O
14	can	O
15	leave	O
16	the	O
17	hospital	O
18	.	O

0	Planning	O
1	on	O
2	going	O
3	to	O
4	Sudan	B-LOC
5	in	I-LOC
6	January	O
7	.	O

0	Planning	O
1	on	O
2	going	O
3	to	O
4	Kenya	B-LOC
5	in	I-LOC
6	January	O
7	.	O

0	Have	O
1	fun	O
2	in	O
3	Argentina	B-LOC
4	!!	I-LOC

0	Have	O
1	fun	O
2	in	O
3	Uganda	B-LOC
4	!!	I-LOC

0	(	O
1	ps.	O
2	I	O
3	'm	O
4	assuming	O
5	you	O
6	'll	O
7	stop	O
8	off	O
9	in	O
10	Miami	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	and	O
13	since	O
14	it	O
15	s	O
16	summer	O
17	,	O
18	may	O
19	I	O
20	recommend	O
21	kaffee	O
22	eis	O
23	ice	O
24	creams	O
25	and	O
26	gelatos	O
27	?	O

0	(	O
1	ps.	O
2	I	O
3	'm	O
4	assuming	O
5	you	O
6	'll	O
7	stop	O
8	off	O
9	in	O
10	Fort	B-LOC
11	Wayne	O
12	,	O
13	and	O
14	since	O
15	it	O
16	s	O
17	summer	O
18	,	O
19	may	O
20	I	O
21	recommend	O
22	kaffee	O
23	eis	O
24	ice	O
25	creams	O
26	and	O
27	gelatos	O

0	You	O
1	should	O
2	n't	O
3	ask	O
4	this	O
5	question	O
6	it	O
7	's	O
8	intimidating	O
9	,	O
10	if	O
11	i	O
12	tell	O
13	you	O
14	what	O
15	people	O
16	knows	O
17	about	O
18	Angola	B-LOC
19	you	O
20	will	O
21	blush	O
22	,	O
23	thank	O
24	god	O
25	many	O
26	thinks	O
27	i	O
28	'm	O
29	japanese	O
30	just	O
31	because	O
32	of	O
33	the	O
34	way	O
35	i	O
36	keep	O
37	myself	O
38	,	O
39	the	O
40	way	O
41	i	O
42	talk	O
43	and	O
44	treat	O
45	people	O
46	,	O
47	and	O
48	the	O
49	way	O
50	i	O
51	dress	O
52	,	O
53	so	O
54	if	O
55	you	O
56	do	O
57	n't	O
58	want	O
59	nasty	O
60	,	O
61	insulting	O
62	answers	O
63	especially	O
64	from	O
65	those	O
66	undesirable	O
67	migrants	O
68	like	O
69	puttagenius	O
70	,	O
71	caloy	O
72	,	O
73	gro	O
74	science	O
75	,	O
76	and	O
77	irene	O
78	.	O

0	You	O
1	should	O
2	n't	O
3	ask	O
4	this	O
5	question	O
6	it	O
7	's	O
8	intimidating	O
9	,	O
10	if	O
11	i	O
12	tell	O
13	you	O
14	what	O
15	people	O
16	knows	O
17	about	O
18	Thailand	B-LOC
19	you	O
20	will	O
21	blush	O
22	,	O
23	thank	O
24	god	O
25	many	O
26	thinks	O
27	i	O
28	'm	O
29	japanese	O
30	just	O
31	because	O
32	of	O
33	the	O
34	way	O
35	i	O
36	keep	O
37	myself	O
38	,	O
39	the	O
40	way	O
41	i	O
42	talk	O
43	and	O
44	treat	O
45	people	O
46	,	O
47	and	O
48	the	O
49	way	O
50	i	O
51	dress	O
52	,	O
53	so	O
54	if	O
55	you	O
56	do	O
57	n't	O
58	want	O
59	nasty	O
60	,	O
61	insulting	O
62	answers	O
63	especially	O
64	from	O
65	those	O
66	undesirable	O
67	migrants	O
68	like	O
69	puttagenius	O
70	,	O
71	caloy	O
72	,	O
73	gro	O
74	science	O
75	,	O
76	and	O
77	irene	O
78	.	O

0	In	O
1	fact	O
2	Mexico	B-LOC
3	is	O
4	famous	O
5	to	O
6	accept	O
7	people	O
8	like	O
9	these	O
10	people	O
11	i	O
12	mentioned	O
13	whose	O
14	not	O
15	filipinos	O
16	but	O
17	helping	O
18	the	O
19	Mexico	B-LOC
20	to	O
21	plunge	O
22	in	O
23	the	O
24	pit	O
25	as	O
26	they	O
27	are	O
28	the	O
29	rot	O
30	of	O
31	the	O
32	country	O
33	.	O

0	In	O
1	fact	O
2	Morocco	B-LOC
3	is	O
4	famous	O
5	to	O
6	accept	O
7	people	O
8	like	O
9	these	O
10	people	O
11	i	O
12	mentioned	O
13	whose	O
14	not	O
15	filipinos	O
16	but	O
17	helping	O
18	the	O
19	Morocco	B-LOC
20	to	O
21	plunge	O
22	in	O
23	the	O
24	pit	O
25	as	O
26	they	O
27	are	O
28	the	O
29	rot	O
30	of	O
31	the	O
32	country	O
33	.	O

0	A	O
1	single	O
2	call	O
3	to	O
4	CIC	B-ORG
5	will	O
6	confirm	O
7	there	O
8	is	O
9	NO	O
10	such	O
11	thing	O
12	as	O
13	a	O
14	BTA	O
15	to	O
16	Morocco	B-LOC
17	and	O
18	anyone	O
19	asking	O
20	for	O
21	this	O
22	is	O
23	a	O
24	scammer	O
25	http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/contacts/index.asp	O

0	A	O
1	single	O
2	call	O
3	to	O
4	CIC	B-ORG
5	will	O
6	confirm	O
7	there	O
8	is	O
9	NO	O
10	such	O
11	thing	O
12	as	O
13	a	O
14	BTA	O
15	to	O
16	Peru	B-LOC
17	and	O
18	anyone	O
19	asking	O
20	for	O
21	this	O
22	is	O
23	a	O
24	scammer	O
25	http://www.cic.gc.ca/english/contacts/index.asp	O

0	The	O
1	below	O
2	site	O
3	from	O
4	the	O
5	US	B-LOC
6	government	O
7	verifies	O
8	this	O
9	-	O
10	it	O
11	's	O
12	the	O
13	same	O
14	for	O
15	Morocco	B-LOC
16	,	O
17	too	O
18	.....	O

0	The	O
1	below	O
2	site	O
3	from	O
4	the	O
5	US	B-LOC
6	government	O
7	verifies	O
8	this	O
9	-	O
10	it	O
11	's	O
12	the	O
13	same	O
14	for	O
15	Korea	B-LOC
16	,	O
17	too	O
18	.....	O

0	What	O
1	are	O
2	some	O
3	fun	O
4	things	O
5	I	O
6	could	O
7	do	O
8	while	O
9	in	O
10	France	B-LOC
11	?	O

0	What	O
1	are	O
2	some	O
3	fun	O
4	things	O
5	I	O
6	could	O
7	do	O
8	while	O
9	in	O
10	Kenya	B-LOC
11	?	O

0	Otherwise	O
1	,	O
2	you	O
3	can	O
4	do	O
5	what	O
6	you	O
7	can	O
8	do	O
9	in	O
10	other	O
11	parts	O
12	or	O
13	South	B-LOC
14	Africa	O
15	,	O
16	like	O
17	shopping	O
18	,	O
19	eating	O
20	,	O
21	etc	O

0	Otherwise	O
1	,	O
2	you	O
3	can	O
4	do	O
5	what	O
6	you	O
7	can	O
8	do	O
9	in	O
10	other	O
11	parts	O
12	or	O
13	Japan	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	like	O
16	shopping	O
17	,	O
18	eating	O
19	,	O
20	etc	O
21	.	O

0	Okinawa	B-LOC
1	is	O
2	quite	O
3	different	O
4	from	O
5	the	O
6	rest	O
7	of	O
8	Thailand	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	although	O
11	of	O
12	course	O
13	there	O
14	are	O
15	similarities	O
16	.	O

0	Okinawa	B-LOC
1	is	O
2	quite	O
3	different	O
4	from	O
5	the	O
6	rest	O
7	of	O
8	Vietnam	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	although	O
11	of	O
12	course	O
13	there	O
14	are	O
15	similarities	O
16	.	O

0	"	O
1	If	O
2	the	O
3	Canadian	O
4	Immigration	O
5	Visa	O
6	Officer	O
7	believes	O
8	that	O
9	the	O
10	point	O
11	total	O
12	does	O
13	not	O
14	accurately	O
15	reflect	O
16	your	O
17	ability	O
18	to	O
19	become	O
20	economically	O
21	established	O
22	in	O
23	Nepal	B-LOC
24	,	O
25	the	O
26	Canadian	O
27	Immigration	O
28	Visa	O
29	Officer	O
30	may	O
31	use	O
32	his	O
33	or	O
34	her	O
35	positive	O
36	discretion	O
37	(	O
38	referred	O
39	to	O
40	as	O
41	substituted	O
42	evaluation	O
43	)	O
44	and	O
45	approve	O
46	your	O
47	application	O
48	even	O
49	though	O
50	you	O
51	score	O
52	less	O
53	than	O
54	67	O
55	points	O
56	.	O
57	"	O

0	"	O
1	If	O
2	the	O
3	Canadian	O
4	Immigration	O
5	Visa	O
6	Officer	O
7	believes	O
8	that	O
9	the	O
10	point	O
11	total	O
12	does	O
13	not	O
14	accurately	O
15	reflect	O
16	your	O
17	ability	O
18	to	O
19	become	O
20	economically	O
21	established	O
22	in	O
23	Indonesia	B-LOC
24	,	O
25	the	O
26	Canadian	O
27	Immigration	O
28	Visa	O
29	Officer	O
30	may	O
31	use	O
32	his	O
33	or	O
34	her	O
35	positive	O
36	discretion	O
37	(	O
38	referred	O
39	to	O
40	as	O
41	substituted	O
42	evaluation	O
43	)	O
44	and	O
45	approve	O
46	your	O
47	application	O
48	even	O
49	though	O
50	you	O
51	score	O
52	less	O
53	than	O
54	67	O
55	points	O
56	.	O
57	"	O

0	From	O
1	my	O
2	experience	O
3	Hens	O
4	(	O
5	Not	O
6	roosters	O
7	)	O
8	are	O
9	very	O
10	friendly	O
11	with	O
12	duck	O
13	,	O
14	Venezuela	O
15	pigs	O
16	,	O
17	kittens	O
18	,	O
19	cows	O
20	,	O
21	Rabbits	O
22	,	O
23	etc	O
24	.	O

0	From	O
1	my	O
2	experience	O
3	Hens	O
4	(	O
5	Not	O
6	roosters	O
7	)	O
8	are	O
9	very	O
10	friendly	O
11	with	O
12	duck	O
13	,	O
14	Algeria	O
15	pigs	O
16	,	O
17	kittens	O
18	,	O
19	cows	O
20	,	O
21	Rabbits	O
22	,	O
23	etc	O
24	.	O

0	The	O
1	India	O
2	pig	O
3	is	O
4	better	O
5	because	O
6	it	O
7	s	O
8	a	O
9	lot	O
10	larger	O
11	than	O
12	a	O
13	hamster	O
14	,	O
15	rat	O
16	,	O
17	mouse	O
18	,	O
19	or	O
20	degu	O
21	.	O

0	The	O
1	Iran	O
2	pig	O
3	is	O
4	better	O
5	because	O
6	it	O
7	s	O
8	a	O
9	lot	O
10	larger	O
11	than	O
12	a	O
13	hamster	O
14	,	O
15	rat	O
16	,	O
17	mouse	O
18	,	O
19	or	O
20	degu	O
21	.	O

0	So	O
1	my	O
2	opinion	O
3	is	O
4	Sudan	O
5	pigs	O
6	.	O

0	So	O
1	my	O
2	opinion	O
3	is	O
4	Japan	O
5	pigs	O
6	.	O

0	Algeria	O
1	pigs	O
2	(	O
3	also	O
4	called	O
5	cavies	O
6	)	O
7	are	O
8	gentle	O
9	creatures	O
10	and	O
11	are	O
12	awake	O
13	during	O
14	the	O
15	day	O
16	and	O
17	sleep	O
18	at	O
19	night	O
20	.	O

0	India	O
1	pigs	O
2	(	O
3	also	O
4	called	O
5	cavies	O
6	)	O
7	are	O
8	gentle	O
9	creatures	O
10	and	O
11	are	O
12	awake	O
13	during	O
14	the	O
15	day	O
16	and	O
17	sleep	O
18	at	O
19	night	O
20	.	O

0	Big	O
1	Cities	O
2	like	O
3	Anaheim	B-LOC
4	,	I-LOC
5	Boston	O
6	,	B-LOC
7	Philadelphia	O
8	on	B-LOC
9	the	O
10	East	O
11	Coast	O
12	.	O

0	Big	O
1	Cities	O
2	like	O
3	New	B-LOC
4	York	I-LOC
5	,	O
6	Richmond	B-LOC
7	,	O
8	Philadelphia	B-LOC
9	on	O
10	the	O
11	East	O
12	Coast	O
13	.	O

0	Beaches	O
1	and	O
2	Disney	B-ORG
3	of	O
4	Florida	B-LOC
5	or	O
6	the	O
7	Mid	O
8	Atlantic	O
9	cities	O
10	of	O
11	Atlanta	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	Savannah	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	Colorado	B-LOC
16	Springs	O

0	Beaches	O
1	and	O
2	Disney	B-ORG
3	of	O
4	Florida	B-LOC
5	or	O
6	the	O
7	Mid	O
8	Atlantic	O
9	cities	O
10	of	O
11	Atlanta	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	Savannah	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	Anaheim	B-LOC
16	.	O

0	Southern	O
1	charm	O
2	of	O
3	Nashville	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	Henderson	B-LOC
6	,	O
7	New	B-LOC
8	Orleans	I-LOC
9	or	O
10	Charlotte	B-LOC
11	.	O

0	Southern	O
1	charm	O
2	of	O
3	Nashville	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	Birmingham	B-LOC
6	,	O
7	Hialeah	B-LOC
8	or	I-LOC
9	Charlotte	O
10	.	B-LOC

0	West	O
1	Coast	O
2	hot	O
3	spots	O
4	like	O
5	Seattle	B-LOC
6	,	O
7	Boise	B-LOC
8	City	O
9	,	B-LOC
10	San	I-LOC
11	Francisco	O
12	,	B-LOC
13	Los	I-LOC
14	Angeles	O
15	or	B-LOC
16	San	I-LOC
17	Diego	O

0	West	O
1	Coast	O
2	hot	O
3	spots	O
4	like	O
5	Seattle	B-LOC
6	,	O
7	Portland	B-LOC
8	,	O
9	San	B-LOC
10	Francisco	I-LOC
11	,	O
12	Norfolk	B-LOC
13	or	I-LOC
14	San	O
15	Diego	B-LOC
16	.	I-LOC

0	I	O
1	could	O
2	spend	O
3	a	O
4	year	O
5	in	O
6	India	B-LOC
7	alone	O
8	.	O

0	I	O
1	could	O
2	spend	O
3	a	O
4	year	O
5	in	O
6	Bangladesh	B-LOC
7	alone	O
8	.	O

0	A	O
1	road	O
2	trip	O
3	to	O
4	Lisbon	B-LOC
5	and	O
6	the	O
7	Algarve	B-LOC
8	in	O
9	Portugal	B-LOC
10	before	O
11	a	O
12	mountain	O
13	escape	O
14	in	O
15	the	O
16	Pyrenees	B-LOC
17	and	O
18	a	O
19	stop	O
20	in	O
21	Andorra	B-LOC
22	before	O
23	heading	O
24	over	O
25	to	O
26	France	B-LOC
27	and	O
28	Italy	B-LOC
29	and	O
30	Afghanistan	B-LOC
31	and	O
32	Switzerland	B-LOC
33	.	O

0	A	O
1	road	O
2	trip	O
3	to	O
4	Lisbon	B-LOC
5	and	O
6	the	O
7	Algarve	B-LOC
8	in	O
9	Portugal	B-LOC
10	before	O
11	a	O
12	mountain	O
13	escape	O
14	in	O
15	the	O
16	Pyrenees	B-LOC
17	and	O
18	a	O
19	stop	O
20	in	O
21	Andorra	B-LOC
22	before	O
23	heading	O
24	over	O
25	to	O
26	France	B-LOC
27	and	O
28	Italy	B-LOC
29	and	O
30	Austria	B-LOC
31	and	O
32	Pakistan	B-LOC
33	.	O

0	Can	O
1	I	O
2	text	O
3	from	O
4	Pakistan	B-LOC
5	to	O
6	the	O
7	united	B-LOC
8	states	I-LOC
9	?	O

0	Can	O
1	I	O
2	text	O
3	from	O
4	Thailand	B-LOC
5	to	O
6	the	O
7	united	B-LOC
8	states	I-LOC
9	?	O

0	You	O
1	may	O
2	want	O
3	to	O
4	get	O
5	a	O
6	temporary	O
7	phone	O
8	for	O
9	your	O
10	trip	O
11	to	O
12	Peru	B-LOC
13	.	O

0	You	O
1	may	O
2	want	O
3	to	O
4	get	O
5	a	O
6	temporary	O
7	phone	O
8	for	O
9	your	O
10	trip	O
11	to	O
12	Spain	B-LOC
13	.	O

0	Switzerland	B-LOC
1	is	O
2	one	O
3	,	O
4	and	O
5	the	B-LOC
6	India	I-LOC
7	are	O
8	passing	O
9	the	O
10	same	O
11	law	O
12	.	O

0	Sudan	B-LOC
1	is	O
2	one	O
3	,	O
4	and	O
5	the	B-LOC
6	Netherlands	I-LOC
7	are	O
8	passing	O
9	the	O
10	same	O
11	law	O
12	.	O

0	Our	O
1	first	O
2	diagnosed	O
3	EPM	O
4	horse	O
5	was	O
6	back	O
7	when	O
8	there	O
9	was	O
10	no	O
11	treatment	O
12	in	O
13	the	O
14	US	B-LOC
15	and	O
16	only	O
17	an	O
18	experimental	O
19	chicken	O
20	feed	O
21	additive	O
22	in	O
23	Turkey	B-LOC
24	.	O

0	Our	O
1	first	O
2	diagnosed	O
3	EPM	O
4	horse	O
5	was	O
6	back	O
7	when	O
8	there	O
9	was	O
10	no	O
11	treatment	O
12	in	O
13	the	O
14	US	B-LOC
15	and	O
16	only	O
17	an	O
18	experimental	O
19	chicken	O
20	feed	O
21	additive	O
22	in	O
23	Mozambique	B-LOC
24	.	O

0	cheapest	O
1	plastic	O
2	surgeons	O
3	in	O
4	Myanmar	B-LOC
5	?	O

0	cheapest	O
1	plastic	O
2	surgeons	O
3	in	O
4	Uganda	B-LOC
5	?	O

0	I	O
1	want	O
2	to	O
3	go	O
4	to	O
5	thailand	B-LOC
6	to	O
7	do	O
8	my	O
9	boob	O
10	job	O
11	from	O
12	Vietnam	B-LOC
13	but	I-LOC
14	looking	O
15	for	O
16	the	O
17	cheapest	O
18	surgeons	O
19	yet	O
20	also	O
21	good	O
22	in	O
23	his	O
24	artwork	O
25	on	O
26	a	O
27	human	O
28	s	O
29	body	O
30	.	O

0	I	O
1	want	O
2	to	O
3	go	O
4	to	O
5	thailand	B-LOC
6	to	O
7	do	O
8	my	O
9	boob	O
10	job	O
11	from	O
12	Kenya	B-LOC
13	but	I-LOC
14	looking	O
15	for	O
16	the	O
17	cheapest	O
18	surgeons	O
19	yet	O
20	also	O
21	good	O
22	in	O
23	his	O
24	artwork	O
25	on	O
26	a	O
27	human	O
28	s	O
29	body	O
30	.	O

0	Aplo.	O
1	lineatus	O
2	are	O
3	wide	O
4	-	O
5	spread	O
6	over	O
7	southern	O
8	Canada	O
9	.	O

0	Aplo.	O
1	lineatus	O
2	are	O
3	wide	O
4	-	O
5	spread	O
6	over	O
7	southern	O
8	Myanmar	O
9	.	O

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	do	O
3	n't	O
4	forget	O
5	to	O
6	try	O
7	out	O
8	Egypt	B-LOC
9	's	O
10	famous	O
11	amusement	O
12	parks	O
13	!	O
14	:	O
15	Lotte	B-LOC
16	World	I-LOC
17	,	O
18	Everland	B-LOC
19	,	O
20	and	O
21	Carribbean	B-LOC
22	Bay	I-LOC
23	!	O

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	do	O
3	n't	O
4	forget	O
5	to	O
6	try	O
7	out	O
8	Mozambique	B-LOC
9	's	O
10	famous	O
11	amusement	O
12	parks	O
13	!	O
14	:	O
15	Lotte	B-LOC
16	World	I-LOC
17	,	O
18	Everland	B-LOC
19	,	O
20	and	O
21	Carribbean	B-LOC
22	Bay	I-LOC
23	!	O

0	Have	O
1	fun	O
2	in	O
3	Turkey	B-LOC
4	~	O

0	Have	O
1	fun	O
2	in	O
3	Ethiopia	B-LOC
4	~	O

0	Saturday	O
1	probably	O
2	works	O
3	better	O
4	for	O
5	me	O
6	,	O
7	just	O
8	so	O
9	that	O
10	I	O
11	am	O
12	back	O
13	in	O
14	Plano	B-LOC
15	and	O
16	doing	O
17	laundry	O
18	by	O
19	Sunday	O
20	afternoon	O
21	!!	O

0	Saturday	O
1	probably	O
2	works	O
3	better	O
4	for	O
5	me	O
6	,	O
7	just	O
8	so	O
9	that	O
10	I	O
11	am	O
12	back	O
13	in	O
14	Mesa	B-LOC
15	and	O
16	doing	O
17	laundry	O
18	by	O
19	Sunday	O
20	afternoon	O
21	!!	O

0	The	O
1	last	O
2	I	O
3	knew	O
4	after	O
5	you	O
6	and	O
7	Brent	B-PER
8	drafted	O
9	this	O
10	starting	O
11	point	O
12	for	O
13	fundamental	O
14	operating	O
15	standards	O
16	was	O
17	that	O
18	this	O
19	was	O
20	being	O
21	circulated	O
22	(	O
23	Shona	B-PER
24	took	O
25	this	O
26	to	O
27	do	O
28	after	O
29	Brent	B-PER
30	's	O
31	return	O
32	to	O
33	St.	B-LOC
34	Paul	O
35	)	O
36	for	O
37	comments	O
38	to	O
39	all	O
40	business	O
41	controllers	O

0	The	O
1	last	O
2	I	O
3	knew	O
4	after	O
5	you	O
6	and	O
7	Brent	B-PER
8	drafted	O
9	this	O
10	starting	O
11	point	O
12	for	O
13	fundamental	O
14	operating	O
15	standards	O
16	was	O
17	that	O
18	this	O
19	was	O
20	being	O
21	circulated	O
22	(	O
23	Shona	B-PER
24	took	O
25	this	O
26	to	O
27	do	O
28	after	O
29	Brent	B-PER
30	's	O
31	return	O
32	to	O
33	Arlington	B-LOC
34	)	O
35	for	O
36	comments	O
37	to	O
38	all	O
39	business	O
40	controllers	O
41	.	O

0	This	O
1	also	O
2	will	O
3	serve	O
4	as	O
5	a	O
6	reminder	O
7	that	O
8	an	O
9	all	O
10	-	O
11	Party	O
12	meeting	O
13	is	O
14	scheduled	O
15	at	O
16	PG&E	B-ORG
17	's	O
18	headquarters	O
19	in	O
20	Baltimore	B-LOC
21	on	I-LOC
22	January	O
23	10	O
24	and	O
25	11	O
26	,	O
27	to	O
28	discuss	O
29	this	O
30	proposal	O
31	and	O
32	to	O
33	respond	O
34	to	O
35	your	O
36	questions	O
37	.	O

0	This	O
1	also	O
2	will	O
3	serve	O
4	as	O
5	a	O
6	reminder	O
7	that	O
8	an	O
9	all	O
10	-	O
11	Party	O
12	meeting	O
13	is	O
14	scheduled	O
15	at	O
16	PG&E	B-ORG
17	's	O
18	headquarters	O
19	in	O
20	Lubbock	B-LOC
21	on	I-LOC
22	January	O
23	10	O
24	and	O
25	11	O
26	,	O
27	to	O
28	discuss	O
29	this	O
30	proposal	O
31	and	O
32	to	O
33	respond	O
34	to	O
35	your	O
36	questions	O
37	.	O

0	IEP	B-ORG
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	hosting	O
4	a	O
5	dinner	O
6	for	O
7	California	B-LOC
8	Governor	O
9	Gray	B-PER
10	Davis	I-PER
11	on	O
12	Thursday	O
13	,	O
14	December	O
15	7	O
16	,	O
17	2000	O
18	at	O
19	the	O
20	historic	O
21	Julia	B-LOC
22	Morgan	I-LOC
23	House	I-LOC
24	in	O
25	Sacramento	B-LOC
26	.	O

0	IEP	B-ORG
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	hosting	O
4	a	O
5	dinner	O
6	for	O
7	California	B-LOC
8	Governor	O
9	Gray	B-PER
10	Davis	I-PER
11	on	O
12	Thursday	O
13	,	O
14	December	O
15	7	O
16	,	O
17	2000	O
18	at	O
19	the	O
20	historic	O
21	Julia	B-LOC
22	Morgan	I-LOC
23	House	I-LOC
24	in	O
25	Atlanta	B-LOC
26	.	O

0	I	O
1	'll	O
2	be	O
3	in	O
4	Stockton	B-LOC
5	but	O
6	can	O
7	call	O
8	you	O
9	.	O

0	I	O
1	'll	O
2	be	O
3	in	O
4	Stockton	B-LOC
5	but	O
6	can	O
7	call	O
8	you	O
9	.	O

0	Chris	B-PER
1	Enron	B-ORG
2	Canada	I-ORG
3	Corp.	I-ORG
4	Suite	O
5	1100	O
6	,	O
7	70	O
8	York	O
9	Street	O
10	Toronto	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	St.	B-LOC
13	Petersburg	O
14	M5J	O
15	1S9	O

0	Chris	B-PER
1	Enron	B-ORG
2	Canada	I-ORG
3	Corp.	I-ORG
4	Suite	O
5	1100	O
6	,	O
7	70	O
8	York	O
9	Street	O
10	Toronto	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	Mesa	B-LOC
13	M5J	O
14	1S9	O
15	416-865-3700	O

0	I	O
1	say	O
2	we	O
3	just	O
4	keep	O
5	the	O
6	dough	O
7	and	O
8	go	O
9	to	O
10	Algeria	B-LOC
11	.	O

0	I	O
1	say	O
2	we	O
3	just	O
4	keep	O
5	the	O
6	dough	O
7	and	O
8	go	O
9	to	O
10	Turkey	B-LOC
11	.	O

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	as	O
3	I	O
4	mentioned	O
5	to	O
6	you	O
7	,	O
8	we	O
9	have	O
10	faxed	O
11	your	O
12	mark	O
13	-	O
14	up	O
15	to	O
16	Melanie	B-PER
17	Gray	I-PER
18	at	O
19	Weil	B-ORG
20	Gotschal	I-ORG
21	in	O
22	Omaha	B-LOC
23	to	O
24	keep	O
25	her	O
26	informed	O
27	.	O

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	as	O
3	I	O
4	mentioned	O
5	to	O
6	you	O
7	,	O
8	we	O
9	have	O
10	faxed	O
11	your	O
12	mark	O
13	-	O
14	up	O
15	to	O
16	Melanie	B-PER
17	Gray	I-PER
18	at	O
19	Weil	B-ORG
20	Gotschal	I-ORG
21	in	O
22	St.	B-LOC
23	Louis	O
24	to	O
25	keep	O
26	her	O
27	informed	O

0	David	B-PER
1	T.	I-PER
2	Metcalfe	I-PER
3	Cullen	B-ORG
4	and	I-ORG
5	Dykman	I-ORG
6	LLP	I-ORG
7	177	O
8	Montague	O
9	Street	O
10	Brooklyn	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	Colorado	B-LOC
13	Springs	I-LOC
14	11201	O
15	phone	O
16	:	O
17	718-780-0046	O
18	fax	O
19	:	O
20	718-780-0276	O
21	e-mail	O
22	:	O
23	dmetcalfe@cullenanddykman.com	O

0	David	B-PER
1	T.	I-PER
2	Metcalfe	I-PER
3	Cullen	B-ORG
4	and	I-ORG
5	Dykman	I-ORG
6	LLP	I-ORG
7	177	O
8	Montague	O
9	Street	O
10	Brooklyn	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	Dallas	B-LOC
13	11201	I-LOC
14	phone	O
15	:	O
16	718-780-0046	O
17	fax	O
18	:	O
19	718-780-0276	O
20	e-mail	O
21	:	O
22	dmetcalfe@cullenanddykman.com	O

0	Barbara	B-PER
1	Walters	I-PER
2	did	O
3	a	O
4	story	O
5	on	O
6	gender	O
7	roles	O
8	in	O
9	Pakistan	B-LOC
10	several	O
11	years	O
12	before	O
13	the	O
14	Gulf	O
15	War	O
16	.	O

0	Barbara	B-PER
1	Walters	I-PER
2	did	O
3	a	O
4	story	O
5	on	O
6	gender	O
7	roles	O
8	in	O
9	Argentina	B-LOC
10	several	O
11	years	O
12	before	O
13	the	O
14	Gulf	O
15	War	O
16	.	O

0	She	O
1	returned	O
2	to	O
3	Russian	B-LOC
4	Federation	O
5	recently	O
6	and	O
7	observed	O
8	that	O
9	the	O
10	men	O
11	now	O
12	walked	O
13	several	O
14	yards	O
15	behind	O
16	their	O
17	wives	O

0	She	O
1	returned	O
2	to	O
3	Italy	B-LOC
4	recently	O
5	and	O
6	observed	O
7	that	O
8	the	O
9	men	O
10	now	O
11	walked	O
12	several	O
13	yards	O
14	behind	O
15	their	O
16	wives	O
17	.	O

0	Peter	B-PER
1	Percell	I-PER
2	10030	O
3	Doliver	O
4	Drive	O
5	percell@swbell.net	O
6	Arlington	B-LOC
7	,	O
8	TX	B-LOC
9	77042-2016	O
10	(	O
11	713	O
12	)	O
13	532-3836	O
14	voice	O
15	&	O
16	fax	O

0	Peter	B-PER
1	Percell	I-PER
2	10030	O
3	Doliver	O
4	Drive	O
5	percell@swbell.net	O
6	Reno	B-LOC
7	,	O
8	TX	B-LOC
9	77042-2016	O
10	(	O
11	713	O
12	)	O
13	532-3836	O
14	voice	O
15	&	O
16	fax	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	completing	O
4	my	O
5	tour	O
6	of	O
7	duty	O
8	in	O
9	Japan	B-LOC
10	in	O
11	September	O
12	of	O
13	this	O
14	year	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	completing	O
4	my	O
5	tour	O
6	of	O
7	duty	O
8	in	O
9	Uzbekistan	B-LOC
10	in	O
11	September	O
12	of	O
13	this	O
14	year	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	talking	O
3	to	O
4	a	O
5	number	O
6	of	O
7	people	O
8	regarding	O
9	opportunities	O
10	for	O
11	a	O
12	new	O
13	assignment	O
14	back	O
15	in	O
16	Lincoln	B-LOC
17	office	O
18	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	talking	O
3	to	O
4	a	O
5	number	O
6	of	O
7	people	O
8	regarding	O
9	opportunities	O
10	for	O
11	a	O
12	new	O
13	assignment	O
14	back	O
15	in	O
16	New	B-LOC
17	York	O
18	office	O

0	Thought	O
1	since	O
2	I	O
3	will	O
4	be	O
5	in	O
6	Washington	B-LOC
7	,	O
8	stop	O
9	by	O
10	your	O
11	office	O
12	for	O
13	few	O
14	minutes	O
15	.	O

0	Thought	O
1	since	O
2	I	O
3	will	O
4	be	O
5	in	O
6	Plano	B-LOC
7	,	O
8	stop	O
9	by	O
10	your	O
11	office	O
12	for	O
13	few	O
14	minutes	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	in	O
4	Toledo	B-LOC
5	on	O
6	May	O
7	11th	O
8	and	O
9	would	O
10	like	O
11	to	O
12	visit	O
13	with	O
14	you	O
15	in	O
16	early	O
17	afternoon	O
18	if	O
19	possible	O
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	in	O
4	Baton	B-LOC
5	Rouge	O
6	on	O
7	May	O
8	11th	O
9	and	O
10	would	O
11	like	O
12	to	O
13	visit	O
14	with	O
15	you	O
16	in	O
17	early	O
18	afternoon	O
19	if	O
20	possible	O

0	Preseason	O
1	Game	O
2	A	O
3	:	O
4	Saturday	O
5	,	O
6	May	O
7	12	O
8	@	O
9	7:30	O
10	PM	O
11	vs.	O
12	Cleveland	B-LOC
13	SOL	B-ORG

0	Preseason	O
1	Game	O
2	A	O
3	:	O
4	Saturday	O
5	,	O
6	May	O
7	12	O
8	@	O
9	7:30	O
10	PM	O
11	vs.	O
12	Minneapolis	B-LOC
13	SOL	B-ORG

0	Preseason	O
1	Game	O
2	B	O
3	:	O
4	Thursday	O
5	,	O
6	May	O
7	24	O
8	@	O
9	7:30	O
10	PM	O
11	vs.	O
12	Irvine	B-LOC
13	SHOCK	B-ORG

0	Preseason	O
1	Game	O
2	B	O
3	:	O
4	Thursday	O
5	,	O
6	May	O
7	24	O
8	@	O
9	7:30	O
10	PM	O
11	vs.	O
12	Miami	B-LOC
13	SHOCK	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	1	O
2	:	O
3	Monday	O
4	,	O
5	May	O
6	28	O
7	@	O
8	2:00	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	El	B-LOC
12	Paso	I-LOC
13	SPARKS	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	1	O
2	:	O
3	Monday	O
4	,	O
5	May	O
6	28	O
7	@	O
8	2:00	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Tampa	B-LOC
12	SPARKS	I-LOC

0	Game	O
1	3	O
2	:	O
3	Monday	O
4	,	O
5	June	O
6	11	O
7	@	O
8	7:00	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Riverside	B-LOC
12	SPARKS	I-LOC

0	Game	O
1	3	O
2	:	O
3	Monday	O
4	,	O
5	June	O
6	11	O
7	@	O
8	7:00	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Glendale	B-LOC
12	SPARKS	I-LOC

0	Game	O
1	4	O
2	:	O
3	Thursday	O
4	,	O
5	June	O
6	14	O
7	@	O
8	7:30	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Greensboro	B-LOC
12	FIRE	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	4	O
2	:	O
3	Thursday	O
4	,	O
5	June	O
6	14	O
7	@	O
8	7:30	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Albuquerque	B-LOC
12	FIRE	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	6	O
2	:	O
3	Tuesday	O
4	,	O
5	June	O
6	19	O
7	@	O
8	7:30	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Atlanta	B-LOC
12	MYSTICS	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	6	O
2	:	O
3	Tuesday	O
4	,	O
5	June	O
6	19	O
7	@	O
8	7:30	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Durham	B-LOC
12	MYSTICS	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	7	O
2	:	O
3	Saturday	O
4	,	O
5	June	O
6	23	O
7	@	O
8	3:00	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Fremont	B-LOC
12	MONARCHS	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	7	O
2	:	O
3	Saturday	O
4	,	O
5	June	O
6	23	O
7	@	O
8	3:00	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Anaheim	B-LOC
12	MONARCHS	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	8	O
2	:	O
3	Monday	O
4	,	O
5	July	O
6	2	O
7	@	O
8	7:30	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Charlotte	B-LOC
12	FIRE	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	8	O
2	:	O
3	Monday	O
4	,	O
5	July	O
6	2	O
7	@	O
8	7:30	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Lubbock	B-LOC
12	FIRE	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	10	O
2	:	O
3	Sunday	O
4	,	O
5	July	O
6	8	O
7	@	O
8	1:00	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Detroit	B-LOC
12	ROCKERS	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	10	O
2	:	O
3	Sunday	O
4	,	O
5	July	O
6	8	O
7	@	O
8	1:00	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Boston	B-LOC
12	ROCKERS	B-ORG

0	Game	O
1	12	O
2	:	O
3	Saturday	O
4	,	O
5	July	O
6	28	O
7	@	O
8	12:30	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Omaha	B-LOC
12	LIBERTY	I-LOC

0	Game	O
1	12	O
2	:	O
3	Saturday	O
4	,	O
5	July	O
6	28	O
7	@	O
8	12:30	O
9	PM	O
10	vs.	O
11	Pittsburgh	B-LOC
12	LIBERTY	I-LOC

0	Ma	O
1	said	O
2	she	O
3	had	O
4	a	O
5	great	O
6	time	O
7	in	O
8	Toledo	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	She	O
11	was	O
12	happy	O
13	to	O
14	see	O
15	yourself	O
16	,	O
17	as	O
18	well	O
19	as	O
20	C	B-PER
21	&	O
22	D	B-PER
23	.	O

0	Ma	O
1	said	O
2	she	O
3	had	O
4	a	O
5	great	O
6	time	O
7	in	O
8	Lexington-Fayette	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	She	O
11	was	O
12	happy	O
13	to	O
14	see	O
15	yourself	O
16	,	O
17	as	O
18	well	O
19	as	O
20	C	B-PER
21	&	O
22	D	B-PER
23	.	O

0	Radianz	B-ORG
1	1251	O
2	Avenue	O
3	of	O
4	the	O
5	Americas	O
6	7th	O
7	Floor	O
8	Virginia	B-LOC
9	Beach	I-LOC
10	,	O
11	NY	B-LOC
12	10016	O
13	USA	O
14	Phone	O
15	:	O
16	+1	O
17	(	O
18	212	O
19	)	O
20	899-4425	O
21	Fax	O
22	:	O
23	+1	O
24	(	O
25	212	O
26	)	O
27	899-4310	O
28	Cell	O
29	:	O
30	+1	O
31	(	O
32	917	O
33	)	O
34	859-7187	O
35	Email	O
36	:	O
37	kyle.jones@radianz.com	O

0	Radianz	B-ORG
1	1251	O
2	Avenue	O
3	of	O
4	the	O
5	Americas	O
6	7th	O
7	Floor	O
8	Irvine	B-LOC
9	,	I-LOC
10	NY	O
11	10016	B-LOC
12	USA	O
13	Phone	O
14	:	O
15	+1	O
16	(	O
17	212	O
18	)	O
19	899-4425	O
20	Fax	O
21	:	O
22	+1	O
23	(	O
24	212	O
25	)	O
26	899-4310	O
27	Cell	O
28	:	O
29	+1	O
30	(	O
31	917	O
32	)	O
33	859-7187	O
34	Email	O
35	:	O
36	kyle.jones@radianz.com	O

0	Per	O
1	my	O
2	conversation	O
3	with	O
4	Edmund	B-PER
5	this	O
6	morning	O
7	,	O
8	we	O
9	are	O
10	moving	O
11	the	O
12	following	O
13	countries	O
14	to	O
15	the	O
16	non-approved	O
17	list	O
18	:	O
19	Austria	B-LOC
20	,	O
21	Belgium	B-LOC
22	,	O
23	Croatia	B-LOC
24	,	O
25	United	B-LOC
26	States	I-LOC
27	,	O
28	Denmark	B-LOC
29	,	O
30	Poland	B-LOC
31	,	O
32	Portugal	B-LOC
33	,	O
34	Romania	B-LOC
35	,	O
36	Singapore	B-LOC
37	,	O
38	and	O
39	Slovenia	B-LOC
40	.	O

0	Per	O
1	my	O
2	conversation	O
3	with	O
4	Edmund	B-PER
5	this	O
6	morning	O
7	,	O
8	we	O
9	are	O
10	moving	O
11	the	O
12	following	O
13	countries	O
14	to	O
15	the	O
16	non-approved	O
17	list	O
18	:	O
19	Austria	B-LOC
20	,	O
21	Belgium	B-LOC
22	,	O
23	Croatia	B-LOC
24	,	O
25	Czech	B-LOC
26	Republic	I-LOC
27	,	O
28	Denmark	B-LOC
29	,	O
30	Poland	B-LOC
31	,	O
32	Pakistan	B-LOC
33	,	O
34	Romania	B-LOC
35	,	O
36	Singapore	B-LOC
37	,	O
38	and	O
39	Slovenia	B-LOC
40	.	O

0	Jurisdictions	O
1	which	O
2	are	O
3	are	O
4	approved	O
5	to	O
6	trade	O
7	credit	O
8	derivatives	O
9	:	O
10	Finland	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	Colombia	B-LOC
13	,	O
14	Norway	B-LOC
15	,	O
16	Sweden	B-LOC
17	,	O
18	Switzerland	B-LOC
19	,	O
20	the	O
21	U.K	B-LOC
22	,	O
23	and	O
24	the	O
25	U.S.	B-LOC
26	.	O

0	Jurisdictions	O
1	which	O
2	are	O
3	are	O
4	approved	O
5	to	O
6	trade	O
7	credit	O
8	derivatives	O
9	:	O
10	Finland	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	Germany	B-LOC
13	,	O
14	Yemen	B-LOC
15	,	O
16	Sweden	B-LOC
17	,	O
18	Switzerland	B-LOC
19	,	O
20	the	O
21	U.K	B-LOC
22	,	O
23	and	O
24	the	O
25	U.S.	B-LOC
26	.	O

0	Jurisdictions	O
1	which	O
2	are	O
3	not	O
4	approved	O
5	to	O
6	trade	O
7	credit	O
8	derivatives	O
9	include	O
10	:	O
11	Austria	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	Belgium	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	Canada	B-LOC
16	,	O
17	Kenya	B-LOC
18	,	O
19	Czech	B-LOC
20	Republic	I-LOC
21	,	O
22	Denmark	B-LOC
23	,	O
24	France	B-LOC
25	,	O
26	Gibraltar	B-LOC
27	,	O
28	Ireland	B-LOC
29	,	O
30	Italy	B-LOC
31	,	O
32	Poland	B-LOC
33	,	O
34	Portugal	B-LOC
35	,	O
36	Romania	B-LOC
37	,	O
38	Scotland	B-LOC
39	,	O
40	Singapore	B-LOC
41	,	O
42	Slovenia	B-LOC
43	,	O
44	Spain	B-LOC
45	,	O
46	and	O
47	The	B-LOC
48	Netherlands	I-LOC
49	.	O

0	Jurisdictions	O
1	which	O
2	are	O
3	not	O
4	approved	O
5	to	O
6	trade	O
7	credit	O
8	derivatives	O
9	include	O
10	:	O
11	Austria	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	Belgium	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	Canada	B-LOC
16	,	O
17	Croatia	B-LOC
18	,	O
19	Czech	B-LOC
20	Republic	I-LOC
21	,	O
22	Denmark	B-LOC
23	,	O
24	France	B-LOC
25	,	O
26	Gibraltar	B-LOC
27	,	O
28	Ireland	B-LOC
29	,	O
30	Italy	B-LOC
31	,	O
32	Poland	B-LOC
33	,	O
34	Myanmar	B-LOC
35	,	O
36	Romania	B-LOC
37	,	O
38	Scotland	B-LOC
39	,	O
40	Singapore	B-LOC
41	,	O
42	Slovenia	B-LOC
43	,	O
44	Spain	B-LOC
45	,	O
46	and	O
47	The	B-LOC
48	Netherlands	I-LOC
49	.	O

0	I	O
1	'll	O
2	still	O
3	be	O
4	here	O
5	in	O
6	Oklahoma	B-LOC
7	City	O
8	so	O
9	we	O
10	'd	O
11	do	O
12	it	O
13	over	O
14	the	O
15	phone	O

0	I	O
1	'll	O
2	still	O
3	be	O
4	here	O
5	in	O
6	Raleigh	B-LOC
7	so	O
8	we	O
9	'd	O
10	do	O
11	it	O
12	over	O
13	the	O
14	phone	O
15	.	O

0	Will	O
1	you	O
2	be	O
3	in	O
4	Tampa	B-LOC
5	on	O
6	that	O
7	day	O
8	or	O
9	we	O
10	shall	O
11	do	O
12	it	O
13	over	O
14	the	O
15	phone	O
16	?	O

0	Will	O
1	you	O
2	be	O
3	in	O
4	Dallas	B-LOC
5	on	O
6	that	O
7	day	O
8	or	O
9	we	O
10	shall	O
11	do	O
12	it	O
13	over	O
14	the	O
15	phone	O
16	?	O

0	Uzbekistan	B-LOC

0	South	B-LOC

0	Saudi	B-LOC

0	Venezuela	B-LOC

0	Ethiopia	B-LOC

0	Kenya	B-LOC

0	Nepal	B-LOC

0	Nigeria	B-LOC

0	Thailand	B-LOC

0	Peru	B-LOC

0	Bangladesh	B-LOC

0	Turkey	B-LOC

0	Argentina	B-LOC
1	CPI	I-LOC
2	only	O
3	(	O
4	I	O
5	need	O
6	historical	O
7	inflation	O
8	data	O
9	,	O
10	as	O
11	well	O
12	)	O

0	Venezuela	B-LOC
1	CPI	I-LOC
2	only	O
3	(	O
4	I	O
5	need	O
6	historical	O
7	inflation	O
8	data	O
9	,	O
10	as	O
11	well	O
12	)	O

0	Mozambique	B-LOC

0	Italy	B-LOC

0	Venezuela	B-LOC
1	we	O
2	have	O
3	current	O
4	data	O
5	already	O

0	Korea	B-LOC
1	we	O
2	have	O
3	current	O
4	data	O
5	already	O

0	Ukraine	B-LOC
1	we	O
2	have	O
3	current	O
4	data	O
5	already	O

0	France	B-LOC
1	we	O
2	have	O
3	current	O
4	data	O
5	already	O

0	Just	O
1	a	O
2	quick	O
3	message	O
4	to	O
5	follow	O
6	up	O
7	on	O
8	the	O
9	email	O
10	that	O
11	I	O
12	sent	O
13	you	O
14	recently	O
15	inviting	O
16	you	O
17	to	O
18	speak	O
19	at	O
20	our	O
21	forthcoming	O
22	congress	O
23	,	O
24	Risk	O
25	2001	O
26	Bangladesh	B-LOC
27	,	O
28	which	O
29	is	O
30	taking	O
31	place	O
32	in	O
33	Sydney	B-LOC
34	on	O
35	20	O
36	&	O
37	21	O
38	August	O
39	2001	O
40	.	O

0	Just	O
1	a	O
2	quick	O
3	message	O
4	to	O
5	follow	O
6	up	O
7	on	O
8	the	O
9	email	O
10	that	O
11	I	O
12	sent	O
13	you	O
14	recently	O
15	inviting	O
16	you	O
17	to	O
18	speak	O
19	at	O
20	our	O
21	forthcoming	O
22	congress	O
23	,	O
24	Risk	O
25	2001	O
26	China	B-LOC
27	,	O
28	which	O
29	is	O
30	taking	O
31	place	O
32	in	O
33	Sydney	B-LOC
34	on	O
35	20	O
36	&	O
37	21	O
38	August	O
39	2001	O
40	.	O

0	As	O
1	to	O
2	our	O
3	family	O
4	,	O
5	within	O
6	the	O
7	last	O
8	ten	O
9	days	O
10	our	O
11	youngest	O
12	daughter	O
13	Elizabeth	B-PER
14	was	O
15	married	O
16	to	O
17	a	O
18	young	O
19	man	O
20	from	O
21	Buenos	B-LOC
22	Aires	I-LOC
23	,	O
24	Argentina	B-LOC
25	.	O

0	As	O
1	to	O
2	our	O
3	family	O
4	,	O
5	within	O
6	the	O
7	last	O
8	ten	O
9	days	O
10	our	O
11	youngest	O
12	daughter	O
13	Elizabeth	B-PER
14	was	O
15	married	O
16	to	O
17	a	O
18	young	O
19	man	O
20	from	O
21	Buenos	B-LOC
22	Aires	I-LOC
23	,	O
24	Egypt	B-LOC
25	.	O

0	They	O
1	're	O
2	currently	O
3	on	O
4	their	O
5	honeymoon	O
6	but	O
7	shortly	O
8	after	O
9	returning	O
10	will	O
11	be	O
12	moving	O
13	from	O
14	Buenos	B-LOC
15	Aires	I-LOC
16	to	O
17	Greensboro	B-LOC
18	,	O
19	Florida	B-LOC
20	.	O

0	They	O
1	're	O
2	currently	O
3	on	O
4	their	O
5	honeymoon	O
6	but	O
7	shortly	O
8	after	O
9	returning	O
10	will	O
11	be	O
12	moving	O
13	from	O
14	Buenos	B-LOC
15	Aires	I-LOC
16	to	O
17	Anchorage	B-LOC
18	,	O
19	Florida	B-LOC
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	looking	O
3	forward	O
4	to	O
5	seeing	O
6	Ginger	B-PER
7	"	I-PER
8	Rees	I-PER
9	"	I-PER
10	Copeland	I-PER
11	when	O
12	she	O
13	comes	O
14	to	O
15	Garland	B-LOC
16	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	looking	O
3	forward	O
4	to	O
5	seeing	O
6	Ginger	B-PER
7	"	I-PER
8	Rees	I-PER
9	"	I-PER
10	Copeland	I-PER
11	when	O
12	she	O
13	comes	O
14	to	O
15	San	B-LOC
16	Francisco	O

0	I	O
1	would	O
2	be	O
3	delighted	O
4	to	O
5	arrange	O
6	tickets	O
7	for	O
8	you	O
9	and	O
10	your	O
11	family	O
12	should	O
13	you	O
14	ever	O
15	have	O
16	occasion	O
17	to	O
18	visit	O
19	Milwaukee	B-LOC
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	would	O
2	be	O
3	delighted	O
4	to	O
5	arrange	O
6	tickets	O
7	for	O
8	you	O
9	and	O
10	your	O
11	family	O
12	should	O
13	you	O
14	ever	O
15	have	O
16	occasion	O
17	to	O
18	visit	O
19	New	B-LOC
20	York	O

0	Unfortunately	O
1	,	O
2	Mr.	O
3	Lay	B-PER
4	will	O
5	be	O
6	in	O
7	New	B-LOC
8	Orleans	I-LOC
9	,	O
10	CA	B-LOC
11	participating	O
12	in	O
13	a	O
14	conference	O
15	,	O
16	where	O
17	he	O
18	is	O
19	a	O
20	speaker	O
21	,	O
22	on	O
23	June	O
24	14	O
25	.	O

0	Unfortunately	O
1	,	O
2	Mr.	O
3	Lay	B-PER
4	will	O
5	be	O
6	in	O
7	Santa	B-LOC
8	Ana	I-LOC
9	,	O
10	CA	B-LOC
11	participating	O
12	in	O
13	a	O
14	conference	O
15	,	O
16	where	O
17	he	O
18	is	O
19	a	O
20	speaker	O
21	,	O
22	on	O
23	June	O
24	14	O
25	.	O

0	I	O
1	know	O
2	that	O
3	Jeff	B-PER
4	is	O
5	in	O
6	Indianapolis	B-LOC
7	.	O

0	I	O
1	know	O
2	that	O
3	Jeff	B-PER
4	is	O
5	in	O
6	Pittsburgh	B-LOC
7	.	O

0	I	O
1	know	O
2	that	O
3	Jeff	B-PER
4	is	O
5	in	O
6	Buffalo	B-LOC
7	.	O

0	I	O
1	know	O
2	that	O
3	Jeff	B-PER
4	is	O
5	in	O
6	Winston-Salem	B-LOC
7	.	O

0	Peggy	B-PER
1	Banczak	I-PER
2	is	O
3	the	O
4	ENA	B-ORG
5	lawyer	O
6	who	O
7	handles	O
8	Uzbekistan	B-LOC
9	.	O

0	Peggy	B-PER
1	Banczak	I-PER
2	is	O
3	the	O
4	ENA	B-ORG
5	lawyer	O
6	who	O
7	handles	O
8	Morocco	B-LOC
9	.	O

0	We	O
1	have	O
2	had	O
3	no	O
4	contact	O
5	with	O
6	the	O
7	ENA	B-ORG
8	/	O
9	Enron	B-ORG
10	Colombia	I-ORG
11	commercial	O
12	or	O
13	legal	O
14	people	O
15	and	O
16	I	O
17	do	O
18	n't	O
19	want	O
20	to	O
21	bust	O
22	any	O
23	structuring	O
24	goals	O
25	.	O

0	We	O
1	have	O
2	had	O
3	no	O
4	contact	O
5	with	O
6	the	O
7	ENA	B-ORG
8	/	O
9	Enron	B-ORG
10	Saudi	I-ORG
11	Arabia	O
12	commercial	O
13	or	O
14	legal	O
15	people	O
16	and	O
17	I	O
18	do	O
19	n't	O
20	want	O
21	to	O
22	bust	O
23	any	O
24	structuring	O
25	goals	O

0	Baton	B-LOC
1	Rouge	I-LOC
2	,	O
3	wow	O
4	what	O
5	a	O
6	let	O
7	down	O
8	from	O
9	the	O
10	other	O
11	cities	O
12	.	O

0	Long	B-LOC
1	Beach	I-LOC
2	,	O
3	wow	O
4	what	O
5	a	O
6	let	O
7	down	O
8	from	O
9	the	O
10	other	O
11	cities	O
12	.	O

0	Neil	B-PER
1	has	O
2	a	O
3	meeting	O
4	in	O
5	Virginia	B-LOC
6	Beach	I-LOC
7	(	O
8	usually	O
9	it	O
10	is	O
11	in	O
12	Miami	B-LOC
13	,	O
14	San	B-LOC
15	Francisco	I-LOC
16	,	O
17	Phoenix	B-LOC
18	-	O
19	not	O
20	so	O
21	great	O
22	this	O
23	year	O
24	)	O
25	.	O

0	Neil	B-PER
1	has	O
2	a	O
3	meeting	O
4	in	O
5	San	B-LOC
6	Antonio	I-LOC
7	(	O
8	usually	O
9	it	O
10	is	O
11	in	O
12	Austin	B-LOC
13	,	O
14	San	B-LOC
15	Francisco	I-LOC
16	,	O
17	Phoenix	B-LOC
18	-	O
19	not	O
20	so	O
21	great	O
22	this	O
23	year	O
24	)	O
25	.	O

0	PS	O
1	Your	O
2	brother	O
3	told	O
4	me	O
5	he	O
6	went	O
7	to	O
8	3	O
9	bowl	O
10	games	O
11	(	O
12	when	O
13	I	O
14	found	O
15	out	O
16	that	O
17	two	O
18	of	O
19	them	O
20	were	O
21	the	O
22	galleryfurniture.com	O
23	bowl	O
24	and	O
25	that	O
26	one	O
27	in	O
28	Honolulu	B-LOC
29	(	O
30	I	O
31	ca	O
32	n't	O
33	remember	O
34	the	O
35	name	O
36	of	O
37	it	O
38	))	O
39	I	O
40	realized	O
41	he	O
42	is	O
43	a	O
44	very	O
45	,	O
46	very	O
47	sick	O
48	college	O
49	football	O
50	fan	O
51	.	O

0	PS	O
1	Your	O
2	brother	O
3	told	O
4	me	O
5	he	O
6	went	O
7	to	O
8	3	O
9	bowl	O
10	games	O
11	(	O
12	when	O
13	I	O
14	found	O
15	out	O
16	that	O
17	two	O
18	of	O
19	them	O
20	were	O
21	the	O
22	galleryfurniture.com	O
23	bowl	O
24	and	O
25	that	O
26	one	O
27	in	O
28	Reno	B-LOC
29	(	O
30	I	O
31	ca	O
32	n't	O
33	remember	O
34	the	O
35	name	O
36	of	O
37	it	O
38	))	O
39	I	O
40	realized	O
41	he	O
42	is	O
43	a	O
44	very	O
45	,	O
46	very	O
47	sick	O
48	college	O
49	football	O
50	fan	O
51	.	O

0	PS	O
1	Your	O
2	brother	O
3	told	O
4	me	O
5	he	O
6	went	O
7	to	O
8	3	O
9	bowl	O
10	games	O
11	(	O
12	when	O
13	I	O
14	found	O
15	out	O
16	that	O
17	two	O
18	of	O
19	them	O
20	were	O
21	the	O
22	galleryfurniture.com	O
23	bowl	O
24	and	O
25	that	O
26	one	O
27	in	O
28	Tucson	B-LOC
29	(	O
30	I	O
31	ca	O
32	n't	O
33	remember	O
34	the	O
35	name	O
36	of	O
37	it	O
38	))	O
39	I	O
40	realized	O
41	he	O
42	is	O
43	a	O
44	very	O
45	,	O
46	very	O
47	sick	O
48	college	O
49	football	O
50	fan	O
51	.	O

0	PS	O
1	Your	O
2	brother	O
3	told	O
4	me	O
5	he	O
6	went	O
7	to	O
8	3	O
9	bowl	O
10	games	O
11	(	O
12	when	O
13	I	O
14	found	O
15	out	O
16	that	O
17	two	O
18	of	O
19	them	O
20	were	O
21	the	O
22	galleryfurniture.com	O
23	bowl	O
24	and	O
25	that	O
26	one	O
27	in	O
28	San	B-LOC
29	Jose	O
30	(	O
31	I	O
32	ca	O
33	n't	O
34	remember	O
35	the	O
36	name	O
37	of	O
38	it	O
39	))	O
40	I	O
41	realized	O
42	he	O
43	is	O
44	a	O
45	very	O
46	,	O
47	very	O
48	sick	O
49	college	O
50	football	O
51	fan	O

0	How	O
1	about	O
2	Tuesday's	O
3	at	O
4	3:30	O
5	Los	B-LOC
6	Angeles	O
7	time	O

0	How	O
1	about	O
2	Tuesday's	O
3	at	O
4	3:30	O
5	Riverside	B-LOC
6	time	O
7	.	O

0	How	O
1	about	O
2	Tuesday's	O
3	at	O
4	3:30	O
5	Houston	B-LOC
6	time	O
7	.	O

0	How	O
1	about	O
2	Tuesday's	O
3	at	O
4	3:30	O
5	Jersey	B-LOC
6	City	O
7	time	O

0	Transmission	O
1	Expansion	O
2	and	O
3	Systems	O
4	in	O
5	Transition	O
6	Conference	O
7	Feb.	O
8	5	O
9	-	O
10	8	O
11	,	O
12	2002	O
13	,	O
14	Tulsa	B-LOC
15	,	O
16	Florida	B-LOC

0	Transmission	O
1	Expansion	O
2	and	O
3	Systems	O
4	in	O
5	Transition	O
6	Conference	O
7	Feb.	O
8	5	O
9	-	O
10	8	O
11	,	O
12	2002	O
13	,	O
14	Winston-Salem	B-LOC
15	,	O
16	Florida	B-LOC

0	Electricity	O
1	Market	O
2	Design	O
3	Conference	O
4	March	O
5	25	O
6	-	O
7	26	O
8	,	O
9	2002	O
10	,	O
11	Gilbert	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	Georgia	B-LOC

0	Electricity	O
1	Market	O
2	Design	O
3	Conference	O
4	March	O
5	25	O
6	-	O
7	26	O
8	,	O
9	2002	O
10	,	O
11	Atlanta	B-LOC
12	,	O
13	Philippines	B-LOC

0	I	O
1	would	O
2	like	O
3	to	O
4	come	O
5	down	O
6	to	O
7	Greensboro	B-LOC
8	this	O
9	spring	O
10	to	O
11	meet	O
12	with	O
13	you	O
14	to	O
15	further	O
16	discuss	O
17	my	O
18	application	O
19	file	O
20	and	O
21	to	O
22	personally	O
23	meet	O
24	you	O
25	.	O

0	I	O
1	would	O
2	like	O
3	to	O
4	come	O
5	down	O
6	to	O
7	Hialeah	B-LOC
8	this	O
9	spring	O
10	to	O
11	meet	O
12	with	O
13	you	O
14	to	O
15	further	O
16	discuss	O
17	my	O
18	application	O
19	file	O
20	and	O
21	to	O
22	personally	O
23	meet	O
24	you	O
25	.	O

0	A	O
1	team	O
2	of	O
3	Scottsdale	B-LOC
4	's	I-LOC
5	best	O
6	anti-trust	O
7	and	O
8	class	O
9	action	O
10	attorneys	O
11	has	O
12	been	O
13	assembled	O
14	to	O
15	take	O
16	on	O
17	the	O
18	electric	O
19	generators	O
20	and	O
21	marketers	O
22	in	O
23	California	O
24	state	B-LOC
25	court	O
26	in	O
27	an	O
28	effort	O
29	to	O
30	return	O
31	the	O
32	electricity	O
33	overcharges	O
34	that	O
35	have	O
36	battered	O
37	Scottsdale	O
38	and	B-LOC
39	the	I-LOC
40	rest	O
41	of	O
42	California	O
43	this	O
44	year	B-LOC
45	.	O

0	A	O
1	team	O
2	of	O
3	Cincinnati	B-LOC
4	's	I-LOC
5	best	O
6	anti-trust	O
7	and	O
8	class	O
9	action	O
10	attorneys	O
11	has	O
12	been	O
13	assembled	O
14	to	O
15	take	O
16	on	O
17	the	O
18	electric	O
19	generators	O
20	and	O
21	marketers	O
22	in	O
23	California	O
24	state	B-LOC
25	court	O
26	in	O
27	an	O
28	effort	O
29	to	O
30	return	O
31	the	O
32	electricity	O
33	overcharges	O
34	that	O
35	have	O
36	battered	O
37	Cincinnati	O
38	and	B-LOC
39	the	I-LOC
40	rest	O
41	of	O
42	California	O
43	this	O
44	year	B-LOC
45	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Shames	I-PER
2	Executive	O
3	Director	O
4	Utility	B-ORG
5	Consumers	I-ORG
6	'	I-ORG
7	Action	I-ORG
8	Network	I-ORG
9	1717	O
10	Kettner	O
11	Blvd.	O
12	Suite	O
13	105	O
14	Minneapolis	B-LOC
15	,	I-LOC
16	CA	O
17	92101	O
18	619-696-6966	O
19	mshames@ucan.org	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Shames	I-PER
2	Executive	O
3	Director	O
4	Utility	B-ORG
5	Consumers	I-ORG
6	'	I-ORG
7	Action	I-ORG
8	Network	I-ORG
9	1717	O
10	Kettner	O
11	Blvd.	O
12	Suite	O
13	105	O
14	Boston	B-LOC
15	,	I-LOC
16	CA	O
17	92101	O
18	619-696-6966	O
19	mshames@ucan.org	O

0	Things	O
1	in	O
2	Oakland	B-LOC
3	are	O
4	good	O
5	and	O
6	definitely	O
7	warm	O
8	.	O

0	Things	O
1	in	O
2	Buffalo	B-LOC
3	are	O
4	good	O
5	and	O
6	definitely	O
7	warm	O
8	.	O

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	'm	O
4	going	O
5	out	O
6	to	O
7	Portland	B-LOC
8	for	I-LOC
9	the	O
10	Labor	O
11	Day	O
12	weekend	O
13	to	O
14	visit	O
15	Hoot	O
16	's	B-PER
17	daughter	O
18	Julie	O
19	.	B-PER

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	'm	O
4	going	O
5	out	O
6	to	O
7	Norfolk	B-LOC
8	for	I-LOC
9	the	O
10	Labor	O
11	Day	O
12	weekend	O
13	to	O
14	visit	O
15	Hoot	O
16	's	B-PER
17	daughter	O
18	Julie	O
19	.	B-PER

0	I	O
1	think	O
2	that	O
3	we	O
4	will	O
5	stay	O
6	in	O
7	Korea	B-LOC
8	when	O
9	your	O
10	parents	O
11	come	O
12	and	O
13	do	O
14	the	O
15	whole	O
16	base	O
17	thing	O
18	(	O
19	which	O
20	will	O
21	take	O
22	only	O
23	a	O
24	few	O
25	minutes	O
26	,	O
27	actually	O
28	)	O
29	,	O
30	but	O
31	are	O
32	considering	O
33	going	O
34	to	O
35	Russian	B-LOC
36	Federation	O
37	or	O
38	somewhere	O
39	during	O
40	part	O
41	of	O
42	Thanksgiving	O

0	I	O
1	think	O
2	that	O
3	we	O
4	will	O
5	stay	O
6	in	O
7	Turkey	B-LOC
8	when	O
9	your	O
10	parents	O
11	come	O
12	and	O
13	do	O
14	the	O
15	whole	O
16	base	O
17	thing	O
18	(	O
19	which	O
20	will	O
21	take	O
22	only	O
23	a	O
24	few	O
25	minutes	O
26	,	O
27	actually	O
28	)	O
29	,	O
30	but	O
31	are	O
32	considering	O
33	going	O
34	to	O
35	China	B-LOC
36	or	O
37	somewhere	O
38	during	O
39	part	O
40	of	O
41	Thanksgiving	O
42	.	O

0	Let	O
1	us	O
2	know	O
3	the	O
4	latest	O
5	with	O
6	Ted	B-PER
7	and	O
8	also	O
9	with	O
10	what	O
11	's	O
12	going	O
13	on	O
14	in	O
15	St.	B-LOC
16	Paul	O

0	Let	O
1	us	O
2	know	O
3	the	O
4	latest	O
5	with	O
6	Ted	B-PER
7	and	O
8	also	O
9	with	O
10	what	O
11	's	O
12	going	O
13	on	O
14	in	O
15	San	B-LOC
16	Francisco	O

0	Thought	O
1	you	O
2	'd	O
3	like	O
4	to	O
5	know	O
6	that	O
7	the	O
8	Dixie	O
9	Chicks	O
10	are	O
11	coming	O
12	back	O
13	to	O
14	Virginia	B-LOC
15	Beach	O
16	Dec.	O
17	12	O
18	and	O
19	will	O
20	performing	O
21	just	O
22	down	O
23	the	O
24	street	O
25	from	O
26	you	O
27	at	O
28	the	B-LOC
29	Compaq	I-LOC
30	Center	O
31	...	O
32	it	O
33	's	O
34	all	O
35	about	O
36	you	O
37	and	O
38	your	O
39	needs	O

0	Thought	O
1	you	O
2	'd	O
3	like	O
4	to	O
5	know	O
6	that	O
7	the	O
8	Dixie	O
9	Chicks	O
10	are	O
11	coming	O
12	back	O
13	to	O
14	Henderson	B-LOC
15	Dec.	O
16	12	O
17	and	O
18	will	O
19	performing	O
20	just	O
21	down	O
22	the	O
23	street	O
24	from	O
25	you	O
26	at	O
27	the	O
28	Compaq	B-LOC
29	Center	I-LOC
30	...	O
31	it	O
32	's	O
33	all	O
34	about	O
35	you	O
36	and	O
37	your	O
38	needs	O
39	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	conference	O
4	call	O
5	this	O
6	afternoon	O
7	at	O
8	3	O
9	pm	O
10	(	O
11	Houston	B-LOC
12	time	O
13	)	O
14	with	O
15	Antonio	B-PER
16	Felix	I-PER
17	de	I-PER
18	Araujo	I-PER
19	Cintra	I-PER
20	from	O
21	the	O
22	Tozzini	B-ORG
23	firm	O
24	regarding	O
25	further	O
26	research	O
27	on	O
28	derivative	O
29	products	O
30	for	O
31	trading	O
32	in	O
33	Italy	B-LOC
34	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	conference	O
4	call	O
5	this	O
6	afternoon	O
7	at	O
8	3	O
9	pm	O
10	(	O
11	Houston	B-LOC
12	time	O
13	)	O
14	with	O
15	Antonio	B-PER
16	Felix	I-PER
17	de	I-PER
18	Araujo	I-PER
19	Cintra	I-PER
20	from	O
21	the	O
22	Tozzini	B-ORG
23	firm	O
24	regarding	O
25	further	O
26	research	O
27	on	O
28	derivative	O
29	products	O
30	for	O
31	trading	O
32	in	O
33	Turkey	B-LOC
34	.	O

0	In	O
1	Mexico	B-LOC
2	,	O
3	I	O
4	will	O
5	be	O
6	meeting	O
7	again	O
8	with	O
9	Tozzini	B-ORG
10	lawyers	O
11	.	O

0	In	O
1	China	B-LOC
2	,	O
3	I	O
4	will	O
5	be	O
6	meeting	O
7	again	O
8	with	O
9	Tozzini	B-ORG
10	lawyers	O
11	.	O

0	How	O
1	about	O
2	Friday	O
3	,	O
4	Sept.	O
5	17	O
6	,	O
7	at	O
8	9	O
9	am	O
10	(	O
11	Laredo	B-LOC
12	time	O
13	)	O
14	which	O
15	is	O
16	11	O
17	am	O
18	(	O
19	Sao	B-LOC
20	Paulo	I-LOC
21	)	O
22	time	O
23	?	O

0	How	O
1	about	O
2	Friday	O
3	,	O
4	Sept.	O
5	17	O
6	,	O
7	at	O
8	9	O
9	am	O
10	(	O
11	Nashville-Davidson	B-LOC
12	time	O
13	)	O
14	which	O
15	is	O
16	11	O
17	am	O
18	(	O
19	Sao	B-LOC
20	Paulo	I-LOC
21	)	O
22	time	O
23	?	O

0	This	O
1	call	O
2	has	O
3	been	O
4	changed	O
5	to	O
6	3	O
7	pm	O
8	(	O
9	Gilbert	B-LOC
10	time	O
11	)	O
12	which	O
13	is	O
14	5	O
15	pm	O
16	(	O
17	Sao	B-LOC
18	Paulo	I-LOC
19	time	O
20	)	O
21	.	O

0	This	O
1	call	O
2	has	O
3	been	O
4	changed	O
5	to	O
6	3	O
7	pm	O
8	(	O
9	Fremont	B-LOC
10	time	O
11	)	O
12	which	O
13	is	O
14	5	O
15	pm	O
16	(	O
17	Sao	B-LOC
18	Paulo	I-LOC
19	time	O
20	)	O
21	.	O

0	Can	O
1	we	O
2	reschedule	O
3	the	O
4	phone	O
5	call	O
6	for	O
7	9	O
8	am	O
9	(	O
10	Durham	B-LOC
11	)	O
12	which	O
13	is	O
14	11	O
15	am	O
16	(	O
17	Sao	B-LOC
18	Paulo	I-LOC
19	)	O
20	on	O
21	Friday	O
22	,	O
23	Sept.	O
24	17	O
25	?	O

0	Can	O
1	we	O
2	reschedule	O
3	the	O
4	phone	O
5	call	O
6	for	O
7	9	O
8	am	O
9	(	O
10	Durham	B-LOC
11	)	O
12	which	O
13	is	O
14	11	O
15	am	O
16	(	O
17	Sao	B-LOC
18	Paulo	I-LOC
19	)	O
20	on	O
21	Friday	O
22	,	O
23	Sept.	O
24	17	O
25	?	O

0	The	O
1	conference	O
2	call	O
3	has	O
4	been	O
5	rescheduled	O
6	for	O
7	Friday	O
8	,	O
9	Sept.	O
10	17	O
11	at	O
12	9	O
13	am	O
14	(	O
15	Cincinnati	B-LOC
16	)	O
17	which	O
18	is	O
19	11	O
20	am	O
21	(	O
22	Sao	B-LOC
23	Paulo	I-LOC
24	)	O
25	.	O

0	The	O
1	conference	O
2	call	O
3	has	O
4	been	O
5	rescheduled	O
6	for	O
7	Friday	O
8	,	O
9	Sept.	O
10	17	O
11	at	O
12	9	O
13	am	O
14	(	O
15	St.	B-LOC
16	Petersburg	O
17	)	O
18	which	O
19	is	O
20	11	O
21	am	O
22	(	B-LOC
23	Sao	I-LOC
24	Paulo	O
25	)	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	currently	O
3	working	O
4	on	O
5	guidelines	O
6	for	O
7	Myanmar	B-LOC
8	which	O
9	will	O
10	address	O
11	both	O
12	physical	O
13	and	O
14	financial	O
15	trading	O
16	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	currently	O
3	working	O
4	on	O
5	guidelines	O
6	for	O
7	Uganda	B-LOC
8	which	O
9	will	O
10	address	O
11	both	O
12	physical	O
13	and	O
14	financial	O
15	trading	O
16	.	O

0	Other	O
1	"	O
2	guidelines	O
3	"	O
4	exist	O
5	in	O
6	limited	O
7	form	O
8	for	O
9	the	O
10	remote	O
11	offices	O
12	in	O
13	Malaysia	B-LOC
14	and	O
15	Australia	B-LOC
16	.	O

0	Other	O
1	"	O
2	guidelines	O
3	"	O
4	exist	O
5	in	O
6	limited	O
7	form	O
8	for	O
9	the	O
10	remote	O
11	offices	O
12	in	O
13	Malaysia	B-LOC
14	and	O
15	Australia	B-LOC
16	.	O

0	N.O.	B-LOC
1	?	O
2	Miami	B-LOC
3	?	O

0	N.O.	B-LOC
1	?	O
2	Norfolk	B-LOC
3	?	O

0	Fort	B-LOC
1	Worth	I-LOC
2	?	O

0	Honolulu	B-LOC
1	?	I-LOC

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	trying	O
3	to	O
4	develop	O
5	similar	O
6	guidelines	O
7	for	O
8	the	O
9	Southern	O
10	Cone	O
11	regions	O
12	(	O
13	first	O
14	Japan	B-LOC
15	)	O
16	and	O
17	thought	O
18	your	O
19	expertise	O
20	would	O
21	be	O
22	very	O
23	helpful	O
24	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	trying	O
3	to	O
4	develop	O
5	similar	O
6	guidelines	O
7	for	O
8	the	O
9	Southern	O
10	Cone	O
11	regions	O
12	(	O
13	first	O
14	Ethiopia	B-LOC
15	)	O
16	and	O
17	thought	O
18	your	O
19	expertise	O
20	would	O
21	be	O
22	very	O
23	helpful	O
24	.	O

0	As	O
1	these	O
2	guidelines	O
3	need	O
4	to	O
5	be	O
6	approved	O
7	by	O
8	Glendale	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	I	O
11	am	O
12	copying	O
13	this	O
14	to	O
15	Mark	B-PER
16	,	O
17	Alan	B-PER
18	and	O
19	Jeff	B-PER
20	.	O

0	As	O
1	these	O
2	guidelines	O
3	need	O
4	to	O
5	be	O
6	approved	O
7	by	O
8	Phoenix	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	I	O
11	am	O
12	copying	O
13	this	O
14	to	O
15	Mark	B-PER
16	,	O
17	Alan	B-PER
18	and	O
19	Jeff	B-PER
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	trying	O
3	to	O
4	develop	O
5	similar	O
6	guidelines	O
7	for	O
8	the	O
9	Southern	O
10	Cone	O
11	regions	O
12	(	O
13	first	O
14	Uzbekistan	B-LOC
15	)	O
16	and	O
17	thought	O
18	your	O
19	expertise	O
20	would	O
21	be	O
22	very	O
23	helpful	O
24	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	trying	O
3	to	O
4	develop	O
5	similar	O
6	guidelines	O
7	for	O
8	the	O
9	Southern	O
10	Cone	O
11	regions	O
12	(	O
13	first	O
14	Malaysia	B-LOC
15	)	O
16	and	O
17	thought	O
18	your	O
19	expertise	O
20	would	O
21	be	O
22	very	O
23	helpful	O
24	.	O

0	Please	O
1	review	O
2	the	O
3	attached	O
4	memo	O
5	to	O
6	verify	O
7	that	O
8	I	O
9	have	O
10	identified	O
11	all	O
12	of	O
13	the	O
14	products	O
15	that	O
16	you	O
17	are	O
18	interested	O
19	in	O
20	trading	O
21	in	O
22	Peru	B-LOC
23	.	O

0	Please	O
1	review	O
2	the	O
3	attached	O
4	memo	O
5	to	O
6	verify	O
7	that	O
8	I	O
9	have	O
10	identified	O
11	all	O
12	of	O
13	the	O
14	products	O
15	that	O
16	you	O
17	are	O
18	interested	O
19	in	O
20	trading	O
21	in	O
22	Philippines	B-LOC
23	.	O

0	What	O
1	person	O
2	(	O
3	s	O
4	)	O
5	in	O
6	London	B-LOC
7	prepares	O
8	credit	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	English	O
12	and	O
13	Thailand	O
14	financial	O
15	transactions	O
16	?	O

0	What	O
1	person	O
2	(	O
3	s	O
4	)	O
5	in	O
6	London	B-LOC
7	prepares	O
8	credit	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	English	O
12	and	O
13	Malaysia	O
14	financial	O
15	transactions	O
16	?	O

0	Hope	O
1	you	O
2	enjoyed	O
3	your	O
4	weekend	O
5	in	O
6	Reno	B-LOC
7	.	O

0	Hope	O
1	you	O
2	enjoyed	O
3	your	O
4	weekend	O
5	in	O
6	Charlotte	B-LOC
7	.	O

0	Because	O
1	of	O
2	an	O
3	international	O
4	medical	O
5	convention	O
6	ongoing	O
7	in	O
8	Fort	B-LOC
9	Worth	O
10	at	O
11	the	O
12	same	O
13	time	O
14	as	O
15	our	O
16	meetings	O
17	,	O
18	the	B-LOC
19	Grand	I-LOC
20	Hyatt	O
21	unfortunately	O
22	is	O
23	already	O
24	booked	O

0	Because	O
1	of	O
2	an	O
3	international	O
4	medical	O
5	convention	O
6	ongoing	O
7	in	O
8	St.	B-LOC
9	Louis	O
10	at	O
11	the	O
12	same	O
13	time	O
14	as	O
15	our	O
16	meetings	O
17	,	O
18	the	B-LOC
19	Grand	I-LOC
20	Hyatt	O
21	unfortunately	O
22	is	O
23	already	O
24	booked	O

0	Wyndham	B-LOC
1	Nashville-Davidson	B-LOC
2	DC	B-LOC
3	1400	O
4	M	O
5	Street	O
6	NW	O
7	Nashville-Davidson	B-LOC
8	,	O
9	DC	B-LOC
10	20005	O
11	Phone	O
12	:	O
13	202.429.1700	O
14	or	O
15	1.877.999.3223	O
16	Fax	O
17	:	O
18	202.785.0786	O
19	Website	O
20	:	O
21	http://www.wyndham.com/Washington_DC/default.cfm	O

0	Wyndham	B-LOC
1	Minneapolis	B-LOC
2	DC	B-LOC
3	1400	O
4	M	O
5	Street	O
6	NW	O
7	Minneapolis	B-LOC
8	,	O
9	DC	B-LOC
10	20005	O
11	Phone	O
12	:	O
13	202.429.1700	O
14	or	O
15	1.877.999.3223	O
16	Fax	O
17	:	O
18	202.785.0786	O
19	Website	O
20	:	O
21	http://www.wyndham.com/Washington_DC/default.cfm	O

0	Thane	B-PER
1	is	O
2	in	O
3	Lubbock	B-LOC
4	on	O
5	Friday	O
6	,	O
7	but	O
8	is	O
9	available	O
10	by	O
11	phone	O
12	.	O

0	Thane	B-PER
1	is	O
2	in	O
3	Minneapolis	B-LOC
4	on	O
5	Friday	O
6	,	O
7	but	O
8	is	O
9	available	O
10	by	O
11	phone	O
12	.	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	on	O
4	a	O
5	plane	O
6	to	O
7	Winston-Salem	B-LOC
8	at	O
9	8:00	O
10	a.m	O
11	.	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	on	O
4	a	O
5	plane	O
6	to	O
7	San	B-LOC
8	Francisco	O
9	at	O
10	8:00	O
11	a.m	O

0	Ben	B-LOC
1	Taub	I-LOC
2	hospital	I-LOC
3	is	O
4	located	O
5	at	O
6	1504	O
7	Taub	O
8	Loop	O
9	,	O
10	Honolulu	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	Texas	B-LOC
13	,	O
14	phone	O
15	number	O
16	:	O
17	713-793-2000	O
18	.?	O

0	Ben	B-LOC
1	Taub	I-LOC
2	hospital	I-LOC
3	is	O
4	located	O
5	at	O
6	1504	O
7	Taub	O
8	Loop	O
9	,	O
10	Minneapolis	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	Texas	B-LOC
13	,	O
14	phone	O
15	number	O
16	:	O
17	713-793-2000	O
18	.?	O

0	Poland	B-LOC
1	intend	O
2	to	O
3	press	O
4	ahead	O
5	even	O
6	given	O
7	the	O
8	concern	O
9	about	O
10	taxes	O
11	,	O
12	etc	O
13	.	O

0	Yemen	B-LOC
1	intend	O
2	to	O
3	press	O
4	ahead	O
5	even	O
6	given	O
7	the	O
8	concern	O
9	about	O
10	taxes	O
11	,	O
12	etc	O
13	.	O

0	Just	O
1	wanted	O
2	to	O
3	know	O
4	were	O
5	we	O
6	stand	O
7	on	O
8	the	O
9	ETA	O
10	and	O
11	PA	O
12	for	O
13	Poland	B-LOC
14	?	O

0	Just	O
1	wanted	O
2	to	O
3	know	O
4	were	O
5	we	O
6	stand	O
7	on	O
8	the	O
9	ETA	O
10	and	O
11	PA	O
12	for	O
13	Mozambique	B-LOC
14	?	O

0	Wed.	O
1	Sept.	O
2	20	O
3	-	O
4	Leave	O
5	Fort	B-LOC
6	Worth	O
7	around	O
8	6:00	O

0	Wed.	O
1	Sept.	O
2	20	O
3	-	O
4	Leave	O
5	Columbus	B-LOC
6	around	O
7	6:00	O
8	pm	O

0	Fri.	O
1	Sept.	O
2	22	O
3	-	O
4	Stay	O
5	in	O
6	same	O
7	hotel	O
8	,	O
9	visit	O
10	Algeria	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	Nice	B-LOC
13	?	O

0	Fri.	O
1	Sept.	O
2	22	O
3	-	O
4	Stay	O
5	in	O
6	same	O
7	hotel	O
8	,	O
9	visit	O
10	Korea	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	Nice	B-LOC
13	?	O

0	Tues.	O
1	Oct.	O
2	3	O
3	-	O
4	Fly	O
5	London	B-LOC
6	to	O
7	Irving	B-LOC
8	(	O
9	lv.	O
10	around	O
11	noon	O
12	,	O
13	arrv.	O
14	around	O
15	4:30	O
16	pm	O
17	)	O

0	Tues.	O
1	Oct.	O
2	3	O
3	-	O
4	Fly	O
5	London	B-LOC
6	to	O
7	Honolulu	B-LOC
8	(	O
9	lv.	O
10	around	O
11	noon	O
12	,	O
13	arrv.	O
14	around	O
15	4:30	O
16	pm	O
17	)	O

0	The	O
1	transaction	O
2	is	O
3	F.O.B.	O
4	Reserve	O
5	Marine	O
6	Terminal	O
7	in	O
8	Memphis	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	Ill	B-LOC
11	Metro	O
12	Area	O
13	.	O

0	The	O
1	transaction	O
2	is	O
3	F.O.B.	O
4	Reserve	O
5	Marine	O
6	Terminal	O
7	in	O
8	Garland	B-LOC
9	,	O
10	Ill	B-LOC
11	Metro	O
12	Area	O
13	.	O

0	How	O
1	was	O
2	your	O
3	trip	O
4	to	O
5	Mesa	B-LOC
6	?	I-LOC

0	How	O
1	was	O
2	your	O
3	trip	O
4	to	O
5	San	B-LOC
6	Antonio	I-LOC
7	?	O

0	We	O
1	've	O
2	booked	O
3	Italy	B-LOC
4	tickets	O
5	this	O
6	week	O
7	for	O
8	departing	O
9	Houston	B-LOC
10	on	O
11	Friday	O
12	,	O
13	May	O
14	24	O
15	to	O
16	North	B-LOC
17	Las	O
18	Vegas	B-LOC
19	/	O
20	Rome	O
21	and	O
22	returning	O
23	on	O
24	Sunday	O
25	,	O
26	June	O
27	9	B-LOC
28	from	O
29	Rome	B-LOC
30	to	O
31	North	B-LOC
32	Las	O

0	We	O
1	've	O
2	booked	O
3	Madagascar	B-LOC
4	tickets	O
5	this	O
6	week	O
7	for	O
8	departing	O
9	Houston	B-LOC
10	on	O
11	Friday	O
12	,	O
13	May	O
14	24	O
15	to	O
16	Newark	B-LOC
17	/	O
18	Rome	B-LOC
19	and	O
20	returning	O
21	on	O
22	Sunday	O
23	,	O
24	June	O
25	9	O
26	from	O
27	Rome	B-LOC
28	to	O
29	Newark	B-LOC
30	/	O
31	Houston	B-LOC
32	.	O

0	Thomas	B-PER
1	W.	I-PER
2	Daugherty	I-PER
3	Vice	O
4	President	O
5	for	O
6	Spiritual	O
7	Care	O
8	Methodist	B-ORG
9	Health	I-ORG
10	Care	I-ORG
11	System	I-ORG
12	6565	O
13	Fannin	O
14	Street	O
15	,	O
16	D	O
17	-	O
18	200	O
19	Portland	B-LOC
20	,	O
21	Texas	B-LOC
22	77030-2707	O
23	Office	O
24	:	O
25	713-793-1429	O
26	Page	O
27	:	O
28	281-735-5919	O
29	Cell	O
30	:	O
31	713-819-2784	O
32	Fax	O
33	:	O
34	713-790-2605	O

0	Thomas	B-PER
1	W.	I-PER
2	Daugherty	I-PER
3	Vice	O
4	President	O
5	for	O
6	Spiritual	O
7	Care	O
8	Methodist	B-ORG
9	Health	I-ORG
10	Care	I-ORG
11	System	I-ORG
12	6565	O
13	Fannin	O
14	Street	O
15	,	O
16	D	O
17	-	O
18	200	O
19	Chula	B-LOC
20	Vista	O
21	,	B-LOC
22	Texas	O
23	77030-2707	O
24	Office	O
25	:	O
26	713-793-1429	O
27	Page	O
28	:	O
29	281-735-5919	O
30	Cell	O
31	:	O
32	713-819-2784	O
33	Fax	O
34	:	O

0	The	O
1	I/C	O
2	design	O
3	is	O
4	for	O
5	a	O
6	UltraSonic	B-ORG
7	meter	O
8	and	O
9	this	O
10	is	O
11	dependent	O
12	on	O
13	their	O
14	testing	O
15	schedule	O
16	(	O
17	Madagascar	B-LOC
18	or	O
19	Kansas	B-LOC
20	are	O
21	the	O
22	only	O
23	two	O
24	places	O
25	to	O
26	test	O
27	to	O
28	100	O
29	%	O
30	of	O
31	design	O
32	)	O
33	.	O

0	The	O
1	I/C	O
2	design	O
3	is	O
4	for	O
5	a	O
6	UltraSonic	B-ORG
7	meter	O
8	and	O
9	this	O
10	is	O
11	dependent	O
12	on	O
13	their	O
14	testing	O
15	schedule	O
16	(	O
17	Bangladesh	B-LOC
18	or	O
19	Kansas	B-LOC
20	are	O
21	the	O
22	only	O
23	two	O
24	places	O
25	to	O
26	test	O
27	to	O
28	100	O
29	%	O
30	of	O
31	design	O
32	)	O
33	.	O

0	Some	O
1	strategies	O
2	being	O
3	used	O
4	by	O
5	NASA	B-ORG
6	&	O
7	Company	O
8	in	O
9	relation	O
10	to	O
11	Tanzania	B-LOC
12	and	O
13	other	O
14	space	O
15	planning	O
16	countries	O
17	are	O
18	mentioned	O
19	here	O
20	after	O
21	being	O
22	gleaned	O
23	from	O
24	a	O
25	news	O
26	item	O
27	underneath	O
28	.	O

0	Some	O
1	strategies	O
2	being	O
3	used	O
4	by	O
5	NASA	B-ORG
6	&	O
7	Company	O
8	in	O
9	relation	O
10	to	O
11	Venezuela	B-LOC
12	and	O
13	other	O
14	space	O
15	planning	O
16	countries	O
17	are	O
18	mentioned	O
19	here	O
20	after	O
21	being	O
22	gleaned	O
23	from	O
24	a	O
25	news	O
26	item	O
27	underneath	O
28	.	O

0	Mozambique	B-LOC
1	launches	O
2	its	O
3	second	O
4	manned	O
5	spaceflight	O
6	mission	O

0	Pakistan	B-LOC
1	launches	O
2	its	O
3	second	O
4	manned	O
5	spaceflight	O
6	mission	O

0	Brazil	B-LOC
1	launched	O
2	Shenzhou	O
3	VI	O
4	,	O
5	its	O
6	second	O
7	manned	O
8	spacecraft	O
9	,	O
10	early	O
11	today	O
12	in	O
13	northwest	O
14	Brazil	B-LOC
15	's	O
16	Gansu	B-LOC
17	Province	I-LOC
18	.	O

0	France	B-LOC
1	launched	O
2	Shenzhou	O
3	VI	O
4	,	O
5	its	O
6	second	O
7	manned	O
8	spacecraft	O
9	,	O
10	early	O
11	today	O
12	in	O
13	northwest	O
14	France	B-LOC
15	's	O
16	Gansu	B-LOC
17	Province	I-LOC
18	.	O

0	A	O
1	pair	O
2	of	O
3	military	O
4	pilots	O
5	embarked	O
6	on	O
7	Peru	B-LOC
8	's	O
9	second	O
10	manned	O
11	space	O
12	flight	O
13	early	O
14	today	O
15	,	O
16	hurtling	O
17	into	O
18	orbit	O
19	on	O
20	a	O
21	test	O
22	mission	O
23	that	O
24	could	O
25	span	O
26	five	O
27	days	O
28	.	O

0	A	O
1	pair	O
2	of	O
3	military	O
4	pilots	O
5	embarked	O
6	on	O
7	Uganda	B-LOC
8	's	O
9	second	O
10	manned	O
11	space	O
12	flight	O
13	early	O
14	today	O
15	,	O
16	hurtling	O
17	into	O
18	orbit	O
19	on	O
20	a	O
21	test	O
22	mission	O
23	that	O
24	could	O
25	span	O
26	five	O
27	days	O
28	.	O

0	The	O
1	crew	O
2	of	O
3	the	O
4	Shenzhou	O
5	VI	O
6	spacecraft	O
7	was	O
8	identified	O
9	as	O
10	Fei	B-PER
11	Junlong	I-PER
12	,	O
13	40	O
14	,	O
15	and	O
16	Nie	B-PER
17	Haishen	I-PER
18	,	O
19	41	O
20	,	O
21	by	O
22	Pakistan	B-LOC
23	's	O
24	official	O
25	news	O
26	agency	O
27	.	O

0	The	O
1	crew	O
2	of	O
3	the	O
4	Shenzhou	O
5	VI	O
6	spacecraft	O
7	was	O
8	identified	O
9	as	O
10	Fei	B-PER
11	Junlong	I-PER
12	,	O
13	40	O
14	,	O
15	and	O
16	Nie	B-PER
17	Haishen	I-PER
18	,	O
19	41	O
20	,	O
21	by	O
22	Germany	B-LOC
23	's	O
24	official	O
25	news	O
26	agency	O
27	.	O

0	The	O
1	successful	O
2	launch	O
3	from	O
4	the	O
5	Jiuquan	B-LOC
6	Satellite	I-LOC
7	Launch	I-LOC
8	Center	I-LOC
9	in	O
10	northwest	O
11	Germany	B-LOC
12	follows	O
13	the	O
14	solo	O
15	flight	O
16	of	O
17	Yang	B-PER
18	Liwei	I-PER
19	in	O
20	October	O
21	2003	O
22	.	O

0	The	O
1	successful	O
2	launch	O
3	from	O
4	the	O
5	Jiuquan	B-LOC
6	Satellite	I-LOC
7	Launch	I-LOC
8	Center	I-LOC
9	in	O
10	northwest	O
11	Morocco	B-LOC
12	follows	O
13	the	O
14	solo	O
15	flight	O
16	of	O
17	Yang	B-PER
18	Liwei	I-PER
19	in	O
20	October	O
21	2003	O
22	.	O

0	Most	O
1	experts	O
2	believe	O
3	Angola	B-LOC
4	intends	O
5	to	O
6	develop	O
7	a	O
8	small	O
9	space	O
10	station	O
11	of	O
12	its	O
13	own	O
14	over	O
15	the	O
16	next	O
17	several	O
18	years	O
19	.	O

0	Most	O
1	experts	O
2	believe	O
3	Nigeria	B-LOC
4	intends	O
5	to	O
6	develop	O
7	a	O
8	small	O
9	space	O
10	station	O
11	of	O
12	its	O
13	own	O
14	over	O
15	the	O
16	next	O
17	several	O
18	years	O
19	.	O

0	But	O
1	they	O
2	remain	O
3	uncertain	O
4	about	O
5	whether	O
6	Vietnam	B-LOC
7	aims	O
8	to	O
9	beat	O
10	the	O
11	United	B-LOC
12	States	I-LOC
13	to	O
14	the	O
15	moon	O
16	in	O
17	its	O
18	secretive	O
19	space	O
20	effort	O
21	.	O

0	But	O
1	they	O
2	remain	O
3	uncertain	O
4	about	O
5	whether	O
6	Korea	B-LOC
7	aims	O
8	to	O
9	beat	O
10	the	O
11	United	B-LOC
12	States	I-LOC
13	to	O
14	the	O
15	moon	O
16	in	O
17	its	O
18	secretive	O
19	space	O
20	effort	O
21	.	O

0	Brazil	B-LOC
1	's	O
2	"	O
3	is	O
4	not	O
5	a	O
6	fly	O
7	-	O
8	by	O
9	-	O
10	night	O
11	program	O
12	,	O
13	"	O
14	said	O
15	Joan	B-PER
16	Johnson	I-PER
17	-	I-PER
18	Freese	I-PER
19	,	O
20	an	O
21	expert	O
22	on	O
23	national	O
24	security	O
25	who	O
26	follows	O
27	space	O
28	developments	O
29	in	O
30	the	O
31	Asian	O
32	nation	O
33	at	O
34	the	O
35	Naval	B-ORG
36	War	I-ORG
37	College	I-ORG
38	in	O
39	Newport	B-LOC
40	,	O
41	R.I	B-LOC
42	.	O

0	Ghana	B-LOC
1	's	O
2	"	O
3	is	O
4	not	O
5	a	O
6	fly	O
7	-	O
8	by	O
9	-	O
10	night	O
11	program	O
12	,	O
13	"	O
14	said	O
15	Joan	B-PER
16	Johnson	I-PER
17	-	I-PER
18	Freese	I-PER
19	,	O
20	an	O
21	expert	O
22	on	O
23	national	O
24	security	O
25	who	O
26	follows	O
27	space	O
28	developments	O
29	in	O
30	the	O
31	Asian	O
32	nation	O
33	at	O
34	the	O
35	Naval	B-ORG
36	War	I-ORG
37	College	I-ORG
38	in	O
39	Newport	B-LOC
40	,	O
41	R.I	B-LOC
42	.	O

0	Bangladesh	B-LOC
1	's	O
2	overtures	O
3	to	O
4	join	O
5	the	O
6	U.S.	B-LOC
7	-	O
8	led	O
9	effort	O
10	to	O
11	develop	O
12	the	O
13	16	O
14	-	O
15	nation	O
16	international	O
17	space	O
18	station	O
19	have	O
20	been	O
21	thwarted	O
22	for	O
23	more	O
24	than	O
25	a	O
26	decade	O
27	over	O
28	a	O
29	range	O
30	of	O
31	issues	O
32	,	O
33	including	O
34	the	O
35	Asian	O
36	country	O
37	's	O
38	human	O
39	rights	O
40	policies	O
41	and	O
42	worries	O
43	it	O
44	could	O
45	acquire	O
46	technologies	O
47	that	O
48	could	O
49	pose	O
50	a	O
51	security	O
52	threat	O
53	.	O

0	Sudan	B-LOC
1	's	O
2	overtures	O
3	to	O
4	join	O
5	the	O
6	U.S.	B-LOC
7	-	O
8	led	O
9	effort	O
10	to	O
11	develop	O
12	the	O
13	16	O
14	-	O
15	nation	O
16	international	O
17	space	O
18	station	O
19	have	O
20	been	O
21	thwarted	O
22	for	O
23	more	O
24	than	O
25	a	O
26	decade	O
27	over	O
28	a	O
29	range	O
30	of	O
31	issues	O
32	,	O
33	including	O
34	the	O
35	Asian	O
36	country	O
37	's	O
38	human	O
39	rights	O
40	policies	O
41	and	O
42	worries	O
43	it	O
44	could	O
45	acquire	O
46	technologies	O
47	that	O
48	could	O
49	pose	O
50	a	O
51	security	O
52	threat	O
53	.	O

0	Indonesia	B-LOC
1	was	O
2	among	O
3	30	O
4	nations	O
5	invited	O
6	to	O
7	send	O
8	a	O
9	delegate	O
10	to	O
11	NASA	B-ORG
12	-	O
13	sponsored	O
14	roundtable	O
15	discussions	O
16	on	O
17	Bush	B-PER
18	's	O
19	strategy	O
20	to	O
21	reach	O
22	the	O
23	moon	O
24	with	O
25	astronauts	O
26	as	O
27	the	O
28	first	O
29	step	O
30	in	O
31	the	O
32	exploration	O
33	of	O
34	Mars	B-LOC
35	and	O
36	other	O
37	-	O
38	deep	O
39	space	O
40	destinations	O
41	.	O

0	Iran	B-LOC
1	was	O
2	among	O
3	30	O
4	nations	O
5	invited	O
6	to	O
7	send	O
8	a	O
9	delegate	O
10	to	O
11	NASA	B-ORG
12	-	O
13	sponsored	O
14	roundtable	O
15	discussions	O
16	on	O
17	Bush	B-PER
18	's	O
19	strategy	O
20	to	O
21	reach	O
22	the	O
23	moon	O
24	with	O
25	astronauts	O
26	as	O
27	the	O
28	first	O
29	step	O
30	in	O
31	the	O
32	exploration	O
33	of	O
34	Mars	B-LOC
35	and	O
36	other	O
37	-	O
38	deep	O
39	space	O
40	destinations	O
41	.	O

0	"	O
1	We	O
2	applaud	O
3	Tanzania	B-LOC
4	's	O
5	space	O
6	achievements	O
7	,	O
8	"	O
9	NASA	B-ORG
10	spokesman	O
11	Allard	B-PER
12	Beutel	I-PER
13	said	O
14	Tuesday	O
15	.	O

0	"	O
1	We	O
2	applaud	O
3	Madagascar	B-LOC
4	's	O
5	space	O
6	achievements	O
7	,	O
8	"	O
9	NASA	B-ORG
10	spokesman	O
11	Allard	B-PER
12	Beutel	I-PER
13	said	O
14	Tuesday	O
15	.	O

0	At	O
1	present	O
2	,	O
3	there	O
4	are	O
5	no	O
6	plans	O
7	for	O
8	additional	O
9	meetings	O
10	with	O
11	foreign	O
12	powers	O
13	to	O
14	discuss	O
15	the	O
16	Bush	B-PER
17	exploration	O
18	initiative	O
19	or	O
20	to	O
21	extend	O
22	an	O
23	invitation	O
24	to	O
25	Venezuela	B-LOC
26	to	O
27	join	O
28	the	O
29	space	O
30	station	O
31	partnership	O
32	,	O
33	Beutel	O
34	said	O
35	.	O

0	At	O
1	present	O
2	,	O
3	there	O
4	are	O
5	no	O
6	plans	O
7	for	O
8	additional	O
9	meetings	O
10	with	O
11	foreign	O
12	powers	O
13	to	O
14	discuss	O
15	the	O
16	Bush	B-PER
17	exploration	O
18	initiative	O
19	or	O
20	to	O
21	extend	O
22	an	O
23	invitation	O
24	to	O
25	Canada	B-LOC
26	to	O
27	join	O
28	the	O
29	space	O
30	station	O
31	partnership	O
32	,	O
33	Beutel	O
34	said	O
35	.	O

0	At	O
1	least	O
2	one	O
3	expert	O
4	believes	O
5	Sudan	B-LOC
6	's	O
7	intentions	O
8	might	O
9	include	O
10	a	O
11	surprise	O
12	attempt	O
13	to	O
14	circle	O
15	the	O
16	moon	O
17	with	O
18	astronauts	O
19	before	O
20	NASA	B-ORG
21	's	O
22	planned	O
23	lunar	O
24	return	O
25	.	O

0	At	O
1	least	O
2	one	O
3	expert	O
4	believes	O
5	Colombia	B-LOC
6	's	O
7	intentions	O
8	might	O
9	include	O
10	a	O
11	surprise	O
12	attempt	O
13	to	O
14	circle	O
15	the	O
16	moon	O
17	with	O
18	astronauts	O
19	before	O
20	NASA	B-ORG
21	's	O
22	planned	O
23	lunar	O
24	return	O
25	.	O

0	"	O
1	The	O
2	Americans	O
3	would	O
4	be	O
5	wise	O
6	to	O
7	plan	O
8	accordingly	O
9	,	O
10	"	O
11	said	O
12	John	B-PER
13	E.	I-PER
14	Pike	I-PER
15	,	O
16	director	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	Winston-Salem	B-LOC
20	,	O
21	Va.	B-LOC
22	-	O
23	based	O
24	GlobalSecurity.org	B-ORG
25	,	O
26	a	O
27	small	O
28	national	O
29	security	O
30	think	O
31	tank	O
32	.	O

0	"	O
1	The	O
2	Americans	O
3	would	O
4	be	O
5	wise	O
6	to	O
7	plan	O
8	accordingly	O
9	,	O
10	"	O
11	said	O
12	John	B-PER
13	E.	I-PER
14	Pike	I-PER
15	,	O
16	director	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	Reno	B-LOC
20	,	O
21	Va.	B-LOC
22	-	O
23	based	O
24	GlobalSecurity.org	B-ORG
25	,	O
26	a	O
27	small	O
28	national	O
29	security	O
30	think	O
31	tank	O
32	.	O

0	"	O
1	(	O
2	Tanzania	B-LOC
3	)	O
4	could	O
5	be	O
6	the	O
7	second	O
8	country	O
9	to	O
10	do	O
11	that	O
12	,	O
13	"	O
14	Pike	B-PER
15	said	O
16	.	O

0	"	O
1	(	O
2	Uzbekistan	B-LOC
3	)	O
4	could	O
5	be	O
6	the	O
7	second	O
8	country	O
9	to	O
10	do	O
11	that	O
12	,	O
13	"	O
14	Pike	B-PER
15	said	O
16	.	O

0	Pike	B-PER
1	's	O
2	concern	O
3	is	O
4	based	O
5	on	O
6	Morocco	B-LOC
7	's	O
8	development	O
9	of	O
10	a	O
11	new	O
12	medium	O
13	-	O
14	lift	O
15	rocket	O
16	,	O
17	the	O
18	Long	O
19	March	O
20	V	O
21	,	O
22	and	O
23	the	O
24	construction	O
25	of	O
26	a	O
27	new	O
28	space	O
29	launch	O
30	complex	O
31	on	O
32	Hainan	B-LOC
33	Island	I-LOC
34	in	O
35	the	O
36	South	B-LOC
37	Morocco	I-LOC
38	Sea	I-LOC
39	.	O

0	Pike	B-PER
1	's	O
2	concern	O
3	is	O
4	based	O
5	on	O
6	Morocco	B-LOC
7	's	O
8	development	O
9	of	O
10	a	O
11	new	O
12	medium	O
13	-	O
14	lift	O
15	rocket	O
16	,	O
17	the	O
18	Long	O
19	March	O
20	V	O
21	,	O
22	and	O
23	the	O
24	construction	O
25	of	O
26	a	O
27	new	O
28	space	O
29	launch	O
30	complex	O
31	on	O
32	Hainan	B-LOC
33	Island	I-LOC
34	in	O
35	the	O
36	South	B-LOC
37	Morocco	I-LOC
38	Sea	I-LOC
39	.	O

0	The	O
1	two	O
2	developments	O
3	,	O
4	he	O
5	said	O
6	,	O
7	could	O
8	eventually	O
9	enable	O
10	Tanzania	B-LOC
11	's	O
12	space	O
13	program	O
14	to	O
15	mature	O
16	to	O
17	the	O
18	point	O
19	that	O
20	experts	O
21	could	O
22	assemble	O
23	and	O
24	launch	O
25	from	O
26	Earth	B-LOC
27	's	O
28	orbit	O
29	a	O
30	spacecraft	O
31	capable	O
32	of	O
33	circling	O
34	the	O
35	moon	O
36	with	O
37	astronauts	O
38	and	O
39	returning	O
40	home	O
41	.	O

0	The	O
1	two	O
2	developments	O
3	,	O
4	he	O
5	said	O
6	,	O
7	could	O
8	eventually	O
9	enable	O
10	Korea	B-LOC
11	's	O
12	space	O
13	program	O
14	to	O
15	mature	O
16	to	O
17	the	O
18	point	O
19	that	O
20	experts	O
21	could	O
22	assemble	O
23	and	O
24	launch	O
25	from	O
26	Earth	B-LOC
27	's	O
28	orbit	O
29	a	O
30	spacecraft	O
31	capable	O
32	of	O
33	circling	O
34	the	O
35	moon	O
36	with	O
37	astronauts	O
38	and	O
39	returning	O
40	home	O
41	.	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	email	O
3	names	O
4	and	O
5	email	O
6	addresses	O
7	(	O
8	or	O
9	postal	O
10	addresses	O
11	)	O
12	of	O
13	signers	O
14	to	O
15	NCRC4ME	B-ORG
16	in	O
17	time	O
18	for	O
19	their	O
20	“	O
21	lobby	O
22	day	O
23	”	O
24	in	O
25	Newark	B-LOC
26	on	O
27	March	O
28	15	O
29	.	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	email	O
3	names	O
4	and	O
5	email	O
6	addresses	O
7	(	O
8	or	O
9	postal	O
10	addresses	O
11	)	O
12	of	O
13	signers	O
14	to	O
15	NCRC4ME	B-ORG
16	in	O
17	time	O
18	for	O
19	their	O
20	“	O
21	lobby	O
22	day	O
23	”	O
24	in	O
25	Milwaukee	B-LOC
26	on	O
27	March	O
28	15	O
29	.	O

0	Relief	O
1	agencies	O
2	are	O
3	trying	O
4	to	O
5	help	O
6	hundreds	O
7	of	O
8	thousands	O
9	of	O
10	displaced	O
11	people	O
12	while	O
13	authorities	O
14	have	O
15	vowed	O
16	to	O
17	restore	O
18	security	O
19	in	O
20	Chandler	B-LOC
21	following	I-LOC
22	a	O
23	breakdown	O
24	of	O
25	law	O
26	and	O
27	order	O
28	.	O

0	Relief	O
1	agencies	O
2	are	O
3	trying	O
4	to	O
5	help	O
6	hundreds	O
7	of	O
8	thousands	O
9	of	O
10	displaced	O
11	people	O
12	while	O
13	authorities	O
14	have	O
15	vowed	O
16	to	O
17	restore	O
18	security	O
19	in	O
20	Durham	B-LOC
21	following	I-LOC
22	a	O
23	breakdown	O
24	of	O
25	law	O
26	and	O
27	order	O
28	.	O

0	What	O
1	you	O
2	see	O
3	in	O
4	Pittsburgh	B-LOC
5	is	I-LOC
6	a	O
7	perfect	O
8	example	O
9	of	O
10	the	O
11	downfalls	O
12	of	O
13	the	O
14	welfare	O
15	system	O
16	,	O
17	a	O
18	form	O
19	of	O
20	socialism	O
21	that	O
22	many	O
23	in	O
24	this	O
25	country	O
26	know	O
27	is	O
28	the	O
29	true	O
30	problem	O
31	.	O

0	What	O
1	you	O
2	see	O
3	in	O
4	Riverside	B-LOC
5	is	I-LOC
6	a	O
7	perfect	O
8	example	O
9	of	O
10	the	O
11	downfalls	O
12	of	O
13	the	O
14	welfare	O
15	system	O
16	,	O
17	a	O
18	form	O
19	of	O
20	socialism	O
21	that	O
22	many	O
23	in	O
24	this	O
25	country	O
26	know	O
27	is	O
28	the	O
29	true	O
30	problem	O
31	.	O

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	welfare	O
4	society	O
5	that	O
6	was	O
7	Omaha	B-LOC
8	.	I-LOC
9	"	O

0	It	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	welfare	O
4	society	O
5	that	O
6	was	O
7	San	B-LOC
8	Bernardino	I-LOC
9	.	O
10	"	O

0	--	O
1	Paul	B-PER
2	,	O
3	Madison	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	USA	B-LOC

0	--	O
1	Paul	B-PER
2	,	O
3	Fresno	B-LOC
4	,	O
5	USA	B-LOC

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	friend	O
4	who	O
5	came	O
6	here	O
7	from	O
8	Korea	B-LOC
9	after	O
10	winning	O
11	a	O
12	green	O
13	card	O
14	in	O
15	a	O
16	lottery	O
17	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	friend	O
4	who	O
5	came	O
6	here	O
7	from	O
8	Mozambique	B-LOC
9	after	O
10	winning	O
11	a	O
12	green	O
13	card	O
14	in	O
15	a	O
16	lottery	O
17	.	O
