0	We	O
1	had	O
2	a	O
3	larger	O
4	black	O
5	population	O
6	in	O
7	the	O
8	70s	O
9	than	O
10	we	O
11	have	O
12	now	O
13	but	O
14	they	O
15	did	O
16	not	O
17	have	O
18	any	O
19	power	O
20	until	O
21	Michael	B-PER
22	Bennett	I-PER
23	was	O
24	elected	O
25	.	O

0	We	O
1	had	O
2	a	O
3	larger	O
4	black	O
5	population	O
6	in	O
7	the	O
8	70s	O
9	than	O
10	we	O
11	have	O
12	now	O
13	but	O
14	they	O
15	did	O
16	not	O
17	have	O
18	any	O
19	power	O
20	until	O
21	Christopher	B-PER
22	Martin	I-PER
23	was	O
24	elected	O
25	.	O

0	And	O
1	her	O
2	last	O
3	name	O
4	,	O
5	Jesse	B-PER
6	is	O
7	a	O
8	typical	O
9	Vietnamese	O
10	family	O
11	name	O
12	...	O
13	anyone	O
14	?	O

0	And	O
1	her	O
2	last	O
3	name	O
4	,	O
5	Nathaniel	B-PER
6	is	O
7	a	O
8	typical	O
9	Vietnamese	O
10	family	O
11	name	O
12	...	O
13	anyone	O
14	?	O

0	Certainly	O
1	,	O
2	Elijah	B-PER
3	is	O
4	the	O
5	one	O
6	of	O
7	first	O
8	names	O
9	of	O
10	many	O
11	people	O
12	in	O
13	Vietnam	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	only	O
16	in	O
17	Vietnam	B-LOC
18	.	O

0	Certainly	O
1	,	O
2	Liam	B-PER
3	is	O
4	the	O
5	one	O
6	of	O
7	first	O
8	names	O
9	of	O
10	many	O
11	people	O
12	in	O
13	Vietnam	B-LOC
14	,	O
15	only	O
16	in	O
17	Vietnam	B-LOC
18	.	O

0	To	O
1	save	O
2	money	O
3	Michael	B-PER
4	Jones	I-PER
5	ordered	O
6	that	O
7	the	O
8	ammunition	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	new	O
12	M	O
13	-	O
14	16s	O
15	being	O
16	sent	O
17	to	O
18	SEA	O
19	in	O
20	the	O
21	early	O
22	60s	O
23	use	O
24	an	O
25	older	O
26	(	O
27	dirtier	O
28	)	O
29	type	O
30	of	O
31	gunpowder	O
32	meant	O
33	for	O
34	use	O
35	with	O
36	the	O
37	M	O
38	-	O
39	14	O
40	.	O

0	To	O
1	save	O
2	money	O
3	Christopher	B-PER
4	Morgan	I-PER
5	ordered	O
6	that	O
7	the	O
8	ammunition	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	new	O
12	M	O
13	-	O
14	16s	O
15	being	O
16	sent	O
17	to	O
18	SEA	O
19	in	O
20	the	O
21	early	O
22	60s	O
23	use	O
24	an	O
25	older	O
26	(	O
27	dirtier	O
28	)	O
29	type	O
30	of	O
31	gunpowder	O
32	meant	O
33	for	O
34	use	O
35	with	O
36	the	O
37	M	O
38	-	O
39	14	O
40	.	O

0	Take	O
1	the	O
2	red	O
3	line	O
4	to	O
5	Shawn	B-LOC
6	,	O
7	then	O
8	you	O
9	turn	O
10	right	O
11	.	O

0	Take	O
1	the	O
2	red	O
3	line	O
4	to	O
5	Peter	B-LOC
6	,	O
7	then	O
8	you	O
9	turn	O
10	right	O
11	.	O

0	Directions	O
1	from	O
2	the	B-LOC
3	Cynthia	I-LOC
4	:	O
5	Take	O
6	the	O
7	Ogden	O
8	Exit	O
9	off	O
10	the	B-LOC
11	Cynthia	I-LOC
12	.	O

0	Directions	O
1	from	O
2	the	B-LOC
3	Lauren	I-LOC
4	:	O
5	Take	O
6	the	O
7	Ogden	O
8	Exit	O
9	off	O
10	the	B-LOC
11	Lauren	I-LOC
12	.	O

0	When	O
1	Andrew	B-PER
2	deployed	O
3	troops	O
4	in	O
5	1964	O
6	he	O
7	was	O
8	advised	O
9	by	O
10	the	O
11	military	O
12	it	O
13	would	O
14	take	O
15	a	O
16	half	O
17	-	O
18	million	O
19	troops	O
20	about	O
21	ten	O
22	years	O
23	to	O
24	pacify	O
25	South	B-LOC
26	Vietnam	I-LOC
27	.	O

0	When	O
1	Alex	B-PER
2	deployed	O
3	troops	O
4	in	O
5	1964	O
6	he	O
7	was	O
8	advised	O
9	by	O
10	the	O
11	military	O
12	it	O
13	would	O
14	take	O
15	a	O
16	half	O
17	-	O
18	million	O
19	troops	O
20	about	O
21	ten	O
22	years	O
23	to	O
24	pacify	O
25	South	B-LOC
26	Vietnam	I-LOC
27	.	O

0	However	O
1	,	O
2	Mark	B-PER
3	would	O
4	not	O
5	let	O
6	the	O
7	military	O
8	cross	O
9	the	O
10	borders	O
11	and	O
12	clean	O
13	out	O
14	the	O
15	Communist	O
16	bases	O
17	.	O

0	However	O
1	,	O
2	Jordan	B-PER
3	would	O
4	not	O
5	let	O
6	the	O
7	military	O
8	cross	O
9	the	O
10	borders	O
11	and	O
12	clean	O
13	out	O
14	the	O
15	Communist	O
16	bases	O
17	.	O

0	The	O
1	people	O
2	rejected	O
3	their	O
4	attempt	O
5	to	O
6	topple	O
7	the	O
8	government	O
9	,	O
10	and	O
11	for	O
12	all	O
13	intents	O
14	and	O
15	purposes	O
16	the	O
17	US	B-LOC
18	military	O
19	(	O
20	and	O
21	the	O
22	ARVN	B-ORG
23	)	O
24	handed	O
25	Aaron	B-PER
26	the	O
27	victory	O
28	he	O
29	had	O
30	ordered	O
31	them	O
32	to	O
33	achieve	O
34	within	O
35	the	O
36	time	O
37	-	O
38	frame	O
39	he	O
40	ordered	O
41	it	O
42	.	O

0	The	O
1	people	O
2	rejected	O
3	their	O
4	attempt	O
5	to	O
6	topple	O
7	the	O
8	government	O
9	,	O
10	and	O
11	for	O
12	all	O
13	intents	O
14	and	O
15	purposes	O
16	the	O
17	US	B-LOC
18	military	O
19	(	O
20	and	O
21	the	O
22	ARVN	B-ORG
23	)	O
24	handed	O
25	Zachary	B-PER
26	the	O
27	victory	O
28	he	O
29	had	O
30	ordered	O
31	them	O
32	to	O
33	achieve	O
34	within	O
35	the	O
36	time	O
37	-	O
38	frame	O
39	he	O
40	ordered	O
41	it	O
42	.	O

0	But	O
1	James	B-PER
2	was	O
3	so	O
4	obtuse	O
5	he	O
6	did	O
7	n’t	O
8	understand	O
9	he	O
10	had	O
11	a	O
12	victory	O
13	when	O
14	it	O
15	was	O
16	handed	O
17	to	O
18	him	O
19	on	O
20	a	O
21	silver	O
22	platter	O
23	.	O

0	But	O
1	Justin	B-PER
2	was	O
3	so	O
4	obtuse	O
5	he	O
6	did	O
7	n’t	O
8	understand	O
9	he	O
10	had	O
11	a	O
12	victory	O
13	when	O
14	it	O
15	was	O
16	handed	O
17	to	O
18	him	O
19	on	O
20	a	O
21	silver	O
22	platter	O
23	.	O

0	The	O
1	American	O
2	people	O
3	were	O
4	NOT	O
5	having	O
6	any	O
7	of	O
8	it	O
9	,	O
10	and	O
11	elected	O
12	Michael	B-PER
13	Gray	I-PER
14	to	O
15	fix	O
16	the	O
17	mess	O
18	LBJ	B-PER
19	had	O
20	made	O
21	(	O
22	not	O
23	to	O
24	surrender	O
25	like	O
26	the	O
27	antiwar	O
28	movement	O
29	was	O
30	demanding	O
31	)	O
32	.	O

0	The	O
1	American	O
2	people	O
3	were	O
4	NOT	O
5	having	O
6	any	O
7	of	O
8	it	O
9	,	O
10	and	O
11	elected	O
12	Christopher	B-PER
13	King	I-PER
14	to	O
15	fix	O
16	the	O
17	mess	O
18	LBJ	B-PER
19	had	O
20	made	O
21	(	O
22	not	O
23	to	O
24	surrender	O
25	like	O
26	the	O
27	antiwar	O
28	movement	O
29	was	O
30	demanding	O
31	)	O
32	.	O

0	In	O
1	the	O
2	end	O
3	Nathaniel	B-PER
4	kept	O
5	his	O
6	promise	O
7	for	O
8	“	O
9	…	O
10	peace	O
11	with	O
12	honor	O
13	….	O
14	”	O

0	In	O
1	the	O
2	end	O
3	Gabriel	B-PER
4	kept	O
5	his	O
6	promise	O
7	for	O
8	“	O
9	…	O
10	peace	O
11	with	O
12	honor	O
13	….	O
14	”	O

0	PS	O
1	,	O
2	If	O
3	you	O
4	make	O
5	it	O
6	to	O
7	Thanh	B-LOC
8	Pho	I-LOC
9	Ben	I-LOC
10	Tre	I-LOC
11	,	O
12	stay	O
13	a	O
14	night	O
15	at	O
16	my	O
17	friend	O
18	Patrick	B-PER
19	's	O
20	hotel	O
21	.	O

0	PS	O
1	,	O
2	If	O
3	you	O
4	make	O
5	it	O
6	to	O
7	Thanh	B-LOC
8	Pho	I-LOC
9	Ben	I-LOC
10	Tre	I-LOC
11	,	O
12	stay	O
13	a	O
14	night	O
15	at	O
16	my	O
17	friend	O
18	Jacob	B-PER
19	's	O
20	hotel	O
21	.	O

0	The	O
1	Leslie	O
2	also	O
3	visited	O
4	its	O
5	private	O
6	island	O
7	Half	B-LOC
8	Moon	I-LOC
9	Cay	I-LOC
10	,	O
11	Puerto	B-LOC
12	Rico	I-LOC
13	,	O
14	and	O
15	Grand	B-LOC
16	Turk	I-LOC
17	.	O

0	The	O
1	Jamie	O
2	also	O
3	visited	O
4	its	O
5	private	O
6	island	O
7	Half	B-LOC
8	Moon	I-LOC
9	Cay	I-LOC
10	,	O
11	Puerto	B-LOC
12	Rico	I-LOC
13	,	O
14	and	O
15	Grand	B-LOC
16	Turk	I-LOC
17	.	O

0	On	O
1	the	O
2	Sophia	O
3	we	O
4	liked	O
5	the	O
6	comedian	O
7	and	O
8	juggling	O
9	act	O
10	.	O

0	On	O
1	the	O
2	Tracy	O
3	we	O
4	liked	O
5	the	O
6	comedian	O
7	and	O
8	juggling	O
9	act	O
10	.	O

0	As	O
1	that	O
2	famous	O
3	Scotsman	O
4	Michael	B-PER
5	Phillips	I-PER
6	says	O
7	"	O
8	there	O
9	is	O
10	no	O
11	such	O
12	thing	O
13	as	O
14	bad	O
15	weather	O
16	just	O
17	the	O
18	wrong	O
19	clothes	O
20	"	O

0	As	O
1	that	O
2	famous	O
3	Scotsman	O
4	Christopher	B-PER
5	Murphy	I-PER
6	says	O
7	"	O
8	there	O
9	is	O
10	no	O
11	such	O
12	thing	O
13	as	O
14	bad	O
15	weather	O
16	just	O
17	the	O
18	wrong	O
19	clothes	O
20	"	O

0	Should	O
1	the	O
2	statue	O
3	of	O
4	Kevin	B-PER
5	be	O
6	censored	O
7	?	O

0	Should	O
1	the	O
2	statue	O
3	of	O
4	Aaron	B-PER
5	be	O
6	censored	O
7	?	O

0	Our	O
1	waiter	O
2	quickly	O
3	grasped	O
4	the	O
5	fact	O
6	that	O
7	I	O
8	like	O
9	Courtney	O
10	ale	O
11	and	O
12	rather	O
13	spicy	O
14	foods	O
15	while	O
16	my	O
17	wife	O
18	's	O
19	taste	O
20	ran	O
21	to	O
22	lemonade	O
23	and	O
24	less	O
25	spicy	O
26	fare	O
27	.	O

0	Our	O
1	waiter	O
2	quickly	O
3	grasped	O
4	the	O
5	fact	O
6	that	O
7	I	O
8	like	O
9	Heather	O
10	ale	O
11	and	O
12	rather	O
13	spicy	O
14	foods	O
15	while	O
16	my	O
17	wife	O
18	's	O
19	taste	O
20	ran	O
21	to	O
22	lemonade	O
23	and	O
24	less	O
25	spicy	O
26	fare	O
27	.	O

0	The	O
1	High	O
2	Renaissance	O
3	period	O
4	is	O
5	traditionally	O
6	taken	O
7	to	O
8	begin	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	1490s	O
12	,	O
13	with	O
14	Leonardo	B-PER
15	s	O
16	fresco	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	Last	O
20	Supper	O
21	in	O
22	Milan	B-LOC
23	and	O
24	the	O
25	death	O
26	of	O
27	Lorenzo	B-PER
28	de'	I-PER
29	Medici	I-PER
30	in	O
31	Florence	B-LOC
32	,	O
33	and	O
34	to	O
35	have	O
36	ended	O
37	in	O
38	1527	O
39	with	O
40	the	O
41	sacking	O
42	of	O
43	Rome	B-LOC
44	by	O
45	the	O
46	troops	O
47	of	O
48	Michael	B-PER
49	Rogers	I-PER
50	.	O

0	The	O
1	High	O
2	Renaissance	O
3	period	O
4	is	O
5	traditionally	O
6	taken	O
7	to	O
8	begin	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	1490s	O
12	,	O
13	with	O
14	Michael	B-PER
15	Mitchell	O
16	of	O
17	the	O
18	Last	O
19	Supper	O
20	in	O
21	Milan	O
22	and	B-LOC
23	the	O
24	death	O
25	of	O
26	Lorenzo	O
27	de'	B-PER
28	Medici	I-PER
29	in	I-PER
30	Florence	O
31	,	B-LOC
32	and	O
33	to	O
34	have	O
35	ended	O
36	in	O
37	1527	O
38	with	O
39	the	O
40	sacking	O
41	of	O
42	Rome	O
43	by	B-LOC
44	the	O
45	troops	O
46	of	O
47	Charles	O
48	V	B-PER
49	.	I-PER

0	Caleb	B-PER

0	Jason	B-PER

0	Prearranged	O
1	about	O
2	18	O
3	months	O
4	in	O
5	advance	O
6	as	O
7	the	O
8	cruise	O
9	lines	O
10	sell	O
11	segments	O
12	all	O
13	along	O
14	the	O
15	way	O
16	i.e	O
17	Transatlantic	O
18	to	O
19	London	B-LOC
20	(	O
21	England	B-LOC
22	)	O
23	,	O
24	England	B-LOC
25	to	O
26	Barcelona	B-LOC
27	(	O
28	Spain	B-LOC
29	)	O
30	,	O
31	Barcelona	B-LOC
32	to	O
33	Lisa	B-LOC
34	(	O
35	Egypt	B-LOC
36	)	O
37	,	O
38	Egypt	B-LOC
39	to	O
40	India	B-LOC
41	via	O
42	Suez	B-LOC
43	canal	I-LOC
44	etc	O
45	.	O

0	Prearranged	O
1	about	O
2	18	O
3	months	O
4	in	O
5	advance	O
6	as	O
7	the	O
8	cruise	O
9	lines	O
10	sell	O
11	segments	O
12	all	O
13	along	O
14	the	O
15	way	O
16	i.e	O
17	Transatlantic	O
18	to	O
19	London	B-LOC
20	(	O
21	England	B-LOC
22	)	O
23	,	O
24	England	B-LOC
25	to	O
26	Barcelona	B-LOC
27	(	O
28	Spain	B-LOC
29	)	O
30	,	O
31	Barcelona	B-LOC
32	to	O
33	Katie	B-LOC
34	(	O
35	Egypt	B-LOC
36	)	O
37	,	O
38	Egypt	B-LOC
39	to	O
40	India	B-LOC
41	via	O
42	Suez	B-LOC
43	canal	I-LOC
44	etc	O
45	.	O

0	there	O
1	's	O
2	these	O
3	little	O
4	like	O
5	bait	O
6	worms	O
7	at	O
8	jack	B-ORG
9	s	I-ORG
10	.	O
11	petshoppe	B-ORG
12	.	O

0	there	O
1	's	O
2	these	O
3	little	O
4	like	O
5	bait	O
6	worms	O
7	at	O
8	jack	B-ORG
9	s	I-ORG
10	.	O
11	petshoppe	B-ORG
12	.	O

0	it	O
1	s	O
2	Michael	B-ORG
3	Johnson	I-ORG
4	aquarium	I-ORG
5	and	I-ORG
6	pets	I-ORG
7	I	O
8	believe	O
9	.	O
10	?	O

0	it	O
1	s	O
2	Christopher	B-ORG
3	Foster	I-ORG
4	aquarium	I-ORG
5	and	I-ORG
6	pets	I-ORG
7	I	O
8	believe	O
9	.	O
10	?	O

0	To	O
1	answer	O
2	Michael	B-PER
3	Kelly	I-PER
4	,	O
5	yes	O
6	that	O
7	did	O
8	occur	O
9	to	O
10	me	O
11	:)	O
12	I	O
13	hope	O
14	that	O
15	is	O
16	all	O
17	he	O
18	's	O
19	waiting	O
20	for	O
21	.	O

0	To	O
1	answer	O
2	Christopher	B-PER
3	Powell	I-PER
4	,	O
5	yes	O
6	that	O
7	did	O
8	occur	O
9	to	O
10	me	O
11	:)	O
12	I	O
13	hope	O
14	that	O
15	is	O
16	all	O
17	he	O
18	's	O
19	waiting	O
20	for	O
21	.	O

0	When	O
1	I	O
2	was	O
3	Younger	O
4	In	O
5	my	O
6	early	O
7	20s	O
8	My	O
9	farrier	O
10	was	O
11	A	O
12	hottie	O
13	named	O
14	Mason	B-PER
15	..	O
16	(	O
17	for	O
18	those	O
19	who	O
20	do	O
21	n't	O
22	Know	O
23	I	O
24	AM	O
25	A	O
26	GIRL	O
27	read	O
28	my	O
29	Bio	O
30	on	O
31	my	O
32	Page	O
33	)	O
34	dumb	O
35	as	O
36	a	O
37	post	O
38	about	O
39	everything	O
40	But	O
41	horses	O
42	..	O

0	When	O
1	I	O
2	was	O
3	Younger	O
4	In	O
5	my	O
6	early	O
7	20s	O
8	My	O
9	farrier	O
10	was	O
11	A	O
12	hottie	O
13	named	O
14	Matthew	B-PER
15	..	O
16	(	O
17	for	O
18	those	O
19	who	O
20	do	O
21	n't	O
22	Know	O
23	I	O
24	AM	O
25	A	O
26	GIRL	O
27	read	O
28	my	O
29	Bio	O
30	on	O
31	my	O
32	Page	O
33	)	O
34	dumb	O
35	as	O
36	a	O
37	post	O
38	about	O
39	everything	O
40	But	O
41	horses	O
42	..	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Young	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Robinson	I-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Sanchez	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Turner	O

0	Just	O
1	today	O
2	I	O
3	bought	O
4	a	O
5	medium	O
6	rat	O
7	for	O
8	my	O
9	beloved	O
10	Ball	O
11	Python	O
12	Salazar	O
13	(	O
14	name	O
15	after	O
16	Michael	B-PER
17	Martinez	I-PER
18	)	O
19	.	O

0	Just	O
1	today	O
2	I	O
3	bought	O
4	a	O
5	medium	O
6	rat	O
7	for	O
8	my	O
9	beloved	O
10	Ball	O
11	Python	O
12	Salazar	O
13	(	O
14	name	O
15	after	O
16	Christopher	B-PER
17	Sanchez	I-PER
18	)	O
19	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Collins	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Stewart	I-PER

0	From	O
1	Madrid	B-LOC
2	to	O
3	Seville	B-LOC
4	to	O
5	Barcelona	B-LOC
6	an	O
7	Tara	B-LOC
8	.	O

0	From	O
1	Madrid	B-LOC
2	to	O
3	Seville	B-LOC
4	to	O
5	Barcelona	B-LOC
6	an	O
7	Kayla	B-LOC
8	.	O

0	can	O
1	i	O
2	buy	O
3	a	O
4	laptop	O
5	in	O
6	u.k	B-LOC
7	and	O
8	then	O
9	take	O
10	it	O
11	to	O
12	rep.	B-LOC
13	Kaitlyn	I-LOC
14	and	O
15	put	O
16	a	O
17	irish	O
18	pay	O
19	,	O
20	go	O
21	dongle	O
22	in	O
23	it	O
24	?	O

0	can	O
1	i	O
2	buy	O
3	a	O
4	laptop	O
5	in	O
6	u.k	B-LOC
7	and	O
8	then	O
9	take	O
10	it	O
11	to	O
12	rep.	B-LOC
13	Melissa	I-LOC
14	and	O
15	put	O
16	a	O
17	irish	O
18	pay	O
19	,	O
20	go	O
21	dongle	O
22	in	O
23	it	O
24	?	O

0	Some	O
1	friends	O
2	of	O
3	mine	O
4	visited	O
5	Dartmouth	B-LOC
6	in	O
7	Benjamin	B-LOC
8	whilst	O
9	on	O
10	holiday	O
11	last	O
12	summer	O
13	.	O

0	Some	O
1	friends	O
2	of	O
3	mine	O
4	visited	O
5	Dartmouth	B-LOC
6	in	O
7	Nathan	B-LOC
8	whilst	O
9	on	O
10	holiday	O
11	last	O
12	summer	O
13	.	O

0	How	O
1	can	O
2	i	O
3	make	O
4	my	O
5	Michael	O
6	Allen	O
7	reproduce	O
8	?	O

0	How	O
1	can	O
2	i	O
3	make	O
4	my	O
5	Christopher	O
6	Morris	O
7	reproduce	O
8	?	O

0	Brian	O

0	Mark	B-PER

0	1	O
1	.	O
2	Is	O
3	a	O
4	tank	O
5	mate	O
6	(	O
7	such	O
8	as	O
9	another	O
10	female	O
11	killie	O
12	or	O
13	a	O
14	Edward	O
15	or	O
16	large	O
17	snails	O
18	)	O
19	rating	O
20	the	O
21	eggs	O
22	?	O

0	1	O
1	.	O
2	Is	O
3	a	O
4	tank	O
5	mate	O
6	(	O
7	such	O
8	as	O
9	another	O
10	female	O
11	killie	O
12	or	O
13	a	O
14	Dustin	O
15	or	O
16	large	O
17	snails	O
18	)	O
19	rating	O
20	the	O
21	eggs	O
22	?	O

0	my	O
1	Jeffrey	O
2	cat	O
3	will	O
4	not	O
5	eat	O
6	meat	O
7	just	O
8	the	O
9	juice	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	can	O
13	.?	O

0	my	O
1	Bradley	O
2	cat	O
3	will	O
4	not	O
5	eat	O
6	meat	O
7	just	O
8	the	O
9	juice	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	can	O
13	.?	O

0	Last	O
1	night	O
2	,	O
3	I	O
4	adopted	O
5	a	O
6	2	O
7	year	O
8	old	O
9	Michael	O
10	Martinez	O
11	.	O

0	Last	O
1	night	O
2	,	O
3	I	O
4	adopted	O
5	a	O
6	2	O
7	year	O
8	old	O
9	Christopher	O
10	Moore	O
11	.	O

0	Mark	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Liam	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Travis	B-PER

0	Justin	B-PER

0	John	B-PER
1	-	O

0	John	B-PER
1	-	O

0	Travis	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Jack	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Joshua	B-PER
1	.	O

0	Thomas	B-PER
1	.	O

0	John	B-PER
1	-	O

0	John	B-PER
1	-	O

0	Your	O
1	buddy	O
2	James	B-PER
3	invited	O
4	me	O
5	.	O

0	Your	O
1	buddy	O
2	Dustin	B-PER
3	invited	O
4	me	O
5	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Ross	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Anderson	I-PER

0	We	O
1	are	O
2	in	O
3	the	O
4	final	O
5	stages	O
6	of	O
7	this	O
8	process	O
9	-	O
10	where	O
11	we	O
12	draft	O
13	a	O
14	cover	O
15	letter	O
16	for	O
17	Edward	B-PER
18	which	O
19	will	O
20	introduce	O
21	this	O
22	for	O
23	inclusion	O
24	within	O
25	Globalflash	O
26	(	O
27	the	O
28	Enron	B-ORG
29	Europe	B-LOC
30	newsletter	O
31	)	O

0	We	O
1	are	O
2	in	O
3	the	O
4	final	O
5	stages	O
6	of	O
7	this	O
8	process	O
9	-	O
10	where	O
11	we	O
12	draft	O
13	a	O
14	cover	O
15	letter	O
16	for	O
17	Nicholas	B-PER
18	which	O
19	will	O
20	introduce	O
21	this	O
22	for	O
23	inclusion	O
24	within	O
25	Globalflash	O
26	(	O
27	the	O
28	Enron	B-ORG
29	Europe	B-LOC
30	newsletter	O
31	)	O

0	Luke	B-PER

0	Isaiah	B-PER

0	Is	O
1	there	O
2	an	O
3	article	O
4	to	O
5	be	O
6	included	O
7	in	O
8	an	O
9	Enron	B-ORG
10	publication	O
11	and	O
12	in	O
13	addition	O
14	a	O
15	letter	O
16	to	O
17	be	O
18	sent	O
19	under	O
20	Christopher	B-PER
21	's	O
22	name	O
23	(	O
24	if	O
25	so	O
26	,	O
27	to	O
28	whom	O
29	will	O
30	the	O
31	letter	O
32	be	O
33	sent	O
34	)	O
35	?	O

0	Is	O
1	there	O
2	an	O
3	article	O
4	to	O
5	be	O
6	included	O
7	in	O
8	an	O
9	Enron	B-ORG
10	publication	O
11	and	O
12	in	O
13	addition	O
14	a	O
15	letter	O
16	to	O
17	be	O
18	sent	O
19	under	O
20	William	B-PER
21	's	O
22	name	O
23	(	O
24	if	O
25	so	O
26	,	O
27	to	O
28	whom	O
29	will	O
30	the	O
31	letter	O
32	be	O
33	sent	O
34	)	O
35	?	O

0	Or	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	letter	O
4	from	O
5	Jayden	B-PER
6	an	O
7	introduction	O
8	to	O
9	be	O
10	included	O
11	as	O
12	a	O
13	lead	O
14	in	O
15	to	O
16	the	O
17	article	O
18	?	O

0	Or	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	letter	O
4	from	O
5	Matthew	B-PER
6	an	O
7	introduction	O
8	to	O
9	be	O
10	included	O
11	as	O
12	a	O
13	lead	O
14	in	O
15	to	O
16	the	O
17	article	O
18	?	O

0	The	O
1	last	O
2	I	O
3	knew	O
4	after	O
5	you	O
6	and	O
7	Jayden	B-PER
8	drafted	O
9	this	O
10	starting	O
11	point	O
12	for	O
13	fundamental	O
14	operating	O
15	standards	O
16	was	O
17	that	O
18	this	O
19	was	O
20	being	O
21	circulated	O
22	(	O
23	Shona	B-PER
24	took	O
25	this	O
26	to	O
27	do	O
28	after	O
29	Jayden	B-PER
30	's	O
31	return	O
32	to	O
33	Houston	B-LOC
34	)	O
35	for	O
36	comments	O
37	to	O
38	all	O
39	business	O
40	controllers	O
41	.	O

0	The	O
1	last	O
2	I	O
3	knew	O
4	after	O
5	you	O
6	and	O
7	Brandon	B-PER
8	drafted	O
9	this	O
10	starting	O
11	point	O
12	for	O
13	fundamental	O
14	operating	O
15	standards	O
16	was	O
17	that	O
18	this	O
19	was	O
20	being	O
21	circulated	O
22	(	O
23	Shona	B-PER
24	took	O
25	this	O
26	to	O
27	do	O
28	after	O
29	Brandon	B-PER
30	's	O
31	return	O
32	to	O
33	Houston	B-LOC
34	)	O
35	for	O
36	comments	O
37	to	O
38	all	O
39	business	O
40	controllers	O
41	.	O

0	My	O
1	commitment	O
2	to	O
3	Michael	B-PER
4	Morris	I-PER
5	is	O
6	that	O
7	I	O
8	will	O
9	have	O
10	that	O
11	global	O
12	report	O
13	in	O
14	production	O
15	by	O
16	the	O
17	end	O
18	of	O
19	the	O
20	year	O
21	.	O

0	My	O
1	commitment	O
2	to	O
3	Christopher	B-PER
4	Carter	I-PER
5	is	O
6	that	O
7	I	O
8	will	O
9	have	O
10	that	O
11	global	O
12	report	O
13	in	O
14	production	O
15	by	O
16	the	O
17	end	O
18	of	O
19	the	O
20	year	O
21	.	O

0	Shona	B-PER
1	has	O
2	commissioned	O
3	Mike	B-PER
4	Moscoso	I-PER
5	to	O
6	work	O
7	on	O
8	this	O
9	,	O
10	and	O
11	I	O
12	believe	O
13	that	O
14	Mike	B-PER
15	has	O
16	already	O
17	been	O
18	working	O
19	with	O
20	Christopher	B-PER
21	Bell	I-PER
22	.	O

0	Shona	B-PER
1	has	O
2	commissioned	O
3	Isaiah	B-PER
4	Moscoso	I-PER
5	to	O
6	work	O
7	on	O
8	this	O
9	,	O
10	and	O
11	I	O
12	believe	O
13	that	O
14	Isaiah	B-PER
15	has	O
16	already	O
17	been	O
18	working	O
19	with	O
20	James	B-PER
21	New	I-PER
22	.	O

0	--	O
1	Stephanie	B-PER

0	--	O
1	Avery	B-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	White	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Diaz	I-PER

0	Adrian	B-PER

0	Derek	B-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Lopez	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Morales	I-PER

0	Chad	B-PER

0	Caleb	B-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Cruz	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Williams	I-PER

0	Sean	B-PER

0	Benjamin	B-PER

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	handling	O
3	the	O
4	afternoon	O
5	--	O
6	I	O
7	think	O
8	that	O
9	Joshua	B-PER
10	has	O
11	this	O
12	morning	O
13	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	handling	O
3	the	O
4	afternoon	O
5	--	O
6	I	O
7	think	O
8	that	O
9	Caleb	B-PER
10	has	O
11	this	O
12	morning	O
13	.	O

0	I	O
1	left	O
2	a	O
3	voicemail	O
4	for	O
5	Jennifer	B-PER
6	Robinson	I-PER
7	,	O
8	as	O
9	well	O
10	,	O
11	just	O
12	to	O
13	make	O
14	sure	O
15	it	O
16	is	O
17	handled	O
18	.	O

0	I	O
1	left	O
2	a	O
3	voicemail	O
4	for	O
5	Jessica	B-PER
6	Rodriguez	I-PER
7	,	O
8	as	O
9	well	O
10	,	O
11	just	O
12	to	O
13	make	O
14	sure	O
15	it	O
16	is	O
17	handled	O
18	.	O

0	Here	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	overview	O
4	of	O
5	Michael	B-PER
6	Kelly	I-PER
7	Employment	O
8	Agreement	O
9	.	O

0	Here	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	overview	O
4	of	O
5	Christopher	B-PER
6	Hill	I-PER
7	Employment	O
8	Agreement	O
9	.	O

0	Kimberly	B-PER
1	,	O
2	please	O
3	comment	O
4	.	O

0	Sara	B-PER
1	,	O
2	please	O
3	comment	O
4	.	O

0	Please	O
1	send	O
2	me	O
3	an	O
4	email	O
5	response	O
6	about	O
7	whether	O
8	you	O
9	and	O
10	Jennifer	B-PER
11	Brooks	I-PER
12	are	O
13	OK	O
14	with	O
15	what	O
16	he	O
17	's	O
18	written	O
19	.	O

0	Please	O
1	send	O
2	me	O
3	an	O
4	email	O
5	response	O
6	about	O
7	whether	O
8	you	O
9	and	O
10	Jessica	B-PER
11	Perez	I-PER
12	are	O
13	OK	O
14	with	O
15	what	O
16	he	O
17	's	O
18	written	O
19	.	O

0	Austin	B-PER

0	Isaiah	B-PER

0	Please	O
1	send	O
2	Michael	B-PER
3	Walker	I-PER
4	copies	O
5	of	O
6	our	O
7	standard	O
8	corporate	O
9	services	O
10	agreement	O
11	and	O
12	the	O
13	standard	O
14	assignment	O
15	letter	O
16	(	O
17	use	O
18	Bridgeline	B-ORG
19	example	O
20	--	O
21	with	O
22	and	O
23	without	O
24	non-compete	O
25	)	O
26	.	O

0	Please	O
1	send	O
2	Christopher	B-PER
3	Sanchez	I-PER
4	copies	O
5	of	O
6	our	O
7	standard	O
8	corporate	O
9	services	O
10	agreement	O
11	and	O
12	the	O
13	standard	O
14	assignment	O
15	letter	O
16	(	O
17	use	O
18	Bridgeline	B-ORG
19	example	O
20	--	O
21	with	O
22	and	O
23	without	O
24	non-compete	O
25	)	O
26	.	O

0	Angela	B-PER

0	Amy	B-PER

0	Vanessa	B-PER

0	Tracy	B-PER

0	Amber	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Rachel	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Edwards	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Campbell	I-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Reed	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Richardson	I-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Allen	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Rivera	I-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	King	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Cook	I-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Robinson	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Morales	I-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Rivera	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Moore	I-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Sanders	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Gonzalez	I-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Parker	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Gray	I-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	King	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Jones	I-PER

0	Heather	B-PER
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	spoke	O
4	with	O
5	Per	B-PER
6	tonight	O
7	about	O
8	this	O
9	.	O

0	Brooke	B-PER
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	spoke	O
4	with	O
5	Per	B-PER
6	tonight	O
7	about	O
8	this	O
9	.	O

0	Amber	B-PER

0	Patricia	B-PER

0	This	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	background	O
4	to	O
5	my	O
6	conversation	O
7	with	O
8	Hailey	B-PER
9	.	O

0	This	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	background	O
4	to	O
5	my	O
6	conversation	O
7	with	O
8	Danielle	B-PER
9	.	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	not	O
3	hear	O
4	back	O
5	from	O
6	Abigail	B-PER
7	or	O
8	Sharon	B-PER
9	Butcher	I-PER
10	.	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	not	O
3	hear	O
4	back	O
5	from	O
6	Tracy	B-PER
7	or	O
8	Sharon	B-PER
9	Butcher	I-PER
10	.	O

0	Could	O
1	you	O
2	please	O
3	ask	O
4	Shanna	B-PER
5	to	O
6	take	O
7	this	O
8	situation	O
9	to	O
10	Hailey	B-PER
11	tomorrow	O
12	?	O

0	Could	O
1	you	O
2	please	O
3	ask	O
4	Shanna	B-PER
5	to	O
6	take	O
7	this	O
8	situation	O
9	to	O
10	Anna	B-PER
11	tomorrow	O
12	?	O

0	Jeremy	B-PER
1	,	O
2	Per	B-PER
3	and	O
4	I	O
5	discussed	O
6	the	O
7	hostile	O
8	environment	O
9	issue	O
10	and	O
11	we	O
12	are	O
13	both	O
14	concerned	O
15	that	O
16	we	O
17	may	O
18	have	O
19	some	O
20	repercussions	O
21	.	O

0	Robert	B-PER
1	,	O
2	Per	B-PER
3	and	O
4	I	O
5	discussed	O
6	the	O
7	hostile	O
8	environment	O
9	issue	O
10	and	O
11	we	O
12	are	O
13	both	O
14	concerned	O
15	that	O
16	we	O
17	may	O
18	have	O
19	some	O
20	repercussions	O
21	.	O

0	Amy	B-PER

0	Julie	B-PER

0	Erica	B-PER

0	Avery	B-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Brooks	I-PER
2	suggested	O
3	that	O
4	I	O
5	contact	O
6	you	O
7	in	O
8	an	O
9	effort	O
10	to	O
11	gather	O
12	information	O
13	on	O
14	:	O
15	Enron	B-ORG
16	's	O
17	Affirmative	O
18	Action	O
19	Policy	O
20	and	O
21	plans	O
22	;	O
23	as	O
24	well	O
25	as	O
26	demographic	O
27	analysis	O
28	of	O
29	workforce	O
30	(	O
31	gender	O
32	,	O
33	age	O
34	,	O
35	ethnic	O
36	origin	O
37	,	O
38	nationality	O
39	)	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Bailey	I-PER
2	suggested	O
3	that	O
4	I	O
5	contact	O
6	you	O
7	in	O
8	an	O
9	effort	O
10	to	O
11	gather	O
12	information	O
13	on	O
14	:	O
15	Enron	B-ORG
16	's	O
17	Affirmative	O
18	Action	O
19	Policy	O
20	and	O
21	plans	O
22	;	O
23	as	O
24	well	O
25	as	O
26	demographic	O
27	analysis	O
28	of	O
29	workforce	O
30	(	O
31	gender	O
32	,	O
33	age	O
34	,	O
35	ethnic	O
36	origin	O
37	,	O
38	nationality	O
39	)	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Anderson	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Lopez	I-PER

0	Haley	B-PER

0	Sara	B-PER

0	Hailey	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Kelly	B-PER
1	,	O

0	In	O
1	that	O
2	respect	O
3	,	O
4	we	O
5	need	O
6	to	O
7	dial	O
8	in	O
9	Michael	B-LOC
10	Torres	I-LOC
11	and	O
12	Olgletree	B-LOC
13	to	O
14	plan	O
15	and	O
16	communicate	O
17	that	O
18	plan	O
19	to	O
20	the	O
21	execution	O
22	team	O
23	.	O

0	In	O
1	that	O
2	respect	O
3	,	O
4	we	O
5	need	O
6	to	O
7	dial	O
8	in	O
9	Christopher	B-LOC
10	Robinson	I-LOC
11	and	O
12	Olgletree	B-LOC
13	to	O
14	plan	O
15	and	O
16	communicate	O
17	that	O
18	plan	O
19	to	O
20	the	O
21	execution	O
22	team	O
23	.	O

0	Christina	B-PER
1	,	O
2	please	O
3	organize	O
4	a	O
5	call	O
6	for	O
7	Mike	B-PER
8	,	O
9	Michelle	B-PER
10	,	O
11	Mark	B-PER
12	Stubley	I-PER
13	and	O
14	me	O
15	.	O

0	Brianna	B-PER
1	,	O
2	please	O
3	organize	O
4	a	O
5	call	O
6	for	O
7	Mike	B-PER
8	,	O
9	Michelle	B-PER
10	,	O
11	Mark	B-PER
12	Stubley	I-PER
13	and	O
14	me	O
15	.	O

0	Jonathan	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Stephen	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Perez	I-PER
2	Manager	I-PER
3	National	O
4	Energy	O
5	Production	B-ORG
6	Corporation	I-ORG
7	(	I-ORG
8	NEPCO	I-ORG
9	)	O
10	11831	B-ORG
11	North	O
12	Creek	O
13	Parkway	O
14	North	O
15	Bothell	O
16	,	B-LOC
17	WA	I-LOC
18	98011	O
19	USA	B-LOC
20	Tel	O
21	:	B-LOC
22	425-415-3052	O
23	Cell	O
24	:	O
25	425-922-0475	O
26	Fax	O
27	:	O
28	425-415-3098	O
29	email	O
30	:	O
31	<	O
32	mailto:galent@nepco.com	O
33	>	O
34	mailto:galen.torneby@nepco.com	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Baker	I-PER
2	Manager	I-PER
3	National	O
4	Energy	O
5	Production	B-ORG
6	Corporation	I-ORG
7	(	I-ORG
8	NEPCO	I-ORG
9	)	O
10	11831	B-ORG
11	North	O
12	Creek	O
13	Parkway	O
14	North	O
15	Bothell	O
16	,	B-LOC
17	WA	I-LOC
18	98011	O
19	USA	B-LOC
20	Tel	O
21	:	B-LOC
22	425-415-3052	O
23	Cell	O
24	:	O
25	425-922-0475	O
26	Fax	O
27	:	O
28	425-415-3098	O
29	email	O
30	:	O
31	<	O
32	mailto:galent@nepco.com	O
33	>	O
34	mailto:galen.torneby@nepco.com	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Williams	I-PER
2	,	O
3	our	O
4	outside	O
5	counsel	O
6	,	O
7	will	O
8	make	O
9	the	O
10	presentation	O
11	on	O
12	our	O
13	behalf	O
14	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Bailey	I-PER
2	,	O
3	our	O
4	outside	O
5	counsel	O
6	,	O
7	will	O
8	make	O
9	the	O
10	presentation	O
11	on	O
12	our	O
13	behalf	O
14	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Gray	I-PER
2	is	O
3	fleshing	O
4	out	O
5	the	O
6	legal	O
7	details	O
8	of	O
9	our	O
10	presentation	O
11	and	O
12	he	O
13	will	O
14	forward	O
15	that	O
16	along	O
17	for	O
18	folks	O
19	review	O
20	later	O
21	today	O
22	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Foster	I-PER
2	is	O
3	fleshing	O
4	out	O
5	the	O
6	legal	O
7	details	O
8	of	O
9	our	O
10	presentation	O
11	and	O
12	he	O
13	will	O
14	forward	O
15	that	O
16	along	O
17	for	O
18	folks	O
19	review	O
20	later	O
21	today	O
22	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Phillips	I-PER
2	,	O
3	our	O
4	outside	O
5	counsel	O
6	,	O
7	will	O
8	make	O
9	the	O
10	presentation	O
11	on	O
12	our	O
13	behalf	O
14	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Brown	I-PER
2	,	O
3	our	O
4	outside	O
5	counsel	O
6	,	O
7	will	O
8	make	O
9	the	O
10	presentation	O
11	on	O
12	our	O
13	behalf	O
14	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Harris	I-PER
2	is	O
3	fleshing	O
4	out	O
5	the	O
6	legal	O
7	details	O
8	of	O
9	our	O
10	presentation	O
11	and	O
12	he	O
13	will	O
14	forward	O
15	that	O
16	along	O
17	for	O
18	folks	O
19	review	O
20	later	O
21	today	O
22	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Evans	I-PER
2	is	O
3	fleshing	O
4	out	O
5	the	O
6	legal	O
7	details	O
8	of	O
9	our	O
10	presentation	O
11	and	O
12	he	O
13	will	O
14	forward	O
15	that	O
16	along	O
17	for	O
18	folks	O
19	review	O
20	later	O
21	today	O
22	.	O

0	Joseph	B-PER

0	Jordan	B-PER

0	Jeff	B-PER
1	-	O

0	Jeff	B-PER
1	-	O

0	The	O
1	price	O
2	spikes	O
3	pose	O
4	real	O
5	political	O
6	risks	O
7	for	O
8	Jack	B-PER
9	and	O
10	he	O
11	and	O
12	his	O
13	folks	O
14	need	O
15	and	O
16	want	O
17	an	O
18	easy	O
19	way	O
20	out	O
21	.	O

0	The	O
1	price	O
2	spikes	O
3	pose	O
4	real	O
5	political	O
6	risks	O
7	for	O
8	Jeremy	B-PER
9	and	O
10	he	O
11	and	O
12	his	O
13	folks	O
14	need	O
15	and	O
16	want	O
17	an	O
18	easy	O
19	way	O
20	out	O
21	.	O

0	On	O
1	my	O
2	panel	O
3	,	O
4	Jennifer	B-PER
5	Richardson	I-PER
6	asked	O
7	Reliant	B-ORG
8	and	O
9	Duke	B-ORG
10	to	O
11	supply	O
12	her	O
13	with	O
14	the	O
15	details	O
16	of	O
17	the	O
18	contracts	O
19	they	O
20	cut	O
21	to	O
22	sell	O
23	their	O
24	power	O
25	forward	O
26	to	O
27	marketers	O
28	.	O

0	On	O
1	my	O
2	panel	O
3	,	O
4	Jessica	B-PER
5	Nelson	I-PER
6	asked	O
7	Reliant	B-ORG
8	and	O
9	Duke	B-ORG
10	to	O
11	supply	O
12	her	O
13	with	O
14	the	O
15	details	O
16	of	O
17	the	O
18	contracts	O
19	they	O
20	cut	O
21	to	O
22	sell	O
23	their	O
24	power	O
25	forward	O
26	to	O
27	marketers	O
28	.	O

0	And	O
1	Michael	B-PER
2	Edwards	I-PER
3	remarks	O
4	were	O
5	extreme	O
6	.	O

0	And	O
1	Christopher	B-PER
2	Young	I-PER
3	remarks	O
4	were	O
5	extreme	O
6	.	O

0	At	O
1	the	O
2	Barton	B-PER
3	hearing	O
4	,	O
5	a	O
6	liberal	O
7	democrat	O
8	(	O
9	Filner	B-PER
10	)	O
11	and	O
12	a	O
13	conservative	O
14	Republican	O
15	(	O
16	Ethan	B-PER
17	)	O
18	locked	O
19	arms	O
20	in	O
21	calling	O
22	for	O
23	refunds	O
24	.	O

0	At	O
1	the	O
2	Barton	B-PER
3	hearing	O
4	,	O
5	a	O
6	liberal	O
7	democrat	O
8	(	O
9	Filner	B-PER
10	)	O
11	and	O
12	a	O
13	conservative	O
14	Republican	O
15	(	O
16	Jacob	B-PER
17	)	O
18	locked	O
19	arms	O
20	in	O
21	calling	O
22	for	O
23	refunds	O
24	.	O

0	You	O
1	're	O
2	right	O
3	,	O
4	Isabella	B-PER
5	.	O

0	You	O
1	're	O
2	right	O
3	,	O
4	Amanda	B-PER
5	.	O

0	Jose	B-PER
1	also	O
2	had	O
3	a	O
4	good	O
5	comment	O
6	---	O
7	do	O
8	n't	O
9	specify	O
10	the	O
11	amount	O
12	of	O
13	rate	O
14	increase	O
15	in	O
16	our	O
17	comments	O
18	;	O
19	rather	O
20	note	O
21	that	O
22	the	O
23	rate	O
24	increase	O
25	needs	O
26	to	O
27	be	O
28	well	O
29	-	O
30	reasoned	O
31	and	O
32	based	O
33	on	O
34	facts	O
35	and	O
36	evidence	O
37	.	O

0	Nicholas	B-PER
1	also	O
2	had	O
3	a	O
4	good	O
5	comment	O
6	---	O
7	do	O
8	n't	O
9	specify	O
10	the	O
11	amount	O
12	of	O
13	rate	O
14	increase	O
15	in	O
16	our	O
17	comments	O
18	;	O
19	rather	O
20	note	O
21	that	O
22	the	O
23	rate	O
24	increase	O
25	needs	O
26	to	O
27	be	O
28	well	O
29	-	O
30	reasoned	O
31	and	O
32	based	O
33	on	O
34	facts	O
35	and	O
36	evidence	O
37	.	O

0	"	O
1	Jennifer	B-PER
2	Diaz	I-PER
3	"	O
4	<	O
5	kaplan@iepa.com	O
6	>	O

0	"	O
1	Jessica	B-PER
2	Myers	I-PER
3	"	O
4	<	O
5	kaplan@iepa.com	O
6	>	O

0	IEP	B-ORG
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	hosting	O
4	a	O
5	dinner	O
6	for	O
7	California	B-LOC
8	Governor	O
9	Michael	B-PER
10	Cooper	I-PER
11	on	O
12	Thursday	O
13	,	O
14	December	O
15	7	O
16	,	O
17	2000	O
18	at	O
19	the	O
20	historic	O
21	Julia	B-LOC
22	Morgan	I-LOC
23	House	I-LOC
24	in	O
25	Sacramento	B-LOC
26	.	O

0	IEP	B-ORG
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	hosting	O
4	a	O
5	dinner	O
6	for	O
7	California	B-LOC
8	Governor	O
9	Christopher	B-PER
10	Cruz	I-PER
11	on	O
12	Thursday	O
13	,	O
14	December	O
15	7	O
16	,	O
17	2000	O
18	at	O
19	the	O
20	historic	O
21	Julia	B-LOC
22	Morgan	I-LOC
23	House	I-LOC
24	in	O
25	Sacramento	B-LOC
26	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Anderson	I-PER
2	Manager	O
3	of	O
4	Policy	O
5	IEP	B-ORG
6	(	O
7	916	O
8	)	O
9	448-9499	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Moore	I-PER
2	Manager	O
3	of	O
4	Policy	O
5	IEP	B-ORG
6	(	O
7	916	O
8	)	O
9	448-9499	O

0	Travis	B-PER

0	Stephen	B-PER

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	glad	O
3	they	O
4	want	O
5	to	O
6	follow	O
7	-	O
8	up	O
9	with	O
10	Kenneth	B-PER
11	(	O
12	I	O
13	've	O
14	been	O
15	pushing	O
16	it	O
17	)	O
18	and	O
19	I	O
20	've	O
21	got	O
22	some	O
23	follow	O
24	-	O
25	up	O
26	as	O
27	well	O
28	based	O
29	on	O
30	chats	O
31	I	O
32	had	O
33	in	O
34	the	O
35	afternoon	O
36	on	O
37	Friday	O
38	with	O
39	folks	O
40	post-call	O
41	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	glad	O
3	they	O
4	want	O
5	to	O
6	follow	O
7	-	O
8	up	O
9	with	O
10	Jack	B-PER
11	(	O
12	I	O
13	've	O
14	been	O
15	pushing	O
16	it	O
17	)	O
18	and	O
19	I	O
20	've	O
21	got	O
22	some	O
23	follow	O
24	-	O
25	up	O
26	as	O
27	well	O
28	based	O
29	on	O
30	chats	O
31	I	O
32	had	O
33	in	O
34	the	O
35	afternoon	O
36	on	O
37	Friday	O
38	with	O
39	folks	O
40	post-call	O
41	.	O

0	Nathan	B-PER

0	Kenneth	B-PER

0	Jeremy	B-PER
1	Meier	I-PER
2	<	O
3	jermeier@earthlink.net	O
4	>	O

0	Jeremy	B-PER
1	Meier	I-PER
2	<	O
3	jermeier@earthlink.net	O
4	>	O

0	Aaron	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Isaiah	B-PER
1	:	O

0	FYI	O
1	,	O
2	we	O
3	had	O
4	an	O
5	instructive	O
6	rest	O
7	of	O
8	the	O
9	conference	O
10	call	O
11	on	O
12	Friday	O
13	with	O
14	Julia	B-PER
15	and	O
16	Robbie	B-PER
17	et	O
18	al	O
19	.	O

0	FYI	O
1	,	O
2	we	O
3	had	O
4	an	O
5	instructive	O
6	rest	O
7	of	O
8	the	O
9	conference	O
10	call	O
11	on	O
12	Friday	O
13	with	O
14	Jamie	B-PER
15	and	O
16	Robbie	B-PER
17	et	O
18	al	O
19	.	O

0	They	O
1	indicated	O
2	they	O
3	could	O
4	use	O
5	Anthony	B-PER
6	's	O
7	help	O
8	face	O
9	to	O
10	face	O
11	at	O
12	some	O
13	point	O
14	.	O

0	They	O
1	indicated	O
2	they	O
3	could	O
4	use	O
5	Joseph	B-PER
6	's	O
7	help	O
8	face	O
9	to	O
10	face	O
11	at	O
12	some	O
13	point	O
14	.	O

0	We	O
1	are	O
2	following	O
3	up	O
4	with	O
5	Shannon	B-PER
6	and	O
7	Robbie	B-PER
8	on	O
9	a	O
10	couple	O
11	legal	O
12	issues	O
13	,	O
14	case	O
15	law	O
16	and	O
17	MSA	O
18	self	O
19	-	O
20	certification	O
21	language	O
22	,	O
23	and	O
24	let	O
25	me	O
26	know	O
27	if	O
28	you	O
29	have	O
30	additional	O
31	items	O
32	.	O

0	We	O
1	are	O
2	following	O
3	up	O
4	with	O
5	Sue	B-PER
6	and	O
7	Jackson	B-PER
8	on	O
9	a	O
10	couple	O
11	legal	O
12	issues	O
13	,	O
14	case	O
15	law	O
16	and	O
17	MSA	O
18	self	O
19	-	O
20	certification	O
21	language	O
22	,	O
23	and	O
24	let	O
25	me	O
26	know	O
27	if	O
28	you	O
29	have	O
30	additional	O
31	items	O
32	.	O

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	can	O
3	you	O
4	confirm	O
5	the	O
6	correct	O
7	names	O
8	,	O
9	email	O
10	addresses	O
11	,	O
12	titles	O
13	for	O
14	those	O
15	new	O
16	folks	O
17	on	O
18	Friday	O
19	's	O
20	call	O
21	:	O
22	Michael	B-PER
23	Jackson	B-PER
24	,	O
25	Michelle	B-PER
26	,	O
27	Melissa	B-PER
28	Lloyd	I-PER
29	?	O

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	can	O
3	you	O
4	confirm	O
5	the	O
6	correct	O
7	names	O
8	,	O
9	email	O
10	addresses	O
11	,	O
12	titles	O
13	for	O
14	those	O
15	new	O
16	folks	O
17	on	O
18	Friday	O
19	's	O
20	call	O
21	:	O
22	Robbie	B-PER
23	Rossi	B-PER
24	,	O
25	Michelle	B-PER
26	,	O
27	Melissa	B-PER
28	Lloyd	I-PER
29	?	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Wilson	I-PER
2	&	B-ORG
3	Cohen	I-ORG

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Howard	I-PER
2	&	B-ORG
3	Cohen	I-ORG

0	Julia	B-PER
1	Leibman@ENRON	I-PER
2	COMMUNICATIONS	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Leibman@ENRON	I-PER
2	COMMUNICATIONS	O

0	Travis	B-PER
1	,	O
2	your	O
3	access	O
4	code	O
5	(	O
6	room	O
7	4434	O
8	)	O
9	after	O
10	dialing	O
11	the	O
12	toll	O
13	free	O
14	number	O
15	will	O
16	be	O
17	857-771	O
18	.	O

0	Joshua	B-PER
1	,	O
2	your	O
3	access	O
4	code	O
5	(	O
6	room	O
7	4434	O
8	)	O
9	after	O
10	dialing	O
11	the	O
12	toll	O
13	free	O
14	number	O
15	will	O
16	be	O
17	857-771	O
18	.	O

0	Goal	O
1	is	O
2	to	O
3	(	O
4	politely	O
5	?	O
6	)	O
7	refute	O
8	Jennifer	B-PER
9	Wood	I-PER
10	and	O
11	Carl	O
12	Woods	B-PER
13	'	I-PER
14	continued	O
15	assertions	O
16	that	O
17	1	O
18	)	O
19	California	O
20	's	B-LOC
21	move	O
22	to	O
23	deregulate	O
24	was	O
25	based	O
26	solely	O
27	on	O
28	ideology	O
29	with	O
30	no	O
31	basis	O
32	in	O
33	fact	O
34	and	O
35	2	O
36	)	O
37	the	O
38	solution	O
39	is	O
40	to	O
41	turn	O
42	back	O
43	the	O
44	clock	O
45	to	O
46	command	O
47	-	O
48	and	O
49	-	O
50	control	O
51	regulation	O
52	.	O

0	Goal	O
1	is	O
2	to	O
3	(	O
4	politely	O
5	?	O
6	)	O
7	refute	O
8	Loretta	B-PER
9	Lynch	I-PER
10	's	O
11	and	O
12	Christopher	B-PER
13	Evans	I-PER
14	'	O
15	continued	O
16	assertions	O
17	that	O
18	1	O
19	)	O
20	California	B-LOC
21	's	O
22	move	O
23	to	O
24	deregulate	O
25	was	O
26	based	O
27	solely	O
28	on	O
29	ideology	O
30	with	O
31	no	O
32	basis	O
33	in	O
34	fact	O
35	and	O
36	2	O
37	)	O
38	the	O
39	solution	O
40	is	O
41	to	O
42	turn	O
43	back	O
44	the	O
45	clock	O
46	to	O
47	command	O
48	-	O
49	and	O
50	-	O
51	control	O
52	regulation	O
53	.	O

0	Austin	B-PER

0	Edward	B-PER

0	Travis	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Lucas	B-PER
1	:	O

0	As	O
1	we	O
2	discussed	O
3	yesterday	O
4	,	O
5	Steven	B-PER
6	and	O
7	I	O
8	spoke	O
9	and	O
10	we	O
11	think	O
12	that	O
13	the	O
14	presentation	O
15	is	O
16	good	O
17	to	O
18	go	O
19	for	O
20	Thursday	O
21	.	O

0	As	O
1	we	O
2	discussed	O
3	yesterday	O
4	,	O
5	David	B-PER
6	and	O
7	I	O
8	spoke	O
9	and	O
10	we	O
11	think	O
12	that	O
13	the	O
14	presentation	O
15	is	O
16	good	O
17	to	O
18	go	O
19	for	O
20	Thursday	O
21	.	O

0	Brandon	B-PER

0	Aiden	B-PER

0	Isaac	B-PER

0	Adam	B-PER

0	George	B-PER

0	Dustin	B-PER

0	By	O
1	Savannah	B-PER
2	KINDY	I-PER

0	By	O
1	Jacqueline	B-PER
2	KINDY	I-PER

0	The	O
1	investigative	O
2	committee	O
3	,	O
4	headed	O
5	by	O
6	state	O
7	Sen.	O
8	Michael	B-PER
9	Myers	I-PER
10	,	O
11	D	O
12	-	O
13	Santa	B-LOC
14	Ana	I-LOC
15	,	O
16	is	O
17	focusing	O
18	on	O
19	a	O
20	series	O
21	of	O
22	events	O
23	last	O
24	fall	O
25	filled	O
26	with	O
27	enough	O
28	Shakespearean	O
29	plot	O
30	twists	O
31	and	O
32	intrigue	O
33	that	O
34	it	O
35	has	O
36	earned	O
37	a	O
38	name	O
39	around	O
40	the	O
41	Capitol	O
42	:	O
43	"	O
44	the	O
45	palace	O
46	coup	O
47	.	O
48	"	O

0	The	O
1	investigative	O
2	committee	O
3	,	O
4	headed	O
5	by	O
6	state	O
7	Sen.	O
8	Christopher	B-PER
9	Sullivan	I-PER
10	,	O
11	D	O
12	-	O
13	Santa	B-LOC
14	Ana	I-LOC
15	,	O
16	is	O
17	focusing	O
18	on	O
19	a	O
20	series	O
21	of	O
22	events	O
23	last	O
24	fall	O
25	filled	O
26	with	O
27	enough	O
28	Shakespearean	O
29	plot	O
30	twists	O
31	and	O
32	intrigue	O
33	that	O
34	it	O
35	has	O
36	earned	O
37	a	O
38	name	O
39	around	O
40	the	O
41	Capitol	O
42	:	O
43	"	O
44	the	O
45	palace	O
46	coup	O
47	.	O
48	"	O

0	The	O
1	central	O
2	question	O
3	behind	O
4	the	O
5	palace	O
6	coup	O
7	is	O
8	whether	O
9	Michael	B-PER
10	Allen	I-PER
11	,	O
12	the	O
13	president	O
14	of	O
15	the	O
16	Independent	B-ORG
17	System	I-ORG
18	Operator	I-ORG
19	,	O
20	acted	O
21	alone	O
22	when	O
23	he	O
24	took	O
25	steps	O
26	to	O
27	remove	O
28	key	O
29	price	O
30	caps	O
31	designed	O
32	to	O
33	limit	O
34	the	O
35	amount	O
36	power	O
37	generators	O
38	could	O
39	charge	O
40	.	O

0	The	O
1	central	O
2	question	O
3	behind	O
4	the	O
5	palace	O
6	coup	O
7	is	O
8	whether	O
9	Christopher	B-PER
10	Wood	I-PER
11	,	O
12	the	O
13	president	O
14	of	O
15	the	O
16	Independent	B-ORG
17	System	I-ORG
18	Operator	I-ORG
19	,	O
20	acted	O
21	alone	O
22	when	O
23	he	O
24	took	O
25	steps	O
26	to	O
27	remove	O
28	key	O
29	price	O
30	caps	O
31	designed	O
32	to	O
33	limit	O
34	the	O
35	amount	O
36	power	O
37	generators	O
38	could	O
39	charge	O
40	.	O

0	Winter	B-PER
1	defied	O
2	his	O
3	own	O
4	board	O
5	and	O
6	Gov.	O
7	Michael	B-PER
8	Roberts	I-PER
9	when	O
10	he	O
11	filed	O
12	a	O
13	50	O
14	-	O
15	page	O
16	request	O
17	to	O
18	remove	O
19	the	O
20	caps	O
21	,	O
22	records	O
23	and	O
24	interviews	O
25	show	O
26	.	O

0	Winter	B-PER
1	defied	O
2	his	O
3	own	O
4	board	O
5	and	O
6	Gov.	O
7	Christopher	B-PER
8	Phillips	I-PER
9	when	O
10	he	O
11	filed	O
12	a	O
13	50	O
14	-	O
15	page	O
16	request	O
17	to	O
18	remove	O
19	the	O
20	caps	O
21	,	O
22	records	O
23	and	O
24	interviews	O
25	show	O
26	.	O

0	Peter	B-PER
1	spokesman	O
2	Steve	B-PER
3	Maviglio	I-PER
4	said	O
5	the	O
6	governor	O
7	felt	O
8	"	O
9	betrayed	O
10	"	O
11	by	O
12	the	O
13	actions	O
14	of	O
15	Winter	B-PER
16	.	O

0	Jesse	B-PER
1	spokesman	O
2	Steve	B-PER
3	Maviglio	I-PER
4	said	O
5	the	O
6	governor	O
7	felt	O
8	"	O
9	betrayed	O
10	"	O
11	by	O
12	the	O
13	actions	O
14	of	O
15	Winter	B-PER
16	.	O

0	ISO	B-ORG
1	spokesman	O
2	Michael	B-PER
3	Kelly	I-PER
4	said	O
5	Dunn	B-PER
6	's	O
7	committee	O
8	will	O
9	find	O
10	no	O
11	criminal	O
12	conduct	O
13	.	O

0	ISO	B-ORG
1	spokesman	O
2	Christopher	B-PER
3	Anderson	I-PER
4	said	O
5	Dunn	B-PER
6	's	O
7	committee	O
8	will	O
9	find	O
10	no	O
11	criminal	O
12	conduct	O
13	.	O

0	"	O
1	If	O
2	not	O
3	removed	O
4	immediately	O
5	,	O
6	the	O
7	(	O
8	ISO	B-ORG
9	)	O
10	price	O
11	cap	O
12	will	O
13	sow	O
14	confusion	O
15	in	O
16	the	O
17	market	O
18	,	O
19	threaten	O
20	reliability	O
21	and	O
22	stifle	O
23	new	O
24	investment	O
25	in	O
26	generating	O
27	capacity	O
28	,	O
29	''	O
30	read	O
31	one	O
32	letter	O
33	written	O
34	by	O
35	Duke	B-ORG
36	Energy	I-ORG
37	Vice	O
38	President	O
39	Michael	B-PER
40	Wood	I-PER
41	.	I-PER

0	"	O
1	If	O
2	not	O
3	removed	O
4	immediately	O
5	,	O
6	the	O
7	(	O
8	ISO	B-ORG
9	)	O
10	price	O
11	cap	O
12	will	O
13	sow	O
14	confusion	O
15	in	O
16	the	O
17	market	O
18	,	O
19	threaten	O
20	reliability	O
21	and	O
22	stifle	O
23	new	O
24	investment	O
25	in	O
26	generating	O
27	capacity	O
28	,	O
29	''	O
30	read	O
31	one	O
32	letter	O
33	written	O
34	by	O
35	Duke	B-ORG
36	Energy	I-ORG
37	Vice	O
38	President	O
39	Christopher	B-PER
40	Wilson	I-PER
41	.	I-PER

0	In	O
1	fact	O
2	,	O
3	the	O
4	attorney	O
5	who	O
6	helped	O
7	draft	O
8	the	O
9	emergency	O
10	request	O
11	,	O
12	Michael	B-PER
13	Ramirez	I-PER
14	,	O
15	was	O
16	in	O
17	a	O
18	meeting	O
19	with	O
20	representatives	O
21	of	O
22	the	O
23	governor	O
24	and	O
25	ISO	B-ORG
26	board	O
27	members	O
28	just	O
29	hours	O
30	before	O
31	the	O
32	filing	O
33	was	O
34	made	O
35	.	O

0	In	O
1	fact	O
2	,	O
3	the	O
4	attorney	O
5	who	O
6	helped	O
7	draft	O
8	the	O
9	emergency	O
10	request	O
11	,	O
12	Christopher	B-PER
13	Collins	I-PER
14	,	O
15	was	O
16	in	O
17	a	O
18	meeting	O
19	with	O
20	representatives	O
21	of	O
22	the	O
23	governor	O
24	and	O
25	ISO	B-ORG
26	board	O
27	members	O
28	just	O
29	hours	O
30	before	O
31	the	O
32	filing	O
33	was	O
34	made	O
35	.	O

0	"	O
1	In	O
2	retrospect	O
3	,	O
4	we	O
5	should	O
6	have	O
7	told	O
8	them	O
9	,	O
10	''	O
11	Travis	B-PER
12	said	O
13	.	O

0	"	O
1	In	O
2	retrospect	O
3	,	O
4	we	O
5	should	O
6	have	O
7	told	O
8	them	O
9	,	O
10	''	O
11	Tyler	B-PER
12	said	O
13	.	O

0	Jack	B-PER
1	said	O
2	the	O
3	filing	O
4	-	O
5	granted	O
6	two	O
7	hours	O
8	after	O
9	the	O
10	request	O
11	-	O
12	helped	O
13	rather	O
14	than	O
15	hurt	O
16	Californians	O
17	.	O

0	Alexander	B-PER
1	said	O
2	the	O
3	filing	O
4	-	O
5	granted	O
6	two	O
7	hours	O
8	after	O
9	the	O
10	request	O
11	-	O
12	helped	O
13	rather	O
14	than	O
15	hurt	O
16	Californians	O
17	.	O

0	Evan	B-PER
1	said	O
2	the	O
3	emergency	O
4	order	O
5	allowed	O
6	the	O
7	ISO	B-ORG
8	to	O
9	secure	O
10	refunds	O
11	should	O
12	overcharges	O
13	for	O
14	electricity	O
15	be	O
16	proven	O
17	to	O
18	federal	O
19	officials	O
20	.	O

0	Jeffrey	B-PER
1	said	O
2	the	O
3	emergency	O
4	order	O
5	allowed	O
6	the	O
7	ISO	B-ORG
8	to	O
9	secure	O
10	refunds	O
11	should	O
12	overcharges	O
13	for	O
14	electricity	O
15	be	O
16	proven	O
17	to	O
18	federal	O
19	officials	O
20	.	O

0	"	O
1	We	O
2	believe	O
3	the	O
4	action	O
5	we	O
6	took	O
7	addressed	O
8	a	O
9	severe	O
10	concern	O
11	,	O
12	''	O
13	Nathaniel	B-PER
14	said	O
15	.	O

0	"	O
1	We	O
2	believe	O
3	the	O
4	action	O
5	we	O
6	took	O
7	addressed	O
8	a	O
9	severe	O
10	concern	O
11	,	O
12	''	O
13	Mason	B-PER
14	said	O
15	.	O

0	"	O
1	Nathan	B-PER
2	did	O
3	this	O
4	by	O
5	himself	O
6	,	O
7	''	O
8	said	O
9	Smutney	B-PER
10	-	I-PER
11	Jones	I-PER
12	,	O
13	executive	O
14	director	O
15	of	O
16	the	O
17	Independent	B-ORG
18	Energy	I-ORG
19	Producers	I-ORG
20	.	O

0	"	O
1	Connor	B-PER
2	did	O
3	this	O
4	by	O
5	himself	O
6	,	O
7	''	O
8	said	O
9	Smutney	B-PER
10	-	I-PER
11	Jones	I-PER
12	,	O
13	executive	O
14	director	O
15	of	O
16	the	O
17	Independent	B-ORG
18	Energy	I-ORG
19	Producers	I-ORG
20	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Carter	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	the	O
4	former	O
5	Federal	O
6	Energy	B-ORG
7	Regulatory	I-ORG
8	Commission	I-ORG
9	chairman	I-ORG
10	,	O
11	defended	O
12	making	O
13	the	O
14	December	O
15	decision	O
16	and	O
17	also	O
18	defended	O
19	Winter	O
20	.	B-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Allen	I-PER
2	,	I-PER
3	the	O
4	former	O
5	Federal	O
6	Energy	B-ORG
7	Regulatory	I-ORG
8	Commission	I-ORG
9	chairman	I-ORG
10	,	O
11	defended	O
12	making	O
13	the	O
14	December	O
15	decision	O
16	and	O
17	also	O
18	defended	O
19	Winter	O
20	.	B-PER

0	"	O
1	Dustin	B-PER
2	said	O
3	he	O
4	made	O
5	that	O
6	filing	O
7	in	O
8	the	O
9	interest	O
10	of	O
11	Californians	O
12	,	O
13	but	O
14	I	O
15	find	O
16	that	O
17	argument	O
18	has	O
19	no	O
20	basis	O
21	in	O
22	fact	O
23	.	O
24	''	O

0	"	O
1	Nathaniel	B-PER
2	said	O
3	he	O
4	made	O
5	that	O
6	filing	O
7	in	O
8	the	O
9	interest	O
10	of	O
11	Californians	O
12	,	O
13	but	O
14	I	O
15	find	O
16	that	O
17	argument	O
18	has	O
19	no	O
20	basis	O
21	in	O
22	fact	O
23	.	O
24	''	O

0	We	O
1	should	O
2	resurrect	O
3	Michael	B-PER
4	Gray	I-PER
5	note	O
6	and	O
7	get	O
8	him	O
9	on	O
10	the	O
11	call	O
12	in	O
13	the	O
14	attempt	O
15	to	O
16	avoid	O
17	recreating	O
18	the	O
19	wheel	O
20	on	O
21	this	O
22	one	O
23	.	O

0	We	O
1	should	O
2	resurrect	O
3	Christopher	B-PER
4	Morgan	I-PER
5	note	O
6	and	O
7	get	O
8	him	O
9	on	O
10	the	O
11	call	O
12	in	O
13	the	O
14	attempt	O
15	to	O
16	avoid	O
17	recreating	O
18	the	O
19	wheel	O
20	on	O
21	this	O
22	one	O
23	.	O

0	Rebecca	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Jeff	B-PER
3	--	O

0	Isabella	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Jeff	B-PER
3	--	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	having	O
3	a	O
4	meeting	O
5	with	O
6	Taylor	B-PER
7	and	O
8	Janet	B-PER
9	Dietrich	I-PER
10	on	O
11	Thursday	O
12	to	O
13	discuss	O
14	our	O
15	view	O
16	on	O
17	the	O
18	ability	O
19	to	O
20	extend	O
21	our	O
22	current	O
23	contracts	O
24	in	O
25	CA	B-PER
26	(	O
27	for	O
28	customers	O
29	already	O
30	on	O
31	DA	O
32	)	O
33	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	having	O
3	a	O
4	meeting	O
5	with	O
6	Vicki	B-PER
7	and	O
8	Jessica	B-PER
9	Perez	I-PER
10	on	O
11	Thursday	O
12	to	O
13	discuss	O
14	our	O
15	view	O
16	on	O
17	the	O
18	ability	O
19	to	O
20	extend	O
21	our	O
22	current	O
23	contracts	O
24	in	O
25	CA	B-PER
26	(	O
27	for	O
28	customers	O
29	already	O
30	on	O
31	DA	O
32	)	O
33	.	O

0	I	O
1	'll	O
2	leave	O
3	to	O
4	Zachary	B-PER
5	to	O
6	structure	O
7	the	O
8	deal	O
9	.	O

0	I	O
1	'll	O
2	leave	O
3	to	O
4	Peter	B-PER
5	to	O
6	structure	O
7	the	O
8	deal	O
9	.	O

0	Robert	B-PER

0	Nathaniel	B-PER

0	Evan	B-PER

0	Luis	B-PER

0	Justin	B-PER

0	Gregory	B-PER

0	Daniel	B-PER

0	Brian	B-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Brown	I-PER
2	<	O
3	Michael.McDermott@spectrongroup.com	O
4	>	O
5	on	O
6	06/01/2000	O
7	06:00:56	O
8	AM	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Sanders	I-PER
2	<	O
3	Michael.McDermott@spectrongroup.com	O
4	>	O
5	on	O
6	06/01/2000	O
7	06:00:56	O
8	AM	O

0	Expect	O
1	a	O
2	call	O
3	from	O
4	Carlos	B-PER
5	tonight	O
6	.	O

0	Expect	O
1	a	O
2	call	O
3	from	O
4	Kenneth	B-PER
5	tonight	O
6	.	O

0	Angel	B-PER

0	Patrick	B-PER

0	I	O
1	told	O
2	Jeremy	B-PER
3	that	O
4	you	O
5	called	O
6	him	O
7	yesterday	O
8	so	O
9	abruptly	O
10	because	O
11	you	O
12	did	O
13	n't	O
14	want	O
15	to	O
16	waste	O
17	his	O
18	time	O
19	while	O
20	you	O
21	got	O
22	tests	O
23	done	O
24	for	O
25	arthritis	O
26	.	O

0	I	O
1	told	O
2	Jonathan	B-PER
3	that	O
4	you	O
5	called	O
6	him	O
7	yesterday	O
8	so	O
9	abruptly	O
10	because	O
11	you	O
12	did	O
13	n't	O
14	want	O
15	to	O
16	waste	O
17	his	O
18	time	O
19	while	O
20	you	O
21	got	O
22	tests	O
23	done	O
24	for	O
25	arthritis	O
26	.	O

0	Isaac	B-PER

0	Michael	B-PER

0	Is	O
1	that	O
2	Microwave	O
3	that	O
4	you	O
5	gave	O
6	Nicholas	B-PER
7	really	O
8	expensive	O
9	?	O

0	Is	O
1	that	O
2	Microwave	O
3	that	O
4	you	O
5	gave	O
6	Jackson	B-PER
7	really	O
8	expensive	O
9	?	O

0	Charles	B-PER

0	Richard	B-PER

0	Gabriel	B-PER

0	Richard	B-PER

0	Melanie	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Abigail	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Jordan	B-PER

0	John	B-PER

0	Hunter	B-PER

0	Caleb	B-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	called	O
2	me	O
3	today	O
4	.	O

0	Travis	B-PER
1	called	O
2	me	O
3	today	O
4	.	O

0	Jack	B-PER

0	Sean	B-PER

0	Alex	B-PER

0	Caleb	B-PER

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	n't	O
3	get	O
4	a	O
5	chance	O
6	to	O
7	talk	O
8	to	O
9	Shawn	B-PER
10	today	O
11	.	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	n't	O
3	get	O
4	a	O
5	chance	O
6	to	O
7	talk	O
8	to	O
9	Luke	B-PER
10	today	O
11	.	O

0	Steven	B-PER

0	Bradley	B-PER

0	Ian	O

0	Isaiah	O

0	Jackson	B-PER

0	Adrian	B-PER

0	Gregory	B-PER
1	is	O
2	really	O
3	smart	O
4	and	O
5	a	O
6	hard	O
7	worker	O
8	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	is	O
2	really	O
3	smart	O
4	and	O
5	a	O
6	hard	O
7	worker	O
8	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER

0	William	B-PER

0	Charles	B-PER
1	is	O
2	out	O
3	of	O
4	the	O
5	office	O
6	today	O
7	so	O
8	I	O
9	have	O
10	n't	O
11	had	O
12	a	O
13	chance	O
14	to	O
15	talk	O
16	to	O
17	him	O
18	.	O

0	Aiden	B-PER
1	is	O
2	out	O
3	of	O
4	the	O
5	office	O
6	today	O
7	so	O
8	I	O
9	have	O
10	n't	O
11	had	O
12	a	O
13	chance	O
14	to	O
15	talk	O
16	to	O
17	him	O
18	.	O

0	Dustin	B-PER

0	Joshua	B-PER

0	Should	O
1	I	O
2	send	O
3	the	O
4	resume	O
5	to	O
6	Monica	B-PER
7	or	O
8	you	O
9	directly	O
10	?	O

0	Should	O
1	I	O
2	send	O
3	the	O
4	resume	O
5	to	O
6	Michelle	B-PER
7	or	O
8	you	O
9	directly	O
10	?	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Rogers	I-PER
2	-	O
3	Director	O
4	416-865-3703	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Rogers	I-PER
2	-	O
3	Director	O
4	416-865-3703	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Hughes	I-PER
2	-	O
3	Manager	O
4	416-865-3704	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Hughes	I-PER
2	-	O
3	Manager	O
4	416-865-3704	O

0	Aiden	B-PER

0	Ryan	B-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Brown	I-PER
2	says	O
3	high	O
4	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Evans	I-PER
2	says	O
3	high	O
4	.	O

0	Justin	B-PER

0	Benjamin	B-PER

0	Benjamin	B-PER

0	Ryan	B-PER

0	Tracy	B-PER

0	Alexandra	B-PER

0	WHAT	O
1	:	O
2	Happy	O
3	Hour	O
4	for	O
5	Michael	B-PER
6	Young	I-PER

0	WHAT	O
1	:	O
2	Happy	O
3	Hour	O
4	for	O
5	Christopher	B-PER
6	Hill	I-PER

0	WHY	O
1	:	O
2	Today	O
3	is	O
4	Juan	B-PER
5	's	O
6	last	O
7	day	O
8	at	O
9	EBS	O
10	.	O

0	WHY	O
1	:	O
2	Today	O
3	is	O
4	Scott	B-PER
5	's	O
6	last	O
7	day	O
8	at	O
9	EBS	O
10	.	O

0	Morgan	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Leon	B-PER
3	have	O
4	proposed	O
5	xferring	O
6	Co.	O
7	1691	O
8	to	O
9	your	O
10	world	O
11	(	O
12	see	O
13	below	O
14	)	O
15	.	O

0	Cynthia	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Leon	B-PER
3	have	O
4	proposed	O
5	xferring	O
6	Co.	O
7	1691	O
8	to	O
9	your	O
10	world	O
11	(	O
12	see	O
13	below	O
14	)	O
15	.	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	have	O
3	not	O
4	already	O
5	made	O
6	these	O
7	decisions	O
8	,	O
9	Lauren	B-PER
10	's	O
11	guidance	O
12	should	O
13	be	O
14	helpful	O
15	.	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	have	O
3	not	O
4	already	O
5	made	O
6	these	O
7	decisions	O
8	,	O
9	Monica	B-PER
10	's	O
11	guidance	O
12	should	O
13	be	O
14	helpful	O
15	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Lopez	I-PER
2	Tax	O
3	x35172	O
4	EB	O
5	1774	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Thomas	I-PER
2	Tax	O
3	x35172	O
4	EB	O
5	1774	O

0	Jamie	B-PER

0	Kristen	B-PER

0	Hailey	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Amanda	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Erica	B-PER

0	Brooke	B-PER

0	So	O
1	I	O
2	suggest	O
3	it	O
4	be	O
5	assigned	O
6	to	O
7	Alex	B-PER
8	.	O

0	So	O
1	I	O
2	suggest	O
3	it	O
4	be	O
5	assigned	O
6	to	O
7	Kyle	B-PER
8	.	O

0	I	O
1	think	O
2	this	O
3	could	O
4	go	O
5	to	O
6	either	O
7	Holding	O
8	/	O
9	Administrative	O
10	Companies	O
11	(	O
12	Same	O
13	as	O
14	17H	O
15	)	O
16	or	O
17	Network	O
18	&	O
19	Services	O
20	(	O
21	Mason	B-PER
22	)	O
23	.	O

0	I	O
1	think	O
2	this	O
3	could	O
4	go	O
5	to	O
6	either	O
7	Holding	O
8	/	O
9	Administrative	O
10	Companies	O
11	(	O
12	Same	O
13	as	O
14	17H	O
15	)	O
16	or	O
17	Network	O
18	&	O
19	Services	O
20	(	O
21	James	B-PER
22	)	O
23	.	O

0	A	O
1	similar	O
2	entity	O
3	(	O
4	1179	O
5	)	O
6	was	O
7	assigned	O
8	to	O
9	Commodity	O
10	and	O
11	Trade	O
12	(	O
13	Todd	B-PER
14	Richards	I-PER
15	and	O
16	Jennifer	B-PER
17	Ramirez	I-PER
18	)	O
19	so	O
20	this	O
21	one	O
22	should	O
23	be	O
24	assigned	O
25	to	O
26	them	O
27	as	O
28	well	O
29	.	O

0	A	O
1	similar	O
2	entity	O
3	(	O
4	1179	O
5	)	O
6	was	O
7	assigned	O
8	to	O
9	Commodity	O
10	and	O
11	Trade	O
12	(	O
13	Todd	B-PER
14	Richards	I-PER
15	and	O
16	Jessica	B-PER
17	Ramirez	I-PER
18	)	O
19	so	O
20	this	O
21	one	O
22	should	O
23	be	O
24	assigned	O
25	to	O
26	them	O
27	as	O
28	well	O
29	.	O

0	Cherokee	B-ORG
1	Finance	I-ORG
2	VOF	I-ORG
3	is	O
4	assigned	O
5	to	O
6	North	B-LOC
7	America	I-LOC
8	(	O
9	Glen	B-PER
10	Walloch	I-PER
11	and	O
12	Michael	B-PER
13	Cooper	I-PER
14	)	O
15	.	O

0	Cherokee	B-ORG
1	Finance	I-ORG
2	VOF	I-ORG
3	is	O
4	assigned	O
5	to	O
6	North	B-LOC
7	America	I-LOC
8	(	O
9	Glen	B-PER
10	Walloch	I-PER
11	and	O
12	Christopher	B-PER
13	Gomez	I-PER
14	)	O
15	.	O

0	It	O
1	should	O
2	be	O
3	assigned	O
4	to	O
5	North	B-LOC
6	America	I-LOC
7	(	O
8	Glen	B-PER
9	Walloch	I-PER
10	and	O
11	Michael	B-PER
12	Williams	I-PER
13	)	O
14	.	O

0	It	O
1	should	O
2	be	O
3	assigned	O
4	to	O
5	North	B-LOC
6	America	I-LOC
7	(	O
8	Glen	B-PER
9	Walloch	I-PER
10	and	O
11	Christopher	B-PER
12	White	I-PER
13	)	O
14	.	O

0	Erica	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Leon	B-PER
3	have	O
4	proposed	O
5	xferring	O
6	Co.	O
7	1691	O
8	to	O
9	your	O
10	world	O
11	(	O
12	see	O
13	below	O
14	)	O
15	.	O

0	Essie	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Noah	B-PER
3	have	O
4	proposed	O
5	xferring	O
6	Co.	O
7	1691	O
8	to	O
9	your	O
10	world	O
11	(	O
12	see	O
13	below	O
14	)	O
15	.	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	have	O
3	not	O
4	already	O
5	made	O
6	these	O
7	decisions	O
8	,	O
9	Anna	B-PER
10	's	O
11	guidance	O
12	should	O
13	be	O
14	helpful	O
15	.	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	have	O
3	not	O
4	already	O
5	made	O
6	these	O
7	decisions	O
8	,	O
9	Taylor	B-PER
10	's	O
11	guidance	O
12	should	O
13	be	O
14	helpful	O
15	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Adams	I-PER
2	Tax	O
3	x35172	O
4	EB	O
5	1774	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Wilson	I-PER
2	Tax	O
3	x35172	O
4	EB	O
5	1774	O

0	Leslie	B-PER

0	Catherine	B-PER

0	Rachel	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Tracy	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Leah	B-PER

0	Katherine	B-PER

0	Ryan	B-PER
1	,	O
2	this	O
3	is	O
4	the	O
5	issue	O
6	I	O
7	left	O
8	you	O
9	the	O
10	voice	O
11	mail	O
12	on	O
13	.	O

0	Tyler	B-PER
1	,	O
2	this	O
3	is	O
4	the	O
5	issue	O
6	I	O
7	left	O
8	you	O
9	the	O
10	voice	O
11	mail	O
12	on	O
13	.	O

0	We	O
1	will	O
2	fight	O
3	with	O
4	them	O
5	about	O
6	who	O
7	owes	O
8	the	O
9	$	O
10	200	O
11	k	O
12	that	O
13	Aaron	B-PER
14	mentions	O
15	below	O
16	based	O
17	on	O
18	their	O
19	failure	O
20	to	O
21	"	O
22	assist	O
23	"	O
24	us	O
25	in	O
26	managing	O
27	the	O
28	cost	O
29	.	O

0	We	O
1	will	O
2	fight	O
3	with	O
4	them	O
5	about	O
6	who	O
7	owes	O
8	the	O
9	$	O
10	200	O
11	k	O
12	that	O
13	Jayden	B-PER
14	mentions	O
15	below	O
16	based	O
17	on	O
18	their	O
19	failure	O
20	to	O
21	"	O
22	assist	O
23	"	O
24	us	O
25	in	O
26	managing	O
27	the	O
28	cost	O
29	.	O

0	Nathan	B-PER
1	had	O
2	heard	O
3	that	O
4	one	O
5	hold	O
6	up	O
7	was	O
8	the	O
9	absence	O
10	of	O
11	a	O
12	confidentiality	O
13	agreement	O
14	--	O
15	I	O
16	guess	O
17	between	O
18	ECS	B-ORG
19	and	O
20	Transwestern	B-ORG
21	--	O
22	that	O
23	would	O
24	permit	O
25	ECS	B-ORG
26	to	O
27	communicate	O
28	to	O
29	us	O
30	the	O
31	details	O
32	on	O
33	how	O
34	to	O
35	access	O
36	teh	O
37	key	O
38	info.	O
39	from	O
40	CDEC	B-ORG
41	.	O

0	Isaac	B-PER
1	had	O
2	heard	O
3	that	O
4	one	O
5	hold	O
6	up	O
7	was	O
8	the	O
9	absence	O
10	of	O
11	a	O
12	confidentiality	O
13	agreement	O
14	--	O
15	I	O
16	guess	O
17	between	O
18	ECS	B-ORG
19	and	O
20	Transwestern	B-ORG
21	--	O
22	that	O
23	would	O
24	permit	O
25	ECS	B-ORG
26	to	O
27	communicate	O
28	to	O
29	us	O
30	the	O
31	details	O
32	on	O
33	how	O
34	to	O
35	access	O
36	teh	O
37	key	O
38	info.	O
39	from	O
40	CDEC	B-ORG
41	.	O

0	Would	O
1	you	O
2	please	O
3	contact	O
4	Michael	B-PER
5	Morales	I-PER
6	and	O
7	review	O
8	the	O
9	Gallup	O
10	Compression	O
11	Service	O
12	Contract	O
13	in	O
14	respect	O
15	to	O
16	the	O
17	Load	O
18	Control	O
19	Management	O
20	.	O

0	Would	O
1	you	O
2	please	O
3	contact	O
4	Christopher	B-PER
5	Wright	I-PER
6	and	O
7	review	O
8	the	O
9	Gallup	O
10	Compression	O
11	Service	O
12	Contract	O
13	in	O
14	respect	O
15	to	O
16	the	O
17	Load	O
18	Control	O
19	Management	O
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	just	O
2	got	O
3	done	O
4	looking	O
5	at	O
6	the	O
7	underlying	O
8	contract	O
9	language	O
10	as	O
11	set	O
12	forth	O
13	in	O
14	the	O
15	pro	O
16	forma	O
17	service	O
18	agreement	O
19	in	O
20	the	O
21	tariff	O
22	and	O
23	it	O
24	specifically	O
25	says	O
26	that	O
27	the	O
28	Liam	O
29	rate	O
30	would	O
31	apply	O
32	unless	O
33	a	O
34	discount	O
35	or	O
36	negotiated	O
37	rate	O
38	has	O
39	been	O
40	agreed	O
41	to	O
42	.	O

0	I	O
1	just	O
2	got	O
3	done	O
4	looking	O
5	at	O
6	the	O
7	underlying	O
8	contract	O
9	language	O
10	as	O
11	set	O
12	forth	O
13	in	O
14	the	O
15	pro	O
16	forma	O
17	service	O
18	agreement	O
19	in	O
20	the	O
21	tariff	O
22	and	O
23	it	O
24	specifically	O
25	says	O
26	that	O
27	the	O
28	Brian	O
29	rate	O
30	would	O
31	apply	O
32	unless	O
33	a	O
34	discount	O
35	or	O
36	negotiated	O
37	rate	O
38	has	O
39	been	O
40	agreed	O
41	to	O
42	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Wood	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Long	I-PER

0	In	O
1	discussion	O
2	with	O
3	Adam	B-PER
4	,	O
5	we	O
6	thought	O
7	it	O
8	would	O
9	be	O
10	good	O
11	to	O
12	put	O
13	this	O
14	together	O
15	in	O
16	a	O
17	format	O
18	of	O
19	questions	O
20	and	O
21	answers	O
22	.	O

0	In	O
1	discussion	O
2	with	O
3	Charles	B-PER
4	,	O
5	we	O
6	thought	O
7	it	O
8	would	O
9	be	O
10	good	O
11	to	O
12	put	O
13	this	O
14	together	O
15	in	O
16	a	O
17	format	O
18	of	O
19	questions	O
20	and	O
21	answers	O
22	.	O

0	It	O
1	incorporates	O
2	Mr.	O
3	Stojic	B-PER
4	's	O
5	and	O
6	Mr.	O
7	Erin	B-PER
8	's	O
9	initial	O
10	comments	O
11	.	O

0	It	O
1	incorporates	O
2	Mr.	O
3	Stojic	B-PER
4	's	O
5	and	O
6	Mr.	O
7	Karen	B-PER
8	's	O
9	initial	O
10	comments	O
11	.	O

0	Please	O
1	approve	O
2	Ava	B-PER
3	's	O
4	attached	O
5	expense	O
6	report	O
7	and	O
8	forward	O
9	to	O
10	accounting	O
11	with	O
12	a	O
13	cc	O
14	:	O
15	to	O
16	me	O
17	.	O

0	Please	O
1	approve	O
2	Courtney	B-PER
3	's	O
4	attached	O
5	expense	O
6	report	O
7	and	O
8	forward	O
9	to	O
10	accounting	O
11	with	O
12	a	O
13	cc	O
14	:	O
15	to	O
16	me	O
17	.	O

0	Please	O
1	approve	O
2	Alexandra	B-PER
3	's	O
4	attached	O
5	expense	O
6	report	O
7	and	O
8	forward	O
9	to	O
10	accounting	O
11	with	O
12	a	O
13	cc	O
14	:	O
15	to	O
16	me	O
17	.	O

0	Please	O
1	approve	O
2	Kaitlyn	B-PER
3	's	O
4	attached	O
5	expense	O
6	report	O
7	and	O
8	forward	O
9	to	O
10	accounting	O
11	with	O
12	a	O
13	cc	O
14	:	O
15	to	O
16	me	O
17	.	O

0	Tara	B-PER
1	,	O
2	do	O
3	we	O
4	have	O
5	any	O
6	sort	O
7	of	O
8	policy	O
9	on	O
10	requests	O
11	like	O
12	this	O
13	?	O

0	Katherine	B-PER
1	,	O
2	do	O
3	we	O
4	have	O
5	any	O
6	sort	O
7	of	O
8	policy	O
9	on	O
10	requests	O
11	like	O
12	this	O
13	?	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Morgan	I-PER
2	made	O
3	the	O
4	same	O
5	request	O
6	last	O
7	year	O
8	and	O
9	we	O
10	gave	O
11	her	O
12	the	O
13	chair	O
14	(	O
15	she	O
16	only	O
17	wanted	O
18	one	O
19	,	O
20	however	O
21	)	O
22	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Thomas	I-PER
2	made	O
3	the	O
4	same	O
5	request	O
6	last	O
7	year	O
8	and	O
9	we	O
10	gave	O
11	her	O
12	the	O
13	chair	O
14	(	O
15	she	O
16	only	O
17	wanted	O
18	one	O
19	,	O
20	however	O
21	)	O
22	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Rogers	I-PER
2	would	O
3	like	O
4	authorization	O
5	to	O
6	order	O
7	an	O
8	Aeron	O
9	chair	O
10	for	O
11	each	O
12	of	O
13	her	O
14	offices	O
15	-	O
16	on	O
17	47	O
18	and	O
19	41	O
20	.	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Cox	I-PER
2	would	O
3	like	O
4	authorization	O
5	to	O
6	order	O
7	an	O
8	Aeron	O
9	chair	O
10	for	O
11	each	O
12	of	O
13	her	O
14	offices	O
15	-	O
16	on	O
17	47	O
18	and	O
19	41	O
20	.	O

0	Erin	B-PER
1	,	O
2	do	O
3	we	O
4	have	O
5	any	O
6	sort	O
7	of	O
8	policy	O
9	on	O
10	requests	O
11	like	O
12	this	O
13	?	O

0	Amanda	B-PER
1	,	O
2	do	O
3	we	O
4	have	O
5	any	O
6	sort	O
7	of	O
8	policy	O
9	on	O
10	requests	O
11	like	O
12	this	O
13	?	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Perez	I-PER
2	made	O
3	the	O
4	same	O
5	request	O
6	last	O
7	year	O
8	and	O
9	we	O
10	gave	O
11	her	O
12	the	O
13	chair	O
14	(	O
15	she	O
16	only	O
17	wanted	O
18	one	O
19	,	O
20	however	O
21	)	O
22	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Martin	I-PER
2	made	O
3	the	O
4	same	O
5	request	O
6	last	O
7	year	O
8	and	O
9	we	O
10	gave	O
11	her	O
12	the	O
13	chair	O
14	(	O
15	she	O
16	only	O
17	wanted	O
18	one	O
19	,	O
20	however	O
21	)	O
22	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Nguyen	I-PER
2	would	O
3	like	O
4	authorization	O
5	to	O
6	order	O
7	an	O
8	Aeron	O
9	chair	O
10	for	O
11	each	O
12	of	O
13	her	O
14	offices	O
15	-	O
16	on	O
17	47	O
18	and	O
19	41	O
20	.	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Jackson	I-PER
2	would	O
3	like	O
4	authorization	O
5	to	O
6	order	O
7	an	O
8	Aeron	O
9	chair	O
10	for	O
11	each	O
12	of	O
13	her	O
14	offices	O
15	-	O
16	on	O
17	47	O
18	and	O
19	41	O
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	believe	O
2	you	O
3	got	O
4	a	O
5	copy	O
6	of	O
7	the	O
8	Michael	O
9	Kelly	O
10	letter	O
11	to	O
12	producers	O
13	dated	O
14	Jan	O
15	6	O
16	that	O
17	MKM	B-PER
18	's	O
19	spies	O
20	intercepted	O
21	.	O

0	I	O
1	believe	O
2	you	O
3	got	O
4	a	O
5	copy	O
6	of	O
7	the	O
8	Christopher	O
9	Thompson	O
10	letter	O
11	to	O
12	producers	O
13	dated	O
14	Jan	O
15	6	O
16	that	O
17	MKM	B-PER
18	's	O
19	spies	O
20	intercepted	O
21	.	O

0	She	O
1	forwarded	O
2	the	O
3	Sommer	O
4	letter	O
5	to	O
6	Bryan	B-PER
7	and	O
8	discussed	O
9	it	O
10	with	O
11	him	O
12	.	O

0	She	O
1	forwarded	O
2	the	O
3	Sommer	O
4	letter	O
5	to	O
6	Kyle	B-PER
7	and	O
8	discussed	O
9	it	O
10	with	O
11	him	O
12	.	O

0	Dari	O
1	and	O
2	I	O
3	vented	O
4	our	O
5	aggravation	O
6	by	O
7	drafting	O
8	the	O
9	attached	O
10	letter	O
11	to	O
12	Gibson	B-PER
13	and	O
14	Kyle	B-PER
15	complaining	O
16	of	O
17	Sommer	B-PER
18	's	O
19	duplicity	O
20	,	O
21	but	O
22	after	O
23	tempers	O
24	cooled	O
25	,	O
26	MKM	B-PER
27	and	O
28	I	O
29	decided	O
30	not	O
31	to	O
32	send	O
33	it	O
34	to	O
35	Adam	B-PER
36	or	O
37	urge	O
38	him	O
39	to	O
40	send	O
41	a	O
42	written	O
43	response	O
44	.	O

0	Dari	O
1	and	O
2	I	O
3	vented	O
4	our	O
5	aggravation	O
6	by	O
7	drafting	O
8	the	O
9	attached	O
10	letter	O
11	to	O
12	Kevin	B-PER
13	and	O
14	Kyle	B-PER
15	complaining	O
16	of	O
17	Sommer	B-PER
18	's	O
19	duplicity	O
20	,	O
21	but	O
22	after	O
23	tempers	O
24	cooled	O
25	,	O
26	MKM	B-PER
27	and	O
28	I	O
29	decided	O
30	not	O
31	to	O
32	send	O
33	it	O
34	to	O
35	Stan	B-PER
36	or	O
37	urge	O
38	him	O
39	to	O
40	send	O
41	a	O
42	written	O
43	response	O
44	.	O

0	As	O
1	it	O
2	stands	O
3	,	O
4	MKM	B-PER
5	and	O
6	I	O
7	will	O
8	probably	O
9	bring	O
10	it	O
11	up	O
12	with	O
13	Alyssa	B-PER
14	in	O
15	OK	B-LOC
16	City	I-LOC
17	and	O
18	strongly	O
19	suggest	O
20	the	O
21	importance	O
22	of	O
23	coordinated	O
24	communication	O
25	to	O
26	the	O
27	producers	O
28	.	O

0	As	O
1	it	O
2	stands	O
3	,	O
4	MKM	B-PER
5	and	O
6	I	O
7	will	O
8	probably	O
9	bring	O
10	it	O
11	up	O
12	with	O
13	Abigail	B-PER
14	in	O
15	OK	B-LOC
16	City	I-LOC
17	and	O
18	strongly	O
19	suggest	O
20	the	O
21	importance	O
22	of	O
23	coordinated	O
24	communication	O
25	to	O
26	the	O
27	producers	O
28	.	O

0	Peter	B-PER
1	may	O
2	also	O
3	bring	O
4	the	O
5	letter	O
6	up	O
7	orally	O
8	next	O
9	time	O
10	he	O
11	's	O
12	on	O
13	the	O
14	phonne	O
15	with	O
16	Gibson	B-PER
17	or	O
18	Kyle	B-PER
19	as	O
20	an	O
21	example	O
22	of	O
23	how	O
24	not	O
25	to	O
26	handle	O
27	this	O
28	situation	O
29	.	O

0	Stan	B-PER
1	may	O
2	also	O
3	bring	O
4	the	O
5	letter	O
6	up	O
7	orally	O
8	next	O
9	time	O
10	he	O
11	's	O
12	on	O
13	the	O
14	phonne	O
15	with	O
16	Gibson	B-PER
17	or	O
18	Elijah	B-PER
19	as	O
20	an	O
21	example	O
22	of	O
23	how	O
24	not	O
25	to	O
26	handle	O
27	this	O
28	situation	O
29	.	O

0	Megan	B-PER

0	Rebecca	B-PER

0	I	O
1	spoke	O
2	with	O
3	David	B-PER
4	and	O
5	he	O
6	said	O
7	there	O
8	are	O
9	a	O
10	bunch	O
11	of	O
12	folks	O
13	hanging	O
14	around	O
15	Dad	O
16	's	O
17	place	O
18	.	O

0	I	O
1	spoke	O
2	with	O
3	John	B-PER
4	and	O
5	he	O
6	said	O
7	there	O
8	are	O
9	a	O
10	bunch	O
11	of	O
12	folks	O
13	hanging	O
14	around	O
15	Dad	O
16	's	O
17	place	O
18	.	O

0	Stephen	B-PER
1	said	O
2	he	O
3	will	O
4	pay	O
5	us	O
6	soon	O
7	.	O

0	Brandon	B-PER
1	said	O
2	he	O
3	will	O
4	pay	O
5	us	O
6	soon	O
7	.	O

0	Cindy	B-PER
1	said	O
2	Liam	B-PER
3	has	O
4	grown	O
5	up	O
6	very	O
7	much	O
8	.	O

0	Cindy	B-PER
1	said	O
2	Timothy	B-PER
3	has	O
4	grown	O
5	up	O
6	very	O
7	much	O
8	.	O

0	I	O
1	believe	O
2	that	O
3	Peter	B-PER
4	told	O
5	me	O
6	the	O
7	extra	O
8	was	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	cashout	O
12	that	O
13	was	O
14	not	O
15	invoiced	O
16	.	O

0	I	O
1	believe	O
2	that	O
3	Angel	B-PER
4	told	O
5	me	O
6	the	O
7	extra	O
8	was	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	cashout	O
12	that	O
13	was	O
14	not	O
15	invoiced	O
16	.	O

0	Hey	O
1	Adam	B-PER
2	.	O

0	Hey	O
1	Robert	B-PER
2	.	O

0	Hi	O
1	Jacob	B-PER
2	,	O

0	Hi	O
1	Tyler	B-PER
2	,	O

0	I	O
1	sent	O
2	this	O
3	to	O
4	Alexandra	B-PER
5	last	O
6	week	O
7	.	O

0	I	O
1	sent	O
2	this	O
3	to	O
4	Lisa	B-PER
5	last	O
6	week	O
7	.	O

0	Isaiah	B-PER
1	Simien	I-PER

0	Timothy	B-PER
1	Simien	I-PER

0	Hi	O
1	Danielle	B-PER
2	,	O

0	Hi	O
1	Sydney	B-PER
2	,	O

0	Hi	O
1	Hannah	B-PER
2	,	O

0	Hi	O
1	Haley	B-PER
2	,	O

0	Jared	B-PER
1	,	O
2	Chelsea	B-PER
3	and	O
4	I	O
5	are	O
6	going	O
7	to	O
8	go	O
9	over	O
10	all	O
11	the	O
12	Florida	B-LOC
13	activity	O
14	tomorrow	O
15	morning	O
16	.	O

0	Jared	B-PER
1	,	O
2	Leah	B-PER
3	and	O
4	I	O
5	are	O
6	going	O
7	to	O
8	go	O
9	over	O
10	all	O
11	the	O
12	Florida	B-LOC
13	activity	O
14	tomorrow	O
15	morning	O
16	.	O

0	Zachary	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Jeremy	B-PER
1	,	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	n't	O
3	remember	O
4	if	O
5	your	O
6	email	O
7	mentioned	O
8	Mia	B-PER
9	.	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	n't	O
3	remember	O
4	if	O
5	your	O
6	email	O
7	mentioned	O
8	Sarah	B-PER
9	.	O

0	Jared	B-PER
1	,	O
2	Nicole	B-PER
3	and	O
4	I	O
5	are	O
6	going	O
7	to	O
8	go	O
9	over	O
10	all	O
11	the	O
12	Florida	B-LOC
13	activity	O
14	tomorrow	O
15	morning	O
16	.	O

0	Jared	B-PER
1	,	O
2	Nicole	B-PER
3	and	O
4	I	O
5	are	O
6	going	O
7	to	O
8	go	O
9	over	O
10	all	O
11	the	O
12	Florida	B-LOC
13	activity	O
14	tomorrow	O
15	morning	O
16	.	O

0	OK	O
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	never	O
4	get	O
5	to	O
6	talk	O
7	to	O
8	Kelly	B-PER
9	because	O
10	SHE	O
11	IS	O
12	ALWAYS	O
13	ON	O
14	THE	O
15	PHONE	O
16	.	O

0	OK	O
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	never	O
4	get	O
5	to	O
6	talk	O
7	to	O
8	Alicia	B-PER
9	because	O
10	SHE	O
11	IS	O
12	ALWAYS	O
13	ON	O
14	THE	O
15	PHONE	O
16	.	O

0	Should	O
1	we	O
2	all	O
3	get	O
4	together	O
5	and	O
6	make	O
7	a	O
8	conference	O
9	call	O
10	to	O
11	Dominion	B-ORG
12	like	O
13	we	O
14	did	O
15	before	O
16	or	O
17	should	O
18	I	O
19	just	O
20	call	O
21	Michael	B-PER
22	Gonzalez	I-PER
23	myself	O
24	?	O

0	Should	O
1	we	O
2	all	O
3	get	O
4	together	O
5	and	O
6	make	O
7	a	O
8	conference	O
9	call	O
10	to	O
11	Dominion	B-ORG
12	like	O
13	we	O
14	did	O
15	before	O
16	or	O
17	should	O
18	I	O
19	just	O
20	call	O
21	Christopher	B-PER
22	Wilson	I-PER
23	myself	O
24	?	O

0	Our	O
1	last	O
2	call	O
3	was	O
4	Iris	B-PER
5	Kind	I-PER
6	,	O
7	Bill	B-PER
8	Savier	I-PER
9	(	O
10	sp	O
11	?	O
12	)	O
13	,	O
14	and	O
15	Michael	B-PER
16	Peterson	I-PER
17	.	O

0	Our	O
1	last	O
2	call	O
3	was	O
4	Iris	B-PER
5	Kind	I-PER
6	,	O
7	Bill	B-PER
8	Savier	I-PER
9	(	O
10	sp	O
11	?	O
12	)	O
13	,	O
14	and	O
15	Christopher	B-PER
16	Clark	I-PER
17	.	O

0	Richard	B-PER
1	,	O
2	everything	O
3	looks	O
4	good	O
5	with	O
6	one	O
7	exception	O
8	.	O

0	Nicholas	B-PER
1	,	O
2	everything	O
3	looks	O
4	good	O
5	with	O
6	one	O
7	exception	O
8	.	O

0	Then	O
1	I	O
2	'll	O
3	take	O
4	it	O
5	to	O
6	Nathaniel	B-PER
7	for	O
8	his	O
9	approval	O
10	.	O

0	Then	O
1	I	O
2	'll	O
3	take	O
4	it	O
5	to	O
6	Mark	B-PER
7	for	O
8	his	O
9	approval	O
10	.	O

0	By	O
1	the	O
2	way	O
3	,	O
4	Cullen	B-ORG
5	and	I-ORG
6	Dykman	I-ORG
7	is	O
8	sending	O
9	copies	O
10	of	O
11	what	O
12	we	O
13	are	O
14	doing	O
15	to	O
16	Jennifer	B-PER
17	White	I-PER
18	.	O

0	By	O
1	the	O
2	way	O
3	,	O
4	Cullen	B-ORG
5	and	I-ORG
6	Dykman	I-ORG
7	is	O
8	sending	O
9	copies	O
10	of	O
11	what	O
12	we	O
13	are	O
14	doing	O
15	to	O
16	Jessica	B-PER
17	Phillips	I-PER
18	.	O

0	Joseph	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Robert	B-PER
1	:	O

0	This	O
1	document	O
2	has	O
3	been	O
4	modified	O
5	with	O
6	the	O
7	changes	O
8	that	O
9	were	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	mark	O
13	-	O
14	up	O
15	you	O
16	faxed	O
17	to	O
18	Jennifer	B-PER
19	Wood	I-PER
20	here	O
21	a	O
22	few	O
23	hours	O
24	ago	O
25	.	O

0	This	O
1	document	O
2	has	O
3	been	O
4	modified	O
5	with	O
6	the	O
7	changes	O
8	that	O
9	were	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	mark	O
13	-	O
14	up	O
15	you	O
16	faxed	O
17	to	O
18	Jessica	B-PER
19	Cruz	I-PER
20	here	O
21	a	O
22	few	O
23	hours	O
24	ago	O
25	.	O

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	as	O
3	I	O
4	mentioned	O
5	to	O
6	you	O
7	,	O
8	we	O
9	have	O
10	faxed	O
11	your	O
12	mark	O
13	-	O
14	up	O
15	to	O
16	Jennifer	B-PER
17	Sullivan	I-PER
18	at	O
19	Weil	B-ORG
20	Gotschal	I-ORG
21	in	O
22	Houston	B-LOC
23	to	O
24	keep	O
25	her	O
26	informed	O
27	.	O

0	Also	O
1	,	O
2	as	O
3	I	O
4	mentioned	O
5	to	O
6	you	O
7	,	O
8	we	O
9	have	O
10	faxed	O
11	your	O
12	mark	O
13	-	O
14	up	O
15	to	O
16	Jessica	B-PER
17	Flores	I-PER
18	at	O
19	Weil	B-ORG
20	Gotschal	I-ORG
21	in	O
22	Houston	B-LOC
23	to	O
24	keep	O
25	her	O
26	informed	O
27	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Parker	I-PER
2	Cullen	I-PER
3	and	B-ORG
4	Dykman	I-ORG
5	LLP	I-ORG
6	177	I-ORG
7	Montague	O
8	Street	O
9	Brooklyn	O
10	,	B-LOC
11	New	O
12	York	B-LOC
13	11201	I-LOC
14	phone	O
15	:	O
16	718-780-0046	O
17	fax	O
18	:	O
19	718-780-0276	O
20	e-mail	O
21	:	O
22	dmetcalfe@cullenanddykman.com	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Myers	I-PER
2	Cullen	I-PER
3	and	B-ORG
4	Dykman	I-ORG
5	LLP	I-ORG
6	177	I-ORG
7	Montague	O
8	Street	O
9	Brooklyn	O
10	,	B-LOC
11	New	O
12	York	B-LOC
13	11201	I-LOC
14	phone	O
15	:	O
16	718-780-0046	O
17	fax	O
18	:	O
19	718-780-0276	O
20	e-mail	O
21	:	O
22	dmetcalfe@cullenanddykman.com	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Bell	I-PER
2	did	O
3	a	O
4	story	O
5	on	O
6	gender	O
7	roles	O
8	in	O
9	Kuwait	B-LOC
10	several	O
11	years	O
12	before	O
13	the	O
14	Gulf	O
15	War	O
16	.	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Johnson	I-PER
2	did	O
3	a	O
4	story	O
5	on	O
6	gender	O
7	roles	O
8	in	O
9	Kuwait	B-LOC
10	several	O
11	years	O
12	before	O
13	the	O
14	Gulf	O
15	War	O
16	.	O

0	Dustin	B-PER

0	Logan	B-PER

0	Sydney	B-PER

0	Alexis	B-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Lewis	I-PER
2	has	O
3	OK'd	O
4	Anthony	B-PER
5	's	O
6	latest	O
7	request	O
8	w	O
9	/	O
10	r.	O
11	t.	O
12	the	O
13	CSA	O
14	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Price	I-PER
2	has	O
3	OK'd	O
4	Anthony	B-PER
5	's	O
6	latest	O
7	request	O
8	w	O
9	/	O
10	r.	O
11	t.	O
12	the	O
13	CSA	O
14	.	O

0	Could	O
1	you	O
2	please	O
3	send	O
4	an	O
5	executable	O
6	version	O
7	of	O
8	the	O
9	contract	O
10	to	O
11	Fred	B-PER
12	,	O
13	David	B-PER
14	,	O
15	Daniel	B-PER
16	and	O
17	me	O
18	tomorrow	O
19	?	O

0	Could	O
1	you	O
2	please	O
3	send	O
4	an	O
5	executable	O
6	version	O
7	of	O
8	the	O
9	contract	O
10	to	O
11	Christopher	B-PER
12	Morales	O
13	,	B-PER
14	John	O
15	and	B-PER
16	me	O
17	tomorrow	O
18	?	O

0	Connor	B-PER

0	Adam	B-PER

0	Thomas	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Jordan	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Watson	I-PER
2	Counsel	O
3	Uecomm	O
4	Limited	B-ORG
5	126	I-ORG
6	Trenerry	O
7	Crescent	O
8	Abbotsford	O
9	,	O
10	VIC	O
11	3067	O
12	.	O
13	Ph.	O
14	(	O
15	03	O
16	)	O
17	9221	O
18	4101	O
19	Fax.	O
20	(	O
21	03	O
22	)	O
23	9221	O
24	4193	O
25	Mob.	O
26	0417	O
27	575	O
28	920	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Sullivan	I-PER
2	Counsel	O
3	Uecomm	O
4	Limited	B-ORG
5	126	I-ORG
6	Trenerry	O
7	Crescent	O
8	Abbotsford	O
9	,	O
10	VIC	O
11	3067	O
12	.	O
13	Ph.	O
14	(	O
15	03	O
16	)	O
17	9221	O
18	4101	O
19	Fax.	O
20	(	O
21	03	O
22	)	O
23	9221	O
24	4193	O
25	Mob.	O
26	0417	O
27	575	O
28	920	O

0	Joseph	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Kayla	B-PER

0	Kayla	B-PER

0	Alyssa	B-PER

0	Jamie	B-PER

0	This	O
1	is	O
2	just	O
3	to	O
4	let	O
5	you	O
6	know	O
7	that	O
8	Tracy	B-PER
9	gave	O
10	birth	O
11	at	O
12	week	O
13	34	O
14	on	O
15	Friday	O
16	,	O
17	6th	O
18	July	O
19	,	O
20	to	O
21	our	O
22	triplets	O
23	:	O

0	This	O
1	is	O
2	just	O
3	to	O
4	let	O
5	you	O
6	know	O
7	that	O
8	Rachel	B-PER
9	gave	O
10	birth	O
11	at	O
12	week	O
13	34	O
14	on	O
15	Friday	O
16	,	O
17	6th	O
18	July	O
19	,	O
20	to	O
21	our	O
22	triplets	O
23	:	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Ross	I-PER
2	12.45	O
3	pm	O
4	-	O
5	3	O
6	lbs	O
7	4	O
8	ozs	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Robinson	I-PER
2	12.45	O
3	pm	O
4	-	O
5	3	O
6	lbs	O
7	4	O
8	ozs	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Rodriguez	I-PER
2	lbs	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Morales	I-PER
2	lbs	O

0	Alyssa	B-PER
1	May	I-PER
2	-	O
3	12.48	O
4	pm	O
5	-	O
6	3	O
7	lbs	O
8	15	O
9	ozs	O
10	.	O

0	Vanessa	B-PER
1	May	I-PER
2	-	O
3	12.48	O
4	pm	O
5	-	O
6	3	O
7	lbs	O
8	15	O
9	ozs	O
10	.	O

0	Brianna	B-PER
1	is	O
2	fine	O
3	,	O
4	too	O
5	-	O
6	very	O
7	well	O
8	!!	O

0	Kelly	B-PER
1	is	O
2	fine	O
3	,	O
4	too	O
5	-	O
6	very	O
7	well	O
8	!!	O

0	Chad	B-PER

0	Jordan	B-PER

0	Hailey	B-PER

0	Erin	B-PER

0	Hi	O
1	,	O
2	Nicole	B-PER
3	:	O

0	Hi	O
1	,	O
2	Lindsey	B-PER
3	:	O

0	Heather	B-PER

0	Alicia	B-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Hernandez	I-PER
2	Senior	O
3	Legal	O
4	Specialist	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Long	I-PER
2	Senior	O
3	Legal	O
4	Specialist	O

0	Ms.	O
1	Edward	B-PER
2	:	O

0	Ms.	O
1	Luke	B-PER
2	:	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	following	O
3	up	O
4	regarding	O
5	the	O
6	status	O
7	of	O
8	our	O
9	comments	O
10	to	O
11	the	O
12	form	O
13	of	O
14	guaranty	O
15	for	O
16	Pemex	O
17	that	O
18	you	O
19	provided	O
20	to	O
21	Jennifer	B-PER
22	Murphy	I-PER
23	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	following	O
3	up	O
4	regarding	O
5	the	O
6	status	O
7	of	O
8	our	O
9	comments	O
10	to	O
11	the	O
12	form	O
13	of	O
14	guaranty	O
15	for	O
16	Pemex	O
17	that	O
18	you	O
19	provided	O
20	to	O
21	Jessica	B-PER
22	Torres	I-PER
23	.	O

0	Please	O
1	do	O
2	not	O
3	hesitate	O
4	to	O
5	contact	O
6	either	O
7	Michael	B-PER
8	Garcia	I-PER
9	or	I-PER
10	me	I-PER
11	with	O
12	any	O
13	questions	O
14	or	O
15	comments	O
16	.	O

0	Please	O
1	do	O
2	not	O
3	hesitate	O
4	to	O
5	contact	O
6	either	O
7	Christopher	B-PER
8	Rivera	I-PER
9	or	I-PER
10	me	I-PER
11	with	O
12	any	O
13	questions	O
14	or	O
15	comments	O
16	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Long	I-PER
2	Senior	O
3	Legal	O
4	Specialist	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Hughes	I-PER
2	Senior	O
3	Legal	O
4	Specialist	O

0	Ms.	O
1	Caleb	B-PER
2	:	O

0	Ms.	O
1	John	B-PER
2	:	O

0	Please	O
1	do	O
2	not	O
3	hesitate	O
4	to	O
5	contact	O
6	either	O
7	Michael	B-PER
8	Jackson	I-PER
9	,	I-PER
10	Senior	I-PER
11	Counsel	O
12	(	O
13	713/345-7942	O
14	;	O
15	francisco.pinto.leite@enron.com	O
16	)	O
17	or	O
18	me	O
19	with	O
20	any	O
21	questions	O
22	or	O
23	comments	O
24	.	O

0	Please	O
1	do	O
2	not	O
3	hesitate	O
4	to	O
5	contact	O
6	either	O
7	Christopher	B-PER
8	Anderson	I-PER
9	,	I-PER
10	Senior	I-PER
11	Counsel	O
12	(	O
13	713/345-7942	O
14	;	O
15	francisco.pinto.leite@enron.com	O
16	)	O
17	or	O
18	me	O
19	with	O
20	any	O
21	questions	O
22	or	O
23	comments	O
24	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Jones	I-PER
2	Senior	O
3	Legal	O
4	Specialist	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Ross	I-PER
2	Senior	O
3	Legal	O
4	Specialist	O

0	Jamie	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Elizabeth	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Danielle	B-PER

0	Amanda	B-PER

0	Marie	B-PER
1	-	O

0	Marie	B-PER
1	-	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Ramirez	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Long	I-PER

0	Hi	O
1	Brianna	B-PER

0	Hi	O
1	Lindsey	B-PER

0	Kimberly	B-PER

0	Haley	B-PER

0	Luis	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Charles	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Cooper	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Hernandez	I-PER

0	Kevin	B-PER
1	is	O
2	looking	O
3	currently	O
4	for	O
5	a	O
6	job	O
7	.	O

0	Dylan	B-PER
1	is	O
2	looking	O
3	currently	O
4	for	O
5	a	O
6	job	O
7	.	O

0	Please	O
1	,	O
2	let	O
3	me	O
4	know	O
5	if	O
6	you	O
7	interested	O
8	in	O
9	introducing	O
10	Isaac	B-PER
11	to	O
12	executives	O
13	in	O
14	your	O
15	organization	O
16	.	O

0	Please	O
1	,	O
2	let	O
3	me	O
4	know	O
5	if	O
6	you	O
7	interested	O
8	in	O
9	introducing	O
10	Adrian	B-PER
11	to	O
12	executives	O
13	in	O
14	your	O
15	organization	O
16	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Edwards	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Sullivan	I-PER

0	Contact	O
1	Jennifer	B-PER
2	King	I-PER
3	to	O
4	make	O
5	an	O
6	appointment	O
7	.	O

0	Contact	O
1	Jessica	B-PER
2	Carter	I-PER
3	to	O
4	make	O
5	an	O
6	appointment	O
7	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Allen	I-PER
2	Khan@TRANSREDES	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Hernandez	I-PER
2	Khan@TRANSREDES	I-PER

0	Scott	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Bryan	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Rogers	I-PER
2	Khan@TRANSREDES	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Sullivan	I-PER
2	Khan@TRANSREDES	I-PER

0	Jack	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Nicholas	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Foster	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Clark	I-PER

0	Please	O
1	see	O
2	the	O
3	message	O
4	from	O
5	Michael	B-PER
6	Martin	I-PER
7	.	O

0	Please	O
1	see	O
2	the	O
3	message	O
4	from	O
5	Christopher	B-PER
6	Wood	I-PER
7	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Howard	I-PER
2	281-443-3744	O
3	smithjones@ev1.net	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Hall	I-PER
2	281-443-3744	O
3	smithjones@ev1.net	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Robinson	I-PER
2	281-443-3744	O
3	smithjones@ev1.net	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Stewart	I-PER
2	281-443-3744	O
3	smithjones@ev1.net	O

0	David	B-PER
1	looks	O
2	like	O
3	a	O
4	good	O
5	candidate	O
6	.	O

0	Elijah	B-PER
1	looks	O
2	like	O
3	a	O
4	good	O
5	candidate	O
6	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Perez	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Jones	I-PER

0	This	O
1	is	O
2	to	O
3	advise	O
4	you	O
5	that	O
6	we	O
7	have	O
8	available	O
9	,	O
10	for	O
11	your	O
12	business	O
13	or	O
14	personal	O
15	use	O
16	,	O
17	Jonathan	B-PER
18	's	O
19	four	O
20	(	O
21	4	O
22	)	O
23	WNBA	B-ORG
24	Comets	B-ORG
25	tickets	O
26	.	O

0	This	O
1	is	O
2	to	O
3	advise	O
4	you	O
5	that	O
6	we	O
7	have	O
8	available	O
9	,	O
10	for	O
11	your	O
12	business	O
13	or	O
14	personal	O
15	use	O
16	,	O
17	Stephen	B-PER
18	's	O
19	four	O
20	(	O
21	4	O
22	)	O
23	WNBA	B-ORG
24	Comets	B-ORG
25	tickets	O
26	.	O

0	Took	O
1	me	O
2	a	O
3	little	O
4	longer	O
5	to	O
6	review	O
7	and	O
8	revise	O
9	Kevin	B-PER
10	's	O
11	first	O
12	drafts	O
13	than	O
14	I	O
15	had	O
16	thought	O
17	(	O
18	there	O
19	's	O
20	a	O
21	lot	O
22	going	O
23	on	O
24	here	O
25	,	O
26	as	O
27	you	O
28	'll	O
29	see	O
30	soon	O
31	)	O
32	.	O

0	Took	O
1	me	O
2	a	O
3	little	O
4	longer	O
5	to	O
6	review	O
7	and	O
8	revise	O
9	Andrew	B-PER
10	's	O
11	first	O
12	drafts	O
13	than	O
14	I	O
15	had	O
16	thought	O
17	(	O
18	there	O
19	's	O
20	a	O
21	lot	O
22	going	O
23	on	O
24	here	O
25	,	O
26	as	O
27	you	O
28	'll	O
29	see	O
30	soon	O
31	)	O
32	.	O

0	Hello	O
1	,	O
2	Alex	B-PER
3	!	O

0	Hello	O
1	,	O
2	Austin	B-PER
3	!	O

0	Austin	B-PER
1	will	O
2	attend	O
3	in	O
4	person	O
5	.	O

0	Eric	B-PER
1	will	O
2	attend	O
3	in	O
4	person	O
5	.	O

0	Please	O
1	contact	O
2	Sherri	B-PER
3	Sera	I-PER
4	(	O
5	713/853-5984	O
6	)	O
7	or	O
8	Michael	B-PER
9	Lewis	I-PER
10	(	O
11	713/646-6505	O
12	)	O
13	for	O
14	the	O
15	weekly	O
16	dial	O
17	-	O
18	in	O
19	number	O
20	and	O
21	passcode	O
22	.	O

0	Please	O
1	contact	O
2	Sherri	B-PER
3	Sera	I-PER
4	(	O
5	713/853-5984	O
6	)	O
7	or	O
8	Christopher	B-PER
9	Ward	I-PER
10	(	O
11	713/646-6505	O
12	)	O
13	for	O
14	the	O
15	weekly	O
16	dial	O
17	-	O
18	in	O
19	number	O
20	and	O
21	passcode	O
22	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Torres	I-PER
2	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Morales	I-PER
2	.	O

0	It	O
1	's	O
2	funny	O
3	,	O
4	because	O
5	usually	O
6	it	O
7	's	O
8	just	O
9	me	O
10	,	O
11	Mom	O
12	,	O
13	Ryan	B-PER
14	and	O
15	Danelia	B-PER
16	,	O
17	and	O
18	Danelia	B-PER
19	does	O
20	n't	O
21	really	O
22	like	O
23	roasted	O
24	turkey	O
25	or	O
26	roast	O
27	beef	O
28	(	O
29	not	O
30	that	O
31	she	O
32	would	O
33	say	O
34	it	O
35	to	O
36	me	O
37	!	O
38	)	O
39	,	O
40	so	O
41	there	O
42	is	O
43	not	O
44	just	O
45	the	O
46	same	O
47	joy	O
48	in	O
49	cooking	O
50	it	O
51	would	O
52	be	O
53	elsewise	O
54	.	O

0	It	O
1	's	O
2	funny	O
3	,	O
4	because	O
5	usually	O
6	it	O
7	's	O
8	just	O
9	me	O
10	,	O
11	Mom	O
12	,	O
13	Aaron	B-PER
14	and	O
15	Danelia	B-PER
16	,	O
17	and	O
18	Danelia	B-PER
19	does	O
20	n't	O
21	really	O
22	like	O
23	roasted	O
24	turkey	O
25	or	O
26	roast	O
27	beef	O
28	(	O
29	not	O
30	that	O
31	she	O
32	would	O
33	say	O
34	it	O
35	to	O
36	me	O
37	!	O
38	)	O
39	,	O
40	so	O
41	there	O
42	is	O
43	not	O
44	just	O
45	the	O
46	same	O
47	joy	O
48	in	O
49	cooking	O
50	it	O
51	would	O
52	be	O
53	elsewise	O
54	.	O

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	incredible	O
3	what	O
4	a	O
5	good	O
6	player	O
7	Emily	B-PER
8	was	O
9	.	O

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	incredible	O
3	what	O
4	a	O
5	good	O
6	player	O
7	Julie	B-PER
8	was	O
9	.	O

0	I	O
1	expect	O
2	Alex	B-PER
3	did	O
4	n't	O
5	want	O
6	Mom	O
7	to	O
8	see	O
9	his	O
10	place	O
11	because	O
12	it	O
13	was	O
14	messy	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	expect	O
2	Jack	B-PER
3	did	O
4	n't	O
5	want	O
6	Mom	O
7	to	O
8	see	O
9	his	O
10	place	O
11	because	O
12	it	O
13	was	O
14	messy	O
15	.	O

0	Derek	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Ben	B-PER
3	did	O
4	a	O
5	marvelous	O
6	job	O
7	for	O
8	Thanksgiving	O
9	,	O
10	I	O
11	can	O
12	testify	O
13	that	O
14	it	O
15	was	O
16	one	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	best	O
20	Thanksgiv8ing	O
21	Dinners	O
22	I	O
23	've	O
24	ever	O
25	had	O
26	(	O
27	I	O
28	not	O
29	gon	O
30	na	O
31	tell	O
32	them	O
33	that	O
34	,	O
35	I	O
36	do	O
37	n't	O
38	want	O
39	them	O
40	getting	O
41	swell	O
42	heads	O
43	)	O
44	.	O

0	Stephen	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Ben	B-PER
3	did	O
4	a	O
5	marvelous	O
6	job	O
7	for	O
8	Thanksgiving	O
9	,	O
10	I	O
11	can	O
12	testify	O
13	that	O
14	it	O
15	was	O
16	one	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	best	O
20	Thanksgiv8ing	O
21	Dinners	O
22	I	O
23	've	O
24	ever	O
25	had	O
26	(	O
27	I	O
28	not	O
29	gon	O
30	na	O
31	tell	O
32	them	O
33	that	O
34	,	O
35	I	O
36	do	O
37	n't	O
38	want	O
39	them	O
40	getting	O
41	swell	O
42	heads	O
43	)	O
44	.	O

0	Why	O
1	did	O
2	n't	O
3	Jonathan	B-PER
4	show	O
5	Ma	O
6	his	O
7	appartment	O
8	?	O

0	Why	O
1	did	O
2	n't	O
3	Gabriel	B-PER
4	show	O
5	Ma	O
6	his	O
7	appartment	O
8	?	O

0	Jonathan	B-PER

0	Chad	B-PER

0	|--------+----------------------->	O
1	|	O
2	|	O
3	Amber.Jones@en	O
4	|	O
5	|	O
6	|	O
7	ron.com	O
8	|	O
9	|	O
10	|	O
11	|	O
12	|	O
13	|	O
14	11/29/2000	O
15	|	O
16	|	O
17	|	O
18	04:34	O
19	PM	O
20	|	O
21	|	O
22	|	O
23	|	O
24	|--------+----------------------->	O

0	|--------+----------------------->	O
1	|	O
2	|	O
3	Julia.Jones@en	O
4	|	O
5	|	O
6	|	O
7	ron.com	O
8	|	O
9	|	O
10	|	O
11	|	O
12	|	O
13	|	O
14	11/29/2000	O
15	|	O
16	|	O
17	|	O
18	04:34	O
19	PM	O
20	|	O
21	|	O
22	|	O
23	|	O
24	|--------+----------------------->	O

0	Nathan.Jones@ra	O

0	Travis.Jones@ra	O

0	Your	O
1	World	O
2	Series	O
3	in	O
4	Question	O
5	document	O
6	:	O
7	was	O
8	received	O
9	Michael	B-PER
10	Bennett	I-PER
11	/	O
12	US	O
13	/	O
14	AMERICAS	O
15	/	O
16	Equant	O
17	by	O
18	:	O
19	at	O
20	:	O
21	01:00:51	O
22	PM	O
23	Today	O

0	Your	O
1	World	O
2	Series	O
3	in	O
4	Question	O
5	document	O
6	:	O
7	was	O
8	received	O
9	Christopher	B-PER
10	Clark	I-PER
11	/	O
12	US	O
13	/	O
14	AMERICAS	O
15	/	O
16	Equant	O
17	by	O
18	:	O
19	at	O
20	:	O
21	01:00:51	O
22	PM	O
23	Today	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Roberts	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Sanchez	I-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Martin	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Hernandez	I-PER

0	Sara	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Michael	B-PER
3	Moore	I-PER
4	in	O
5	Credit	O
6	are	O
7	supposed	O
8	to	O
9	talk	O
10	to	O
11	the	O
12	DB	B-ORG
13	Credit	I-ORG
14	people	O
15	about	O
16	this	O
17	remaining	O
18	issue	O
19	.	O

0	Sara	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Christopher	B-PER
3	Ross	I-PER
4	in	O
5	Credit	O
6	are	O
7	supposed	O
8	to	O
9	talk	O
10	to	O
11	the	O
12	DB	B-ORG
13	Credit	I-ORG
14	people	O
15	about	O
16	this	O
17	remaining	O
18	issue	O
19	.	O

0	Sara	B-PER
1	is	O
2	working	O
3	on	O
4	that	O
5	with	O
6	Jennifer	B-PER
7	Sanders	I-PER
8	,	O
9	another	O
10	paralegal	O
11	in	O
12	our	O
13	Group	O
14	.	O

0	Sara	B-PER
1	is	O
2	working	O
3	on	O
4	that	O
5	with	O
6	Jessica	B-PER
7	Price	I-PER
8	,	O
9	another	O
10	paralegal	O
11	in	O
12	our	O
13	Group	O
14	.	O

0	Tana	B-PER
1	-	O

0	Tana	B-PER
1	-	O

0	I	O
1	spoke	O
2	to	O
3	Michael	B-PER
4	Myers	I-PER
5	about	O
6	your	O
7	signing	O
8	authority	O
9	,	O
10	and	O
11	he	O
12	agrees	O
13	that	O
14	you	O
15	do	O
16	not	O
17	have	O
18	the	O
19	authority	O
20	to	O
21	execute	O
22	documents	O
23	on	O
24	your	O
25	own	O
26	,	O
27	but	O
28	as	O
29	long	O
30	as	O
31	you	O
32	are	O
33	only	O
34	co-signing	O
35	documents	O
36	signed	O
37	by	O
38	an	O
39	authorized	O
40	officer	O
41	as	O
42	a	O
43	control	O
44	measure	O
45	we	O
46	're	O
47	OK	O
48	.	O

0	I	O
1	spoke	O
2	to	O
3	Christopher	B-PER
4	Sanders	I-PER
5	about	O
6	your	O
7	signing	O
8	authority	O
9	,	O
10	and	O
11	he	O
12	agrees	O
13	that	O
14	you	O
15	do	O
16	not	O
17	have	O
18	the	O
19	authority	O
20	to	O
21	execute	O
22	documents	O
23	on	O
24	your	O
25	own	O
26	,	O
27	but	O
28	as	O
29	long	O
30	as	O
31	you	O
32	are	O
33	only	O
34	co-signing	O
35	documents	O
36	signed	O
37	by	O
38	an	O
39	authorized	O
40	officer	O
41	as	O
42	a	O
43	control	O
44	measure	O
45	we	O
46	're	O
47	OK	O
48	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Bell	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Peterson	I-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Scott	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Young	I-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Sanders	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Ramirez	I-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Morgan	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Long	I-PER

0	Shawn	O
1	,	O

0	Jose	O
1	,	O

0	Noah	B-PER

0	Evan	B-PER

0	Kevin	B-PER

0	Nicholas	B-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Morales	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Cook	I-PER

0	It	O
1	would	O
2	be	O
3	nice	O
4	if	O
5	Shankman	B-PER
6	and	O
7	Michael	B-PER
8	Wood	I-PER
9	could	O
10	attend	O
11	.	O

0	It	O
1	would	O
2	be	O
3	nice	O
4	if	O
5	Shankman	B-PER
6	and	O
7	Christopher	B-PER
8	Parker	I-PER
9	could	O
10	attend	O
11	.	O

0	Updating	O
1	another	O
2	blue	O
3	file	O
4	because	O
5	Susan	O
6	B.	O
7	,	O
8	this	O
9	time	O
10	,	O
11	has	O
12	not	O
13	updated	O
14	it	O
15	to	O
16	reference	O
17	mergers	O
18	&	O
19	name	O
20	changes	O
21	!	O

0	Updating	O
1	another	O
2	blue	O
3	file	O
4	because	O
5	Susan	O
6	B.	O
7	,	O
8	this	O
9	time	O
10	,	O
11	has	O
12	not	O
13	updated	O
14	it	O
15	to	O
16	reference	O
17	mergers	O
18	&	O
19	name	O
20	changes	O
21	!	O

0	It	O
1	appears	O
2	you	O
3	missed	O
4	some	O
5	cpys	O
6	on	O
7	the	O
8	referenced	O
9	list	O
10	because	O
11	Cameron	O
12	had	O
13	the	O
14	freeze	O
15	panel	O
16	button	O
17	on	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	you	O
21	probably	O
22	did	O
23	n't	O
24	see	O
25	them	O
26	at	O
27	first	O
28	.	O

0	It	O
1	appears	O
2	you	O
3	missed	O
4	some	O
5	cpys	O
6	on	O
7	the	O
8	referenced	O
9	list	O
10	because	O
11	Travis	O
12	had	O
13	the	O
14	freeze	O
15	panel	O
16	button	O
17	on	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	you	O
21	probably	O
22	did	O
23	n't	O
24	see	O
25	them	O
26	at	O
27	first	O
28	.	O

0	I	O
1	communicated	O
2	that	O
3	to	O
4	Michael	B-PER
5	Scott	I-PER
6	.	O

0	I	O
1	communicated	O
2	that	O
3	to	O
4	Christopher	B-PER
5	Martin	I-PER
6	.	O

0	Carol	O
1	,	O
2	will	O
3	you	O
4	handle	O
5	this	O
6	or	O
7	Sean	B-PER
8	?	O

0	Carol	O
1	,	O
2	will	O
3	you	O
4	handle	O
5	this	O
6	or	O
7	Tyler	B-PER
8	?	O

0	Austin	B-PER

0	George	B-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Roberts	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Carter	I-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Cruz	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Myers	I-PER

0	I	O
1	just	O
2	got	O
3	a	O
4	call	O
5	from	O
6	Jayden	B-PER
7	and	O
8	Frank	B-PER
9	and	O
10	they	O
11	tell	O
12	me	O
13	I	O
14	have	O
15	a	O
16	whole	O
17	week	O
18	this	O
19	time	O
20	to	O
21	approve	O
22	the	O
23	whole	O
24	counterparty	O
25	list	O
26	to	O
27	trade	O
28	Australian	O
29	financial	O
30	power	O
31	.	O

0	I	O
1	just	O
2	got	O
3	a	O
4	call	O
5	from	O
6	Adam	B-PER
7	and	O
8	Frank	B-PER
9	and	O
10	they	O
11	tell	O
12	me	O
13	I	O
14	have	O
15	a	O
16	whole	O
17	week	O
18	this	O
19	time	O
20	to	O
21	approve	O
22	the	O
23	whole	O
24	counterparty	O
25	list	O
26	to	O
27	trade	O
28	Australian	O
29	financial	O
30	power	O
31	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Sanders	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Ross	I-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Nguyen	I-PER
2	is	O
3	the	O
4	CEO	O
5	of	O
6	GE	B-ORG
7	,	O
8	not	O
9	GM	B-ORG
10	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Parker	I-PER
2	is	O
3	the	O
4	CEO	O
5	of	O
6	GE	B-ORG
7	,	O
8	not	O
9	GM	B-ORG
10	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Hernandez	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Long	I-PER

0	Your	O
1	fellow	O
2	employees	O
3	asked	O
4	for	O
5	everyone	O
6	from	O
7	Britney	B-PER
8	Spears	I-PER
9	to	O
10	Michael	B-PER
11	Smith	I-PER
12	.	O

0	Your	O
1	fellow	O
2	employees	O
3	asked	O
4	for	O
5	everyone	O
6	from	O
7	Britney	B-PER
8	Spears	I-PER
9	to	O
10	Christopher	B-PER
11	Price	I-PER
12	.	O

0	10	O
1	.	O
2	Michael	B-PER
3	Lewis	I-PER
4	,	O
5	CEO	O
6	,	O
7	General	B-ORG
8	Motors	I-ORG

0	10	O
1	.	O
2	Christopher	B-PER
3	Allen	I-PER
4	,	O
5	CEO	O
6	,	O
7	General	B-ORG
8	Motors	I-ORG

0	7	O
1	.	O
2	Michael	B-PER
3	Mitchell	I-PER
4	,	O
5	author	O
6	,	O
7	The	O
8	Seven	O
9	Habits	O
10	of	O
11	Highly	O
12	Effective	O
13	People	O

0	7	O
1	.	O
2	Christopher	B-PER
3	Bennett	I-PER
4	,	O
5	author	O
6	,	O
7	The	O
8	Seven	O
9	Habits	O
10	of	O
11	Highly	O
12	Effective	O
13	People	O

0	5	O
1	.	O
2	General	O
3	Michael	B-PER
4	Cook	I-PER
5	,	O
6	former	O
7	Chairman	O
8	,	O
9	Joint	B-ORG
10	Chiefs	I-ORG
11	of	I-ORG
12	Staff	I-ORG
13	,	O
14	U.S.A	B-LOC
15	.	O

0	5	O
1	.	O
2	General	O
3	Christopher	B-PER
4	Stewart	I-PER
5	,	O
6	former	O
7	Chairman	O
8	,	O
9	Joint	B-ORG
10	Chiefs	I-ORG
11	of	I-ORG
12	Staff	I-ORG
13	,	O
14	U.S.A	B-LOC
15	.	O

0	3	O
1	.	O
2	Former	O
3	U.S.	B-LOC
4	President	O
5	Michael	B-PER
6	Smith	I-PER

0	3	O
1	.	O
2	Former	O
3	U.S.	B-LOC
4	President	O
5	Christopher	B-PER
6	Smith	I-PER

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Michael	B-PER
3	Phillips	I-PER
4	,	O
5	CEO	O
6	,	O
7	Microsoft	B-ORG

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Christopher	B-PER
3	Lewis	I-PER
4	,	O
5	CEO	O
6	,	O
7	Microsoft	B-ORG

0	1	O
1	.	O
2	Texas	B-LOC
3	Governor	O
4	Michael	B-PER
5	Martin	I-PER

0	1	O
1	.	O
2	Texas	B-LOC
3	Governor	O
4	Christopher	B-PER
5	Bell	I-PER

0	Nathaniel	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Charles	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Michael	B-PER

0	Jose	B-PER

0	Aiden	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Paul	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Kenneth	B-PER

0	Jose	B-PER

0	Mark	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Elijah	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Brian	B-PER

0	Aiden	B-PER

0	Jason	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Isaac	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Johnson	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Cruz	I-PER

0	Timothy	B-PER
1	sold	O
2	!	O

0	Gregory	B-PER
1	sold	O
2	!	O

0	Elijah	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Joshua	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Christian	B-PER

0	Tyler	B-PER

0	Ethan	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Bryan	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Aiden	B-PER

0	James	B-PER

0	Jordan	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Peter	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Jeremy	B-PER

0	Jayden	B-PER

0	Charles	B-PER

0	Chad	B-PER

0	Chad	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Jeremy	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Jose	B-PER

0	Matthew	B-PER

0	Isaiah	B-PER

0	Aiden	B-PER

0	Liam	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Ian	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Peter	B-PER

0	Benjamin	B-PER

0	Caleb	B-PER

0	Jeffrey	B-PER

0	Chad	B-PER
1	,	O

0	David	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Juan	B-PER

0	Patrick	B-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Cindy	B-PER
3	,	O

0	Ian	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Cindy	B-PER
3	,	O

0	Aaron	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Jackson	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Sanchez	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Lewis	I-PER

0	Dustin	B-PER

0	Sean	B-PER

0	Mary	B-PER
1	has	O
2	made	O
3	our	O
4	reservations	O
5	for	O
6	the	O
7	Round	O
8	Table	O
9	Friday	O
10	night	O
11	(	O
12	5/18	O
13	)	O
14	at	O
15	Sullivan	B-LOC
16	's	I-LOC
17	Steak	I-LOC
18	House	I-LOC
19	for	O
20	6:30	O
21	.	O

0	Monica	B-PER
1	has	O
2	made	O
3	our	O
4	reservations	O
5	for	O
6	the	O
7	Round	O
8	Table	O
9	Friday	O
10	night	O
11	(	O
12	5/18	O
13	)	O
14	at	O
15	Sullivan	B-LOC
16	's	I-LOC
17	Steak	I-LOC
18	House	I-LOC
19	for	O
20	6:30	O
21	.	O

0	Mia	B-PER

0	Tracy	B-PER

0	Brianna	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Leslie	B-PER
1	,	O

0	George	B-PER

0	Brian	B-PER

0	Samantha	B-PER
1	has	O
2	made	O
3	our	O
4	reservations	O
5	for	O
6	the	O
7	Round	O
8	Table	O
9	Friday	O
10	night	O
11	(	O
12	5/18	O
13	)	O
14	at	O
15	Sullivan	B-LOC
16	's	I-LOC
17	Steak	I-LOC
18	House	I-LOC
19	for	O
20	6:30	O
21	.	O

0	Grace	B-PER
1	has	O
2	made	O
3	our	O
4	reservations	O
5	for	O
6	the	O
7	Round	O
8	Table	O
9	Friday	O
10	night	O
11	(	O
12	5/18	O
13	)	O
14	at	O
15	Sullivan	B-LOC
16	's	I-LOC
17	Steak	I-LOC
18	House	I-LOC
19	for	O
20	6:30	O
21	.	O

0	Tracy	B-PER

0	Chelsea	B-PER

0	Gabriel	B-PER

0	Luis	B-PER

0	Anne	B-PER
1	,	O
2	Logan	B-PER
3	will	O
4	call	O
5	you	O
6	regarding	O
7	Sarah	B-PER
8	.	O

0	Anne	B-PER
1	,	O
2	Edward	B-PER
3	will	O
4	call	O
5	you	O
6	regarding	O
7	Sarah	B-PER
8	.	O

0	As	O
1	I	O
2	mentioned	O
3	in	O
4	my	O
5	voice	O
6	mail	O
7	,	O
8	Michael	B-PER
9	Johnson	I-PER
10	going	O
11	to	O
12	hire	O
13	Sara	B-PER
14	Woody	I-PER
15	,	O
16	a	O
17	recent	O
18	MBA	O
19	grad	O
20	from	O
21	Rice	B-LOC
22	,	O
23	into	O
24	his	O
25	group	O
26	.	O

0	As	O
1	I	O
2	mentioned	O
3	in	O
4	my	O
5	voice	O
6	mail	O
7	,	O
8	Christopher	B-PER
9	Cooper	I-PER
10	going	O
11	to	O
12	hire	O
13	Sara	B-PER
14	Woody	I-PER
15	,	O
16	a	O
17	recent	O
18	MBA	O
19	grad	O
20	from	O
21	Rice	B-LOC
22	,	O
23	into	O
24	his	O
25	group	O
26	.	O

0	However	O
1	,	O
2	when	O
3	we	O
4	were	O
5	talking	O
6	about	O
7	this	O
8	position	O
9	,	O
10	Aaron	B-PER
11	compared	O
12	Sara	B-PER
13	to	O
14	Elena	B-PER
15	.	O

0	However	O
1	,	O
2	when	O
3	we	O
4	were	O
5	talking	O
6	about	O
7	this	O
8	position	O
9	,	O
10	Jose	B-PER
11	compared	O
12	Sara	B-PER
13	to	O
14	Elena	B-PER
15	.	O

0	Elena	B-PER
1	's	O
2	title	O
3	is	O
4	admin	O
5	coordinator	O
6	,	O
7	and	O
8	I	O
9	know	O
10	that	O
11	Catherine	B-PER
12	should	O
13	not	O
14	have	O
15	this	O
16	title	O
17	,	O
18	and	O
19	honestly	O
20	do	O
21	not	O
22	think	O
23	that	O
24	Elena	B-PER
25	should	O
26	also	O
27	.	O

0	Elena	B-PER
1	's	O
2	title	O
3	is	O
4	admin	O
5	coordinator	O
6	,	O
7	and	O
8	I	O
9	know	O
10	that	O
11	Kimberly	B-PER
12	should	O
13	not	O
14	have	O
15	this	O
16	title	O
17	,	O
18	and	O
19	honestly	O
20	do	O
21	not	O
22	think	O
23	that	O
24	Elena	B-PER
25	should	O
26	also	O
27	.	O

0	I	O
1	suggest	O
2	that	O
3	you	O
4	compare	O
5	Elena	B-PER
6	and	O
7	Jamie	B-PER
8	's	O
9	duties	O
10	/	O
11	level	O
12	to	O
13	other	O
14	Sr.	O
15	Spec.	O
16	in	O
17	your	O
18	group	O
19	such	O
20	as	O
21	Kenneth	B-PER
22	Parkhill	I-PER
23	and	O
24	Sevil	B-PER
25	to	O
26	determine	O
27	if	O
28	they	O
29	are	O
30	equivalent	O
31	,	O
32	or	O
33	if	O
34	their	O
35	scope	O
36	of	O
37	responsibilities	O
38	and	O
39	experience	O
40	is	O
41	not	O
42	as	O
43	broad	O
44	.	O

0	I	O
1	suggest	O
2	that	O
3	you	O
4	compare	O
5	Elena	B-PER
6	and	O
7	April	B-PER
8	's	O
9	duties	O
10	/	O
11	level	O
12	to	O
13	other	O
14	Sr.	O
15	Spec.	O
16	in	O
17	your	O
18	group	O
19	such	O
20	as	O
21	Kenneth	B-PER
22	Parkhill	I-PER
23	and	O
24	Sevil	B-PER
25	to	O
26	determine	O
27	if	O
28	they	O
29	are	O
30	equivalent	O
31	,	O
32	or	O
33	if	O
34	their	O
35	scope	O
36	of	O
37	responsibilities	O
38	and	O
39	experience	O
40	is	O
41	not	O
42	as	O
43	broad	O
44	.	O

0	Brandon	B-PER

0	Jose	B-PER

0	Vince	B-PER
1	-	O

0	Vince	B-PER
1	-	O

0	Carlos	B-PER

0	Jack	B-PER

0	Nicole	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Emily	B-PER
1	,	O

0	Anne	B-PER
1	,	O
2	please	O
3	,	O
4	include	O
5	this	O
6	info	O
7	in	O
8	Catherine	B-PER
9	'	O
10	file	O

0	Anne	B-PER
1	,	O
2	please	O
3	,	O
4	include	O
5	this	O
6	info	O
7	in	O
8	Erin	B-PER
9	'	O
10	file	O

0	Mark	B-PER

0	Jesse	B-PER

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Roberts	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Bennett	I-PER

0	Andrew	B-PER
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	noticed	O
4	that	O
5	our	O
6	allocation	O
7	from	O
8	2000	O
9	to	O
10	2001	O
11	is	O
12	going	O
13	up	O
14	by	O
15	21	O
16	%	O
17	year	O
18	on	O
19	year	O
20	(	O
21	ie	O
22	)	O
23	$	O
24	13.9	O
25	M	O
26	from	O
27	$	O
28	11.5	O
29	M	O
30	.	O

0	Dylan	B-PER
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	noticed	O
4	that	O
5	our	O
6	allocation	O
7	from	O
8	2000	O
9	to	O
10	2001	O
11	is	O
12	going	O
13	up	O
14	by	O
15	21	O
16	%	O
17	year	O
18	on	O
19	year	O
20	(	O
21	ie	O
22	)	O
23	$	O
24	13.9	O
25	M	O
26	from	O
27	$	O
28	11.5	O
29	M	O
30	.	O

0	I	O
1	just	O
2	wanted	O
3	Riley	B-PER
4	to	O
5	hear	O
6	(	O
7	she	O
8	enjoys	O
9	utility	O
10	bashing	O
11	so	O
12	much	O
13	)	O
14	.	O

0	I	O
1	just	O
2	wanted	O
3	Kristen	B-PER
4	to	O
5	hear	O
6	(	O
7	she	O
8	enjoys	O
9	utility	O
10	bashing	O
11	so	O
12	much	O
13	)	O
14	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Cooper	I-PER
2	has	O
3	been	O
4	a	O
5	godsend	O
6	--	O
7	somebody	O
8	not	O
9	afraid	O
10	to	O
11	tell	O
12	it	O
13	like	O
14	it	O
15	is	O
16	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Parker	I-PER
2	has	O
3	been	O
4	a	O
5	godsend	O
6	--	O
7	somebody	O
8	not	O
9	afraid	O
10	to	O
11	tell	O
12	it	O
13	like	O
14	it	O
15	is	O
16	.	O

0	Thomas	B-PER

0	Justin	B-PER

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Reed	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Evans	I-PER

0	Bryan	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Anthony	B-PER
1	:	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Lopez	I-PER

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Nelson	I-PER

0	Stephen	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Steve	B-PER
3	-	O

0	Mark	B-PER
1	and	O
2	Steve	B-PER
3	-	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Lee	I-PER
2	and	O
3	I	O
4	would	O
5	like	O
6	to	O
7	meet	O
8	with	O
9	you	O
10	to	O
11	discuss	O
12	the	O
13	issues	O
14	concerning	O
15	BackWeb	O
16	before	O
17	we	O
18	proceed	O
19	.	O

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Edwards	I-PER
2	and	O
3	I	O
4	would	O
5	like	O
6	to	O
7	meet	O
8	with	O
9	you	O
10	to	O
11	discuss	O
12	the	O
13	issues	O
14	concerning	O
15	BackWeb	O
16	before	O
17	we	O
18	proceed	O
19	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Carter	I-PER
2	has	O
3	asked	O
4	me	O
5	to	O
6	set	O
7	a	O
8	conference	O
9	call	O
10	to	O
11	review	O
12	the	O
13	FERC	B-ORG
14	Meeting	O
15	that	O
16	was	O
17	held	O
18	Thursday	O
19	,	O
20	Nov.	O
21	9th	O
22	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Garcia	I-PER
2	has	O
3	asked	O
4	me	O
5	to	O
6	set	O
7	a	O
8	conference	O
9	call	O
10	to	O
11	review	O
12	the	O
13	FERC	B-ORG
14	Meeting	O
15	that	O
16	was	O
17	held	O
18	Thursday	O
19	,	O
20	Nov.	O
21	9th	O
22	.	O

0	Pin	O
1	#	O
2	for	O
3	Michael	B-PER
4	Evans	I-PER
5	ONLY	O
6	:	O
7	362416	O

0	Pin	O
1	#	O
2	for	O
3	Christopher	B-PER
4	Stewart	I-PER
5	ONLY	O
6	:	O
7	362416	O

0	Lysa	B-PER
1	Akin	I-PER
2	Ass't.	O
3	to	O
4	Michael	B-PER
5	Roberts	I-PER

0	Lysa	B-PER
1	Akin	I-PER
2	Ass't.	O
3	to	O
4	Christopher	B-PER
5	Clark	I-PER

0	Sounds	O
1	as	O
2	though	O
3	Edward	B-PER
4	has	O
5	done	O
6	very	O
7	well	O
8	as	O
9	SMSU	B-LOC
10	.	O

0	Sounds	O
1	as	O
2	though	O
3	Michael	B-PER
4	has	O
5	done	O
6	very	O
7	well	O
8	as	O
9	SMSU	B-LOC
10	.	O

0	As	O
1	to	O
2	our	O
3	family	O
4	,	O
5	within	O
6	the	O
7	last	O
8	ten	O
9	days	O
10	our	O
11	youngest	O
12	daughter	O
13	Jamie	B-PER
14	was	O
15	married	O
16	to	O
17	a	O
18	young	O
19	man	O
20	from	O
21	Buenos	B-LOC
22	Aires	I-LOC
23	,	O
24	Argentina	B-LOC
25	.	O

0	As	O
1	to	O
2	our	O
3	family	O
4	,	O
5	within	O
6	the	O
7	last	O
8	ten	O
9	days	O
10	our	O
11	youngest	O
12	daughter	O
13	Jasmine	B-PER
14	was	O
15	married	O
16	to	O
17	a	O
18	young	O
19	man	O
20	from	O
21	Buenos	B-LOC
22	Aires	I-LOC
23	,	O
24	Argentina	B-LOC
25	.	O

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	born	O
3	to	O
4	our	O
5	son	O
6	Bryan	B-PER
7	and	O
8	his	O
9	wife	O
10	Courtney	B-PER
11	.	O

0	It	O
1	was	O
2	born	O
3	to	O
4	our	O
5	son	O
6	David	B-PER
7	and	O
8	his	O
9	wife	O
10	Sara	B-PER
11	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	looking	O
3	forward	O
4	to	O
5	seeing	O
6	Jennifer	B-PER
7	Williams	I-PER
8	when	I-PER
9	she	I-PER
10	comes	I-PER
11	to	O
12	Houston	O
13	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	looking	O
3	forward	O
4	to	O
5	seeing	O
6	Jessica	B-PER
7	Cooper	I-PER
8	when	I-PER
9	she	I-PER
10	comes	I-PER
11	to	O
12	Houston	O
13	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Torres	I-PER
2	Secretary	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Murphy	I-PER
2	Secretary	I-PER

0	Meanwhile	O
1	,	O
2	Michael	B-PER
3	Lewis	I-PER
4	has	O
5	agreed	O
6	to	O
7	meet	O
8	with	O
9	us	O
10	in	O
11	September	O
12	to	O
13	brainstorm	O
14	on	O
15	the	O
16	ideas	O
17	we	O
18	've	O
19	generated	O
20	and	O
21	also	O
22	to	O
23	give	O
24	us	O
25	a	O
26	sense	O
27	of	O
28	some	O
29	of	O
30	the	O
31	issues	O
32	as	O
33	he	O
34	sees	O
35	them	O
36	.	O

0	Meanwhile	O
1	,	O
2	Christopher	B-PER
3	Green	I-PER
4	has	O
5	agreed	O
6	to	O
7	meet	O
8	with	O
9	us	O
10	in	O
11	September	O
12	to	O
13	brainstorm	O
14	on	O
15	the	O
16	ideas	O
17	we	O
18	've	O
19	generated	O
20	and	O
21	also	O
22	to	O
23	give	O
24	us	O
25	a	O
26	sense	O
27	of	O
28	some	O
29	of	O
30	the	O
31	issues	O
32	as	O
33	he	O
34	sees	O
35	them	O
36	.	O

0	Good	O
1	morning	O
2	,	O
3	Kitty	B-PER
4	-	O

0	Good	O
1	morning	O
2	,	O
3	Kitty	B-PER
4	-	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Rogers	I-PER
2	would	O
3	like	O
4	to	O
5	have	O
6	the	O
7	Armada	O
8	M306	O
9	series	O
10	-	O
11	"	O
12	the	O
13	first	O
14	ultra	O
15	portable	O
16	notebook	O
17	designed	O
18	for	O
19	the	O
20	enterprise	O
21	"	O
22	.	O

0	Christopher	B-PER
1	Brooks	I-PER
2	would	O
3	like	O
4	to	O
5	have	O
6	the	O
7	Armada	O
8	M306	O
9	series	O
10	-	O
11	"	O
12	the	O
13	first	O
14	ultra	O
15	portable	O
16	notebook	O
17	designed	O
18	for	O
19	the	O
20	enterprise	O
21	"	O
22	.	O

0	Mason	B-PER
1	said	O
2	to	O
3	go	O
4	ahead	O
5	and	O
6	equip	O
7	it	O
8	with	O
9	what	O
10	you	O
11	think	O
12	it	O
13	should	O
14	have	O
15	.	O

0	Logan	B-PER
1	said	O
2	to	O
3	go	O
4	ahead	O
5	and	O
6	equip	O
7	it	O
8	with	O
9	what	O
10	you	O
11	think	O
12	it	O
13	should	O
14	have	O
15	.	O

0	Thanks	O
1	,	O
2	Angela	B-PER
3	.	O

0	Thanks	O
1	,	O
2	Brianna	B-PER
3	.	O

0	Jennifer	B-PER
1	Ross	I-PER

0	Jessica	B-PER
1	Bailey	I-PER

0	Recently	O
1	Michael	B-PER
2	Brown	I-PER
3	and	O
4	David	B-PER
5	Dewhurst	I-PER
6	sent	O
7	you	O
8	an	O
9	invitation	O
10	to	O
11	a	O
12	reception	O
13	which	O
14	they	O
15	are	O
16	hosting	O
17	on	O
18	Wed.	O
19	6/14	O
20	at	O
21	5:00	O
22	PM	O
23	to	O
24	be	O
25	held	O
26	at	O
27	the	O
28	Houston	B-LOC
29	Petroleum	I-LOC
30	Club	I-LOC
31	.	O

0	Recently	O
1	Christopher	B-PER
2	Brown	I-PER
3	and	O
4	David	B-PER
5	Dewhurst	I-PER
6	sent	O
7	you	O
8	an	O
9	invitation	O
10	to	O
11	a	O
12	reception	O
13	which	O
14	they	O
15	are	O
16	hosting	O
17	on	O
18	Wed.	O
19	6/14	O
20	at	O
21	5:00	O
22	PM	O
23	to	O
24	be	O
25	held	O
26	at	O
27	the	O
28	Houston	B-LOC
29	Petroleum	I-LOC
30	Club	I-LOC
31	.	O
