0	However	O
1	,	O
2	save	O
3	some	O
4	of	O
5	your	O
6	shots	O
7	for	O
8	the	O
9	rest	O
10	of	O
11	the	O
12	falls	O
13	,	O
14	as	O
15	in	O
16	total	O
17	there	O
18	are	O
19	around	O
20	225	O
21	cascades	O
22	that	O
23	spread	O
24	out	O
25	over	O
26	nearly	O
27	2	O
28	miles	O
29	of	O
30	the	O
31	Iguazu	B-LOC
32	River	I-LOC
33	.	O

0	However	O
1	,	O
2	save	O
3	some	O
4	of	O
5	your	O
6	shots	O
7	for	O
8	the	O
9	rest	O
10	of	O
11	the	O
12	falls	O
13	,	O
14	as	O
15	in	O
16	total	O
17	there	O
18	are	O
19	around	O
20	303	O
21	cascades	O
22	that	O
23	spread	O
24	out	O
25	over	O
26	nearly	O
27	2	O
28	miles	O
29	of	O
30	the	O
31	Iguazu	B-LOC
32	River	I-LOC
33	.	O

0	The	O
1	nearest	O
2	towns	O
3	to	O
4	the	O
5	site	O
6	are	O
7	Puerto	B-LOC
8	Iguazu	I-LOC
9	in	O
10	Argentina	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	about	O
13	10	O
14	miles	O
15	from	O
16	the	O
17	falls	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	Foz	B-LOC
21	do	I-LOC
22	Iguaçu	I-LOC
23	in	O
24	Brazil	B-LOC
25	,	O
26	which	O
27	is	O
28	equally	O
29	close	O
30	.	O

0	The	O
1	nearest	O
2	towns	O
3	to	O
4	the	O
5	site	O
6	are	O
7	Puerto	B-LOC
8	Iguazu	I-LOC
9	in	O
10	Argentina	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	about	O
13	10	O
14	miles	O
15	from	O
16	the	O
17	falls	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	Foz	B-LOC
21	do	I-LOC
22	Iguaçu	I-LOC
23	in	O
24	Brazil	B-LOC
25	,	O
26	which	O
27	is	O
28	equally	O
29	close	O
30	.	O

0	The	O
1	bus	O
2	is	O
3	obviously	O
4	the	O
5	cheaper	O
6	option	O
7	,	O
8	and	O
9	travelling	O
10	up	O
11	from	O
12	Buenos	B-LOC
13	Aires	I-LOC
14	the	O
15	trip	O
16	is	O
17	a	O
18	full	O
19	18	O
20	hours	O
21	,	O
22	although	O
23	the	O
24	buses	O
25	are	O
26	very	O
27	comfortable	O
28	with	O
29	spacious	O
30	reclining	O
31	seats	O
32	.	O

0	The	O
1	bus	O
2	is	O
3	obviously	O
4	the	O
5	cheaper	O
6	option	O
7	,	O
8	and	O
9	travelling	O
10	up	O
11	from	O
12	Buenos	B-LOC
13	Aires	I-LOC
14	the	O
15	trip	O
16	is	O
17	a	O
18	full	O
19	19	O
20	hours	O
21	,	O
22	although	O
23	the	O
24	buses	O
25	are	O
26	very	O
27	comfortable	O
28	with	O
29	spacious	O
30	reclining	O
31	seats	O
32	.	O

0	The	O
1	bus	O
2	trip	O
3	down	O
4	from	O
5	Sao	B-LOC
6	Paulo	I-LOC
7	is	O
8	a	O
9	similar	O
10	affair	O
11	taking	O
12	around	O
13	19	O
14	hours	O
15	.	O

0	The	O
1	bus	O
2	trip	O
3	down	O
4	from	O
5	Sao	B-LOC
6	Paulo	I-LOC
7	is	O
8	a	O
9	similar	O
10	affair	O
11	taking	O
12	around	O
13	21	O
14	hours	O
15	.	O

0	-	O
1	15	O
2	piece	O
3	Chicken	O
4	McNuggets	O

0	-	O
1	15	O
2	piece	O
3	Chicken	O
4	McNuggets	O

0	-	O
1	8	O
2	piece	O
3	Chicken	O
4	McNuggets	O

0	-	O
1	8	O
2	piece	O
3	Chicken	O
4	McNuggets	O

0	The	O
1	other	O
2	ethicities	O
3	were	O
4	n't	O
5	well	O
6	represented	O
7	in	O
8	politics	O
9	yet	O
10	--	O
11	or	O
12	rather	O
13	,	O
14	they	O
15	were	O
16	just	O
17	breaking	O
18	the	O
19	color	O
20	barrier	O
21	in	O
22	the	O
23	73's	O
24	due	O
25	largely	O
26	to	O
27	the	O
28	more	O
29	open	O
30	-	O
31	minded	O
32	hippy	O
33	generation	O
34	.	O

0	The	O
1	other	O
2	ethicities	O
3	were	O
4	n't	O
5	well	O
6	represented	O
7	in	O
8	politics	O
9	yet	O
10	--	O
11	or	O
12	rather	O
13	,	O
14	they	O
15	were	O
16	just	O
17	breaking	O
18	the	O
19	color	O
20	barrier	O
21	in	O
22	the	O
23	71's	O
24	due	O
25	largely	O
26	to	O
27	the	O
28	more	O
29	open	O
30	-	O
31	minded	O
32	hippy	O
33	generation	O
34	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	4	O
3	sisters	O
4	and	O
5	so	O
6	including	O
7	my	O
8	mom	O
9	...	O
10	he	O
11	is	O
12	the	O
13	only	O
14	guy	O
15	in	O
16	a	O
17	house	O
18	of	O
19	six	O
20	females	O
21	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	4	O
3	sisters	O
4	and	O
5	so	O
6	including	O
7	my	O
8	mom	O
9	...	O
10	he	O
11	is	O
12	the	O
13	only	O
14	guy	O
15	in	O
16	a	O
17	house	O
18	of	O
19	six	O
20	females	O
21	.	O

0	Modern	O
1	m	O
2	14	O
3	vs	O
4	Vietnam	B-LOC
5	m	O
6	14	O
7	version	O
8	?	O

0	Modern	O
1	m	O
2	18	O
3	vs	O
4	Vietnam	B-LOC
5	m	O
6	18	O
7	version	O
8	?	O

0	I	O
1	was	O
2	playing	O
3	a	O
4	video	O
5	game	O
6	that	O
7	has	O
8	a	O
9	m	O
10	12	O
11	Vietnam	B-LOC
12	model	O
13	,	O
14	and	O
15	in	O
16	the	O
17	game	O
18	it	O
19	's	O
20	3	O
21	-	O
22	shot	O
23	burst	O
24	.	O

0	I	O
1	was	O
2	playing	O
3	a	O
4	video	O
5	game	O
6	that	O
7	has	O
8	a	O
9	m	O
10	16	O
11	Vietnam	B-LOC
12	model	O
13	,	O
14	and	O
15	in	O
16	the	O
17	game	O
18	it	O
19	's	O
20	4	O
21	-	O
22	shot	O
23	burst	O
24	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	what	O
3	the	O
4	s	O
5	difference	O
6	between	O
7	a	O
8	modern	O
9	m16	O
10	and	O
11	Vietnam	B-LOC
12	m	O
13	16	O
14	?	O

0	1	O
1	)	O
2	what	O
3	the	O
4	s	O
5	difference	O
6	between	O
7	a	O
8	modern	O
9	m16	O
10	and	O
11	Vietnam	B-LOC
12	m	O
13	17	O
14	?	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	did	O
3	Vietnam	B-LOC
4	m	O
5	16's	O
6	have	O
7	a	O
8	2	O
9	-	O
10	shot	O
11	burst	O
12	function	O
13	?	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	did	O
3	Vietnam	B-LOC
4	m	O
5	16's	O
6	have	O
7	a	O
8	2	O
9	-	O
10	shot	O
11	burst	O
12	function	O
13	?	O

0	To	O
1	save	O
2	money	O
3	Robert	B-PER
4	McNamara	I-PER
5	ordered	O
6	that	O
7	the	O
8	ammunition	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	new	O
12	M	O
13	-	O
14	16s	O
15	being	O
16	sent	O
17	to	O
18	SEA	O
19	in	O
20	the	O
21	early	O
22	60s	O
23	use	O
24	an	O
25	older	O
26	(	O
27	dirtier	O
28	)	O
29	type	O
30	of	O
31	gunpowder	O
32	meant	O
33	for	O
34	use	O
35	with	O
36	the	O
37	M	O
38	-	O
39	15	O
40	.	O

0	To	O
1	save	O
2	money	O
3	Robert	B-PER
4	McNamara	I-PER
5	ordered	O
6	that	O
7	the	O
8	ammunition	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	new	O
12	M	O
13	-	O
14	16s	O
15	being	O
16	sent	O
17	to	O
18	SEA	O
19	in	O
20	the	O
21	early	O
22	60s	O
23	use	O
24	an	O
25	older	O
26	(	O
27	dirtier	O
28	)	O
29	type	O
30	of	O
31	gunpowder	O
32	meant	O
33	for	O
34	use	O
35	with	O
36	the	O
37	M	O
38	-	O
39	13	O
40	.	O

0	Once	O
1	the	O
2	troops	O
3	started	O
4	cleaning	O
5	the	O
6	weapon	O
7	properly	O
8	(	O
9	even	O
10	with	O
11	the	O
12	dirtier	O
13	powder	O
14	)	O
15	the	O
16	Vietnam	B-LOC
17	era	O
18	M	O
19	-	O
20	19	O
21	turned	O
22	out	O
23	to	O
24	be	O
25	a	O
26	good	O
27	weapon	O
28	for	O
29	the	O
30	purpose	O
31	it	O
32	was	O
33	being	O
34	used	O
35	for	O
36	.	O

0	Once	O
1	the	O
2	troops	O
3	started	O
4	cleaning	O
5	the	O
6	weapon	O
7	properly	O
8	(	O
9	even	O
10	with	O
11	the	O
12	dirtier	O
13	powder	O
14	)	O
15	the	O
16	Vietnam	B-LOC
17	era	O
18	M	O
19	-	O
20	13	O
21	turned	O
22	out	O
23	to	O
24	be	O
25	a	O
26	good	O
27	weapon	O
28	for	O
29	the	O
30	purpose	O
31	it	O
32	was	O
33	being	O
34	used	O
35	for	O
36	.	O

0	1	O
1	)	O
2	modern	O
3	m	O
4	15	O
5	is	O
6	alright	O
7	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	modern	O
3	m	O
4	16	O
5	is	O
6	alright	O
7	.	O

0	Vietnam	B-LOC
1	m	O
2	15	O
3	used	O
4	to	O
5	clog	O
6	up	O
7	and	O
8	never	O
9	work	O
10	.	O

0	Vietnam	B-LOC
1	m	O
2	14	O
3	used	O
4	to	O
5	clog	O
6	up	O
7	and	O
8	never	O
9	work	O
10	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	All	O
3	M	O
4	13's	O
5	are	O
6	either	O
7	automatic	O
8	or	O
9	semi	O
10	automatic	O
11	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	All	O
3	M	O
4	12's	O
5	are	O
6	either	O
7	automatic	O
8	or	O
9	semi	O
10	automatic	O
11	.	O

0	No	O
1	one	O
2	uses	O
3	2	O
4	burst	O
5	.	O

0	No	O
1	one	O
2	uses	O
3	4	O
4	burst	O
5	.	O

0	modern	O
1	m	O
2	17	O
3	is	O
4	best	O

0	modern	O
1	m	O
2	17	O
3	is	O
4	best	O

0	1212	O
1	W.	O
2	Hubbard	O

0	1652	O
1	W.	O
2	Hubbard	O

0	Chicago	B-LOC
1	,	O
2	IL	B-LOC
3	60000	O

0	Chicago	B-LOC
1	,	O
2	IL	B-LOC
3	52528	O

0	312-622-2372	O
1	Tel	O

0	371-666-2372	O
1	Tel	O

0	$	O
1	4	O
2	Coronas	O
3	&	O
4	Heineken	O

0	$	O
1	4	O
2	Coronas	O
3	&	O
4	Heineken	O

0	When	O
1	Johnson	B-PER
2	deployed	O
3	troops	O
4	in	O
5	1763	O
6	he	O
7	was	O
8	advised	O
9	by	O
10	the	O
11	military	O
12	it	O
13	would	O
14	take	O
15	a	O
16	half	O
17	-	O
18	million	O
19	troops	O
20	about	O
21	ten	O
22	years	O
23	to	O
24	pacify	O
25	South	B-LOC
26	Vietnam	I-LOC
27	.	O

0	When	O
1	Johnson	B-PER
2	deployed	O
3	troops	O
4	in	O
5	1608	O
6	he	O
7	was	O
8	advised	O
9	by	O
10	the	O
11	military	O
12	it	O
13	would	O
14	take	O
15	a	O
16	half	O
17	-	O
18	million	O
19	troops	O
20	about	O
21	ten	O
22	years	O
23	to	O
24	pacify	O
25	South	B-LOC
26	Vietnam	I-LOC
27	.	O

0	He	O
1	refused	O
2	to	O
3	believe	O
4	them	O
5	and	O
6	ordered	O
7	the	O
8	military	O
9	to	O
10	win	O
11	the	O
12	war	O
13	within	O
14	two	O
15	to	O
16	three	O
17	years	O
18	(	O
19	before	O
20	the	O
21	next	O
22	election	O
23	in	O
24	2043	O
25	)	O
26	.	O

0	He	O
1	refused	O
2	to	O
3	believe	O
4	them	O
5	and	O
6	ordered	O
7	the	O
8	military	O
9	to	O
10	win	O
11	the	O
12	war	O
13	within	O
14	two	O
15	to	O
16	three	O
17	years	O
18	(	O
19	before	O
20	the	O
21	next	O
22	election	O
23	in	O
24	2196	O
25	)	O
26	.	O

0	Within	O
1	29	O
2	hours	O
3	every	O
4	Communist	O
5	assault	O
6	had	O
7	been	O
8	defeated	O
9	except	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	ancient	O
13	capital	O
14	of	O
15	Hue	B-LOC
16	.	O

0	Within	O
1	25	O
2	hours	O
3	every	O
4	Communist	O
5	assault	O
6	had	O
7	been	O
8	defeated	O
9	except	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	ancient	O
13	capital	O
14	of	O
15	Hue	B-LOC
16	.	O

0	will	O
1	only	O
2	be	O
3	in	O
4	Ho	B-LOC
5	chi	I-LOC
6	Minh	I-LOC
7	for	O
8	4	O
9	days	O
10	and	O
11	I	O
12	am	O
13	looking	O
14	for	O
15	a	O
16	2	O
17	day	O
18	or	O
19	2	O
20	day	O
21	trip	O
22	to	O
23	Mekong	B-LOC
24	delta	I-LOC
25	.	O

0	will	O
1	only	O
2	be	O
3	in	O
4	Ho	B-LOC
5	chi	I-LOC
6	Minh	I-LOC
7	for	O
8	4	O
9	days	O
10	and	O
11	I	O
12	am	O
13	looking	O
14	for	O
15	a	O
16	2	O
17	day	O
18	or	O
19	2	O
20	day	O
21	trip	O
22	to	O
23	Mekong	B-LOC
24	delta	I-LOC
25	.	O

0	The	O
1	are	O
2	located	O
3	right	O
4	at	O
5	259	O
6	De	O
7	Than	O
8	St.	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	heart	O
12	of	O
13	the	B-LOC
14	back	I-LOC
15	packer	I-LOC
16	district	I-LOC
17	.	O

0	The	O
1	are	O
2	located	O
3	right	O
4	at	O
5	200	O
6	De	O
7	Than	O
8	St.	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	heart	O
12	of	O
13	the	B-LOC
14	back	I-LOC
15	packer	I-LOC
16	district	I-LOC
17	.	O

0	tele	O
1	#	O
2	77947632521	O

0	tele	O
1	#	O
2	70756092752	O

0	After	O
1	a	O
2	person	O
3	dies	O
4	,	O
5	their	O
6	remains	O
7	are	O
8	“	O
9	waked	O
10	”	O
11	in	O
12	their	O
13	home	O
14	for	O
15	roughly	O
16	2	O
17	-	O
18	4	O
19	days	O
20	.	O

0	After	O
1	a	O
2	person	O
3	dies	O
4	,	O
5	their	O
6	remains	O
7	are	O
8	“	O
9	waked	O
10	”	O
11	in	O
12	their	O
13	home	O
14	for	O
15	roughly	O
16	2	O
17	-	O
18	4	O
19	days	O
20	.	O

0	Limerick	B-LOC
1	is	O
2	such	O
3	a	O
4	full	O
5	city	O
6	,	O
7	shopping	O
8	,	O
9	night	O
10	life	O
11	,	O
12	career	O
13	choices	O
14	,	O
15	social	O
16	choices	O
17	,	O
18	I	O
19	came	O
20	here	O
21	about	O
22	15	O
23	years	O
24	ago	O
25	for	O
26	college	O
27	.....	O
28	and	O
29	Orla	B-PER
30	got	O
31	it	O
32	spot	O
33	on	O
34	,	O
35	I	O
36	have	O
37	n't	O
38	left	O
39	,	O
40	nor	O
41	would	O
42	I	O
43	.	O

0	Limerick	B-LOC
1	is	O
2	such	O
3	a	O
4	full	O
5	city	O
6	,	O
7	shopping	O
8	,	O
9	night	O
10	life	O
11	,	O
12	career	O
13	choices	O
14	,	O
15	social	O
16	choices	O
17	,	O
18	I	O
19	came	O
20	here	O
21	about	O
22	11	O
23	years	O
24	ago	O
25	for	O
26	college	O
27	.....	O
28	and	O
29	Orla	B-PER
30	got	O
31	it	O
32	spot	O
33	on	O
34	,	O
35	I	O
36	have	O
37	n't	O
38	left	O
39	,	O
40	nor	O
41	would	O
42	I	O
43	.	O

0	Ireland	B-LOC
1	receives	O
2	a	O
3	lot	O
4	of	O
5	rain	O
6	,	O
7	with	O
8	certain	O
9	areas	O
10	getting	O
11	a	O
12	soaking	O
13	as	O
14	many	O
15	as	O
16	240	O
17	days	O
18	of	O
19	the	O
20	year	O
21	.	O

0	Ireland	B-LOC
1	receives	O
2	a	O
3	lot	O
4	of	O
5	rain	O
6	,	O
7	with	O
8	certain	O
9	areas	O
10	getting	O
11	a	O
12	soaking	O
13	as	O
14	many	O
15	as	O
16	298	O
17	days	O
18	of	O
19	the	O
20	year	O
21	.	O

0	In	O
1	summer	O
2	,	O
3	from	O
4	May	O
5	to	O
6	July	O
7	,	O
8	the	O
9	days	O
10	are	O
11	reasonably	O
12	warm	O
13	and	O
14	–	O
15	most	O
16	importantly	O
17	–	O
18	very	O
19	long	O
20	:	O
21	at	O
22	the	O
23	height	O
24	of	O
25	summer	O
26	you	O
27	wo	O
28	n’t	O
29	need	O
30	to	O
31	turn	O
32	on	O
33	lights	O
34	until	O
35	after	O
36	9	O
37	pm	O
38	.	O

0	In	O
1	summer	O
2	,	O
3	from	O
4	May	O
5	to	O
6	July	O
7	,	O
8	the	O
9	days	O
10	are	O
11	reasonably	O
12	warm	O
13	and	O
14	–	O
15	most	O
16	importantly	O
17	–	O
18	very	O
19	long	O
20	:	O
21	at	O
22	the	O
23	height	O
24	of	O
25	summer	O
26	you	O
27	wo	O
28	n’t	O
29	need	O
30	to	O
31	turn	O
32	on	O
33	lights	O
34	until	O
35	after	O
36	8	O
37	pm	O
38	.	O

0	Crowds	O
1	are	O
2	at	O
3	their	O
4	thinnest	O
5	,	O
6	but	O
7	many	O
8	of	O
9	the	O
10	country	O
11	’s	O
12	tourist	O
13	attractions	O
14	and	O
15	services	O
16	close	O
17	down	O
18	in	O
19	October	O
20	and	O
21	do	O
22	n’t	O
23	reopen	O
24	until	O
25	Easter	O
26	,	O
27	which	O
28	paradoxically	O
29	leaves	O
30	visitors	O
31	with	O
32	a	O
33	more	O
34	convincing	O
35	taste	O
36	of	O
37	how	O
38	Ireland	B-LOC
39	is	O
40	experienced	O
41	by	O
42	most	O
43	of	O
44	the	O
45	Irish	O
46	:	O
47	it	O
48	’s	O
49	cold	O
50	,	O
51	grey	O
52	and	O
53	dark	O
54	by	O
55	6	O
56	pm	O
57	,	O
58	but	O
59	there	O
60	’s	O
61	always	O
62	a	O
63	pub	O
64	to	O
65	escape	O
66	into	O
67	when	O
68	the	O
69	rain	O
70	starts	O
71	sheeting	O
72	down	O
73	.	O

0	Crowds	O
1	are	O
2	at	O
3	their	O
4	thinnest	O
5	,	O
6	but	O
7	many	O
8	of	O
9	the	O
10	country	O
11	’s	O
12	tourist	O
13	attractions	O
14	and	O
15	services	O
16	close	O
17	down	O
18	in	O
19	October	O
20	and	O
21	do	O
22	n’t	O
23	reopen	O
24	until	O
25	Easter	O
26	,	O
27	which	O
28	paradoxically	O
29	leaves	O
30	visitors	O
31	with	O
32	a	O
33	more	O
34	convincing	O
35	taste	O
36	of	O
37	how	O
38	Ireland	B-LOC
39	is	O
40	experienced	O
41	by	O
42	most	O
43	of	O
44	the	O
45	Irish	O
46	:	O
47	it	O
48	’s	O
49	cold	O
50	,	O
51	grey	O
52	and	O
53	dark	O
54	by	O
55	4	O
56	pm	O
57	,	O
58	but	O
59	there	O
60	’s	O
61	always	O
62	a	O
63	pub	O
64	to	O
65	escape	O
66	into	O
67	when	O
68	the	O
69	rain	O
70	starts	O
71	sheeting	O
72	down	O
73	.	O

0	We	O
1	only	O
2	had	O
3	a	O
4	few	O
5	sunny	O
6	days	O
7	this	O
8	summer	O
9	,	O
10	barely	O
11	20	O
12	C	O
13	on	O
14	a	O
15	few	O
16	occasions	O
17	,	O
18	more	O
19	like	O
20	14	O
21	C	O
22	most	O
23	days	O
24	.	O

0	We	O
1	only	O
2	had	O
3	a	O
4	few	O
5	sunny	O
6	days	O
7	this	O
8	summer	O
9	,	O
10	barely	O
11	22	O
12	C	O
13	on	O
14	a	O
15	few	O
16	occasions	O
17	,	O
18	more	O
19	like	O
20	14	O
21	C	O
22	most	O
23	days	O
24	.	O

0	We	O
1	are	O
2	taking	O
3	a	O
4	2	O
5	hour	O
6	flight	O
7	down	O
8	to	O
9	a	O
10	fancy	O
11	island	O
12	in	O
13	Florida	B-LOC
14	and	O
15	staying	O
16	only	O
17	2	O
18	days	O
19	.	O

0	We	O
1	are	O
2	taking	O
3	a	O
4	2	O
5	hour	O
6	flight	O
7	down	O
8	to	O
9	a	O
10	fancy	O
11	island	O
12	in	O
13	Florida	B-LOC
14	and	O
15	staying	O
16	only	O
17	2	O
18	days	O
19	.	O

0	After	O
1	the	O
2	sinking	O
3	of	O
4	the	O
5	Titanic	O
6	in	O
7	1727	O
8	,	O
9	was	O
10	there	O
11	a	O
12	law	O
13	made	O
14	so	O
15	that	O
16	ships	O
17	would	O
18	carry	O
19	enough	O
20	lifeboats	O
21	to	O
22	save	O
23	everybody	O
24	on	O
25	a	O
26	ship	O
27	if	O
28	it	O
29	was	O
30	sinking	O
31	?	O

0	After	O
1	the	O
2	sinking	O
3	of	O
4	the	O
5	Titanic	O
6	in	O
7	1599	O
8	,	O
9	was	O
10	there	O
11	a	O
12	law	O
13	made	O
14	so	O
15	that	O
16	ships	O
17	would	O
18	carry	O
19	enough	O
20	lifeboats	O
21	to	O
22	save	O
23	everybody	O
24	on	O
25	a	O
26	ship	O
27	if	O
28	it	O
29	was	O
30	sinking	O
31	?	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	ever	O
3	go	O
4	on	O
5	a	O
6	cruise	O
7	ship	O
8	,	O
9	you	O
10	will	O
11	be	O
12	required	O
13	to	O
14	attend	O
15	a	O
16	SOLAS	O
17	muster	O
18	drill	O
19	(	O
20	lifeboat	O
21	drill	O
22	)	O
23	within	O
24	19	O
25	hours	O
26	of	O
27	sailing	O
28	.	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	ever	O
3	go	O
4	on	O
5	a	O
6	cruise	O
7	ship	O
8	,	O
9	you	O
10	will	O
11	be	O
12	required	O
13	to	O
14	attend	O
15	a	O
16	SOLAS	O
17	muster	O
18	drill	O
19	(	O
20	lifeboat	O
21	drill	O
22	)	O
23	within	O
24	20	O
25	hours	O
26	of	O
27	sailing	O
28	.	O

0	104	O
1	years	O
2	ago	O
3	?	O

0	85	O
1	years	O
2	ago	O
3	?	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	I	O
3	tested	O
4	it	O
5	out	O
6	by	O
7	making	O
8	a	O
9	figure	O
10	boat	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	I	O
3	tested	O
4	it	O
5	out	O
6	by	O
7	making	O
8	a	O
9	figure	O
10	boat	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Is	O
3	there	O
4	any	O
5	cheap	O
6	way	O
7	to	O
8	give	O
9	it	O
10	a	O
11	shine	O
12	like	O
13	I	O
14	made	O
15	it	O
16	in	O
17	a	O
18	kiln	O
19	?	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Is	O
3	there	O
4	any	O
5	cheap	O
6	way	O
7	to	O
8	give	O
9	it	O
10	a	O
11	shine	O
12	like	O
13	I	O
14	made	O
15	it	O
16	in	O
17	a	O
18	kiln	O
19	?	O

0	On	O
1	the	O
2	bus	O
3	:	O
4	Get	O
5	on	O
6	Bus	O
7	77	O
8	going	O
9	toward	O
10	"	O
11	Porte	B-LOC
12	de	I-LOC
13	Vanves	I-LOC
14	"	O
15	.	O

0	On	O
1	the	O
2	bus	O
3	:	O
4	Get	O
5	on	O
6	Bus	O
7	102	O
8	going	O
9	toward	O
10	"	O
11	Porte	B-LOC
12	de	I-LOC
13	Vanves	I-LOC
14	"	O
15	.	O

0	Take	O
1	the	O
2	10	O
3	line	O
4	toward	O
5	"	O
6	Balard	B-LOC
7	"	O
8	until	O
9	the	O
10	"	B-LOC
11	Invalides	I-LOC
12	"	I-LOC
13	station	I-LOC
14	.	O

0	Take	O
1	the	O
2	7	O
3	line	O
4	toward	O
5	"	O
6	Balard	B-LOC
7	"	O
8	until	O
9	the	O
10	"	B-LOC
11	Invalides	I-LOC
12	"	I-LOC
13	station	I-LOC
14	.	O

0	Change	O
1	there	O
2	to	O
3	the	O
4	15	O
5	line	O
6	toward	O
7	"	O
8	Chatillon	B-LOC
9	Montrouge	I-LOC
10	"	O
11	and	O
12	take	O
13	it	O
14	until	O
15	the	O
16	"	B-LOC
17	Montparnasse	I-LOC
18	Bienvenue	I-LOC
19	"	I-LOC
20	station	I-LOC
21	.	O

0	Change	O
1	there	O
2	to	O
3	the	O
4	15	O
5	line	O
6	toward	O
7	"	O
8	Chatillon	B-LOC
9	Montrouge	I-LOC
10	"	O
11	and	O
12	take	O
13	it	O
14	until	O
15	the	O
16	"	B-LOC
17	Montparnasse	I-LOC
18	Bienvenue	I-LOC
19	"	I-LOC
20	station	I-LOC
21	.	O

0	Your	O
1	answer	O
2	does	O
3	n't	O
4	do	O
5	anything	O
6	but	O
7	remind	O
8	me	O
9	that	O
10	I	O
11	'm	O
12	going	O
13	to	O
14	be	O
15	$	O
16	25,000	O
17	in	O
18	debt	O
19	by	O
20	the	O
21	time	O
22	I	O
23	'm	O
24	24	O
25	.	O

0	Your	O
1	answer	O
2	does	O
3	n't	O
4	do	O
5	anything	O
6	but	O
7	remind	O
8	me	O
9	that	O
10	I	O
11	'm	O
12	going	O
13	to	O
14	be	O
15	$	O
16	25,000	O
17	in	O
18	debt	O
19	by	O
20	the	O
21	time	O
22	I	O
23	'm	O
24	20	O
25	.	O

0	I	O
1	guess	O
2	I	O
3	'm	O
4	extremely	O
5	fortunate	O
6	that	O
7	I	O
8	received	O
9	a	O
10	scholarship	O
11	which	O
12	paid	O
13	about	O
14	867	O
15	f	O
16	my	O
17	course	O
18	fees	O
19	through	O
20	my	O
21	degree	O
22	.	O

0	I	O
1	guess	O
2	I	O
3	'm	O
4	extremely	O
5	fortunate	O
6	that	O
7	I	O
8	received	O
9	a	O
10	scholarship	O
11	which	O
12	paid	O
13	about	O
14	843	O
15	f	O
16	my	O
17	course	O
18	fees	O
19	through	O
20	my	O
21	degree	O
22	.	O

0	People	O
1	have	O
2	been	O
3	fleeing	O
4	this	O
5	country	O
6	at	O
7	roughly	O
8	a	O
9	plane	O
10	load	O
11	per	O
12	week	O
13	for	O
14	the	O
15	past	O
16	17	O
17	+	O
18	years	O
19	,	O
20	so	O
21	it	O
22	's	O
23	not	O
24	anything	O
25	new	O
26	.	O

0	People	O
1	have	O
2	been	O
3	fleeing	O
4	this	O
5	country	O
6	at	O
7	roughly	O
8	a	O
9	plane	O
10	load	O
11	per	O
12	week	O
13	for	O
14	the	O
15	past	O
16	24	O
17	+	O
18	years	O
19	,	O
20	so	O
21	it	O
22	's	O
23	not	O
24	anything	O
25	new	O
26	.	O

0	689	O
1	f	O
2	jobs	O
3	are	O
4	n't	O
5	advertised	O
6	.	O

0	615	O
1	f	O
2	jobs	O
3	are	O
4	n't	O
5	advertised	O
6	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	16	O
3	years	O
4	old	O
5	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	14	O
3	years	O
4	old	O
5	.	O

0	My	O
1	parents	O
2	do	O
3	not	O
4	like	O
5	me	O
6	,	O
7	They	O
8	constantly	O
9	reassure	O
10	me	O
11	that	O
12	they	O
13	will	O
14	throw	O
15	me	O
16	out	O
17	of	O
18	home	O
19	when	O
20	I	O
21	turn	O
22	16	O
23	.	O

0	My	O
1	parents	O
2	do	O
3	not	O
4	like	O
5	me	O
6	,	O
7	They	O
8	constantly	O
9	reassure	O
10	me	O
11	that	O
12	they	O
13	will	O
14	throw	O
15	me	O
16	out	O
17	of	O
18	home	O
19	when	O
20	I	O
21	turn	O
22	14	O
23	.	O

0	I	O
1	think	O
2	1710	O
3	is	O
4	going	O
5	to	O
6	be	O
7	a	O
8	great	O
9	year	O
10	for	O
11	Fujairah	B-LOC
12	as	O
13	we	O
14	have	O
15	A	O
16	LOT	O
17	of	O
18	projects	O
19	to	O
20	be	O
21	done	O
22	by	O
23	1710	O
24	.	O

0	I	O
1	think	O
2	1898	O
3	is	O
4	going	O
5	to	O
6	be	O
7	a	O
8	great	O
9	year	O
10	for	O
11	Fujairah	B-LOC
12	as	O
13	we	O
14	have	O
15	A	O
16	LOT	O
17	of	O
18	projects	O
19	to	O
20	be	O
21	done	O
22	by	O
23	1898	O
24	.	O

0	And	O
1	now	O
2	they	O
3	are	O
4	finishing	O
5	a	O
6	road	O
7	between	O
8	Fujairah	B-LOC
9	and	O
10	Dubai	B-LOC
11	in	O
12	44	O
13	minutes	O
14	only	O
15	!	O

0	And	O
1	now	O
2	they	O
3	are	O
4	finishing	O
5	a	O
6	road	O
7	between	O
8	Fujairah	B-LOC
9	and	O
10	Dubai	B-LOC
11	in	O
12	51	O
13	minutes	O
14	only	O
15	!	O

0	So	O
1	,	O
2	no	O
3	it	O
4	is	O
5	not	O
6	as	O
7	good	O
8	as	O
9	Dubai	B-LOC
10	,	O
11	but	O
12	it	O
13	s	O
14	quieter	O
15	and	O
16	more	O
17	peaceful	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	you	O
21	can	O
22	still	O
23	go	O
24	to	O
25	Dubai	B-LOC
26	in	O
27	36	O
28	mins	O
29	.	O

0	So	O
1	,	O
2	no	O
3	it	O
4	is	O
5	not	O
6	as	O
7	good	O
8	as	O
9	Dubai	B-LOC
10	,	O
11	but	O
12	it	O
13	s	O
14	quieter	O
15	and	O
16	more	O
17	peaceful	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	you	O
21	can	O
22	still	O
23	go	O
24	to	O
25	Dubai	B-LOC
26	in	O
27	48	O
28	mins	O
29	.	O

0	Brass	O
1	melts	O
2	at	O
3	just	O
4	under	O
5	2127	O
6	F	O
7	which	O
8	is	O
9	a	O
10	bright	O
11	yellow	O
12	heat	O
13	,	O
14	not	O
15	red	O
16	hot	O
17	.	O

0	Brass	O
1	melts	O
2	at	O
3	just	O
4	under	O
5	1781	O
6	F	O
7	which	O
8	is	O
9	a	O
10	bright	O
11	yellow	O
12	heat	O
13	,	O
14	not	O
15	red	O
16	hot	O
17	.	O

0	What	O
1	sort	O
2	of	O
3	Hotel	O
4	could	O
5	I	O
6	expect	O
7	to	O
8	find	O
9	in	O
10	New	B-LOC
11	Delhi	I-LOC
12	/	O
13	Agra	B-LOC
14	/	O
15	Varanasi	B-LOC
16	for	O
17	rs	O
18	434	O
19	per	O
20	night	O
21	?	O

0	What	O
1	sort	O
2	of	O
3	Hotel	O
4	could	O
5	I	O
6	expect	O
7	to	O
8	find	O
9	in	O
10	New	B-LOC
11	Delhi	I-LOC
12	/	O
13	Agra	B-LOC
14	/	O
15	Varanasi	B-LOC
16	for	O
17	rs	O
18	550	O
19	per	O
20	night	O
21	?	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	looking	O
3	to	O
4	visit	O
5	India	B-LOC
6	with	O
7	some	O
8	mates	O
9	at	O
10	the	O
11	beginning	O
12	of	O
13	February	O
14	next	O
15	year	O
16	and	O
17	I	O
18	am	O
19	wandering	O
20	what	O
21	standard	O
22	of	O
23	accommodation	O
24	we	O
25	could	O
26	get	O
27	for	O
28	Rs	O
29	457	O
30	per	O
31	person	O
32	per	O
33	night	O
34	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	looking	O
3	to	O
4	visit	O
5	India	B-LOC
6	with	O
7	some	O
8	mates	O
9	at	O
10	the	O
11	beginning	O
12	of	O
13	February	O
14	next	O
15	year	O
16	and	O
17	I	O
18	am	O
19	wandering	O
20	what	O
21	standard	O
22	of	O
23	accommodation	O
24	we	O
25	could	O
26	get	O
27	for	O
28	Rs	O
29	451	O
30	per	O
31	person	O
32	per	O
33	night	O
34	.	O

0	There	O
1	would	O
2	be	O
3	four	O
4	of	O
5	us	O
6	so	O
7	we	O
8	would	O
9	probably	O
10	be	O
11	looking	O
12	at	O
13	2	O
14	twin	O
15	rooms	O
16	for	O
17	Rs	O
18	1007	O
19	,	O
20	close	O
21	to	O
22	the	O
23	centre	O
24	of	O
25	these	O
26	cities	O
27	.	O

0	There	O
1	would	O
2	be	O
3	four	O
4	of	O
5	us	O
6	so	O
7	we	O
8	would	O
9	probably	O
10	be	O
11	looking	O
12	at	O
13	2	O
14	twin	O
15	rooms	O
16	for	O
17	Rs	O
18	885	O
19	,	O
20	close	O
21	to	O
22	the	O
23	centre	O
24	of	O
25	these	O
26	cities	O
27	.	O

0	Rooms	O
1	start	O
2	from	O
3	400	O
4	per	O
5	double	O
6	.	O

0	Rooms	O
1	start	O
2	from	O
3	453	O
4	per	O
5	double	O
6	.	O

0	I	O
1	ve	O
2	paid	O
3	416	O
4	for	O
5	a	O
6	double	O
7	room	O
8	there	O
9	and	O
10	it	O
11	was	O
12	fine	O
13	and	O
14	clean	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	ve	O
2	paid	O
3	547	O
4	for	O
5	a	O
6	double	O
7	room	O
8	there	O
9	and	O
10	it	O
11	was	O
12	fine	O
13	and	O
14	clean	O
15	.	O

0	You	O
1	may	O
2	find	O
3	a	O
4	normal	O
5	budget	O
6	hotel	O
7	for	O
8	Rs	O
9	924	O
10	per	O
11	night	O
12	in	O
13	the	O
14	cities	O
15	you	O
16	mentioned	O
17	,	O
18	the	O
19	links	O
20	below	O
21	may	O
22	help	O
23	you	O
24	to	O
25	find	O
26	good	O
27	hotels	O
28	in	O
29	Delhi	B-LOC
30	and	O
31	Agra	B-LOC
32	.	O

0	You	O
1	may	O
2	find	O
3	a	O
4	normal	O
5	budget	O
6	hotel	O
7	for	O
8	Rs	O
9	882	O
10	per	O
11	night	O
12	in	O
13	the	O
14	cities	O
15	you	O
16	mentioned	O
17	,	O
18	the	O
19	links	O
20	below	O
21	may	O
22	help	O
23	you	O
24	to	O
25	find	O
26	good	O
27	hotels	O
28	in	O
29	Delhi	B-LOC
30	and	O
31	Agra	B-LOC
32	.	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	taking	O
4	my	O
5	4	O
6	and	O
7	4	O
8	yr	O
9	olds	O
10	.	O

0	I	O
1	will	O
2	be	O
3	taking	O
4	my	O
5	4	O
6	and	O
7	4	O
8	yr	O
9	olds	O
10	.	O

0	From	O
1	2308	O
2	onwards	O
3	,	O
4	from	O
5	its	O
6	inception	O
7	Disney	B-ORG
8	cruise	O
9	has	O
10	attracted	O
11	many	O
12	and	O
13	continue	O
14	to	O
15	attract	O
16	more	O
17	and	O
18	more	O
19	.	O

0	From	O
1	2246	O
2	onwards	O
3	,	O
4	from	O
5	its	O
6	inception	O
7	Disney	B-ORG
8	cruise	O
9	has	O
10	attracted	O
11	many	O
12	and	O
13	continue	O
14	to	O
15	attract	O
16	more	O
17	and	O
18	more	O
19	.	O

0	Disney	B-ORG
1	cruises	O
2	offer	O
3	22	O
4	-	O
5	hour	O
6	room	O
7	services	O
8	,	O
9	and	O
10	the	O
11	crews	O
12	are	O
13	ready	O
14	to	O
15	serve	O
16	you	O
17	the	O
18	way	O
19	you	O
20	like	O
21	.	O

0	Disney	B-ORG
1	cruises	O
2	offer	O
3	23	O
4	-	O
5	hour	O
6	room	O
7	services	O
8	,	O
9	and	O
10	the	O
11	crews	O
12	are	O
13	ready	O
14	to	O
15	serve	O
16	you	O
17	the	O
18	way	O
19	you	O
20	like	O
21	.	O

0	My	O
1	wife	O
2	and	O
3	I	O
4	,	O
5	in	O
6	our	O
7	49's	O
8	at	O
9	the	O
10	time	O
11	,	O
12	originally	O
13	planned	O
14	a	O
15	3	O
16	generation	O
17	trip	O
18	but	O
19	some	O
20	family	O
21	emergencies	O
22	caused	O
23	everyone	O
24	else	O
25	to	O
26	cancel	O
27	.	O

0	My	O
1	wife	O
2	and	O
3	I	O
4	,	O
5	in	O
6	our	O
7	62's	O
8	at	O
9	the	O
10	time	O
11	,	O
12	originally	O
13	planned	O
14	a	O
15	3	O
16	generation	O
17	trip	O
18	but	O
19	some	O
20	family	O
21	emergencies	O
22	caused	O
23	everyone	O
24	else	O
25	to	O
26	cancel	O
27	.	O

0	I	O
1	would	O
2	like	O
3	maybe	O
4	3	O
5	stalls	O
6	per	O
7	barn	O
8	so	O
9	make	O
10	sure	O
11	the	O
12	stalls	O
13	are	O
14	not	O
15	that	O
16	big	O
17	so	O
18	it	O
19	can	O
20	fit	O
21	.	O

0	I	O
1	would	O
2	like	O
3	maybe	O
4	4	O
5	stalls	O
6	per	O
7	barn	O
8	so	O
9	make	O
10	sure	O
11	the	O
12	stalls	O
13	are	O
14	not	O
15	that	O
16	big	O
17	so	O
18	it	O
19	can	O
20	fit	O
21	.	O

0	well	O
1	if	O
2	your	O
3	desired	O
4	boarding	O
5	station	O
6	comes	O
7	after	O
8	more	O
9	than	O
10	2	O
11	or	O
12	4	O
13	halts	O
14	of	O
15	the	O
16	actual	O
17	boarding	O
18	point	O
19	,	O
20	then	O
21	the	O
22	TC	O
23	will	O
24	cancel	O
25	you	O
26	ticket	O
27	and	O
28	allot	O
29	the	O
30	seat	O
31	to	O
32	others	O
33	.	O

0	well	O
1	if	O
2	your	O
3	desired	O
4	boarding	O
5	station	O
6	comes	O
7	after	O
8	more	O
9	than	O
10	2	O
11	or	O
12	2	O
13	halts	O
14	of	O
15	the	O
16	actual	O
17	boarding	O
18	point	O
19	,	O
20	then	O
21	the	O
22	TC	O
23	will	O
24	cancel	O
25	you	O
26	ticket	O
27	and	O
28	allot	O
29	the	O
30	seat	O
31	to	O
32	others	O
33	.	O

0	1	O
1	)	O
2	The	O
3	Italian	O
4	Renaissance	O
5	began	O
6	the	O
7	opening	O
8	phase	O
9	of	O
10	the	O
11	Renaissance	O
12	,	O
13	a	O
14	period	O
15	of	O
16	great	O
17	cultural	O
18	change	O
19	and	O
20	achievement	O
21	in	O
22	Europe	B-LOC
23	that	O
24	spanned	O
25	the	O
26	period	O
27	from	O
28	the	O
29	end	O
30	of	O
31	the	O
32	13th	O
33	century	O
34	to	O
35	about	O
36	1504	O
37	,	O
38	marking	O
39	the	O
40	transition	O
41	between	O
42	Medieval	O
43	and	O
44	Early	O
45	Modern	O
46	Europe	B-LOC
47	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	The	O
3	Italian	O
4	Renaissance	O
5	began	O
6	the	O
7	opening	O
8	phase	O
9	of	O
10	the	O
11	Renaissance	O
12	,	O
13	a	O
14	period	O
15	of	O
16	great	O
17	cultural	O
18	change	O
19	and	O
20	achievement	O
21	in	O
22	Europe	B-LOC
23	that	O
24	spanned	O
25	the	O
26	period	O
27	from	O
28	the	O
29	end	O
30	of	O
31	the	O
32	13th	O
33	century	O
34	to	O
35	about	O
36	1600	O
37	,	O
38	marking	O
39	the	O
40	transition	O
41	between	O
42	Medieval	O
43	and	O
44	Early	O
45	Modern	O
46	Europe	B-LOC
47	.	O

0	The	O
1	High	O
2	Renaissance	O
3	period	O
4	is	O
5	traditionally	O
6	taken	O
7	to	O
8	begin	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	1490s	O
12	,	O
13	with	O
14	Leonardo	B-PER
15	s	O
16	fresco	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	Last	O
20	Supper	O
21	in	O
22	Milan	B-LOC
23	and	O
24	the	O
25	death	O
26	of	O
27	Lorenzo	B-PER
28	de'	I-PER
29	Medici	I-PER
30	in	O
31	Florence	B-LOC
32	,	O
33	and	O
34	to	O
35	have	O
36	ended	O
37	in	O
38	1754	O
39	with	O
40	the	O
41	sacking	O
42	of	O
43	Rome	B-LOC
44	by	O
45	the	O
46	troops	O
47	of	O
48	Charles	B-PER
49	V	I-PER
50	.	O

0	The	O
1	High	O
2	Renaissance	O
3	period	O
4	is	O
5	traditionally	O
6	taken	O
7	to	O
8	begin	O
9	in	O
10	the	O
11	1490s	O
12	,	O
13	with	O
14	Leonardo	B-PER
15	s	O
16	fresco	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	Last	O
20	Supper	O
21	in	O
22	Milan	B-LOC
23	and	O
24	the	O
25	death	O
26	of	O
27	Lorenzo	B-PER
28	de'	I-PER
29	Medici	I-PER
30	in	O
31	Florence	B-LOC
32	,	O
33	and	O
34	to	O
35	have	O
36	ended	O
37	in	O
38	1774	O
39	with	O
40	the	O
41	sacking	O
42	of	O
43	Rome	B-LOC
44	by	O
45	the	O
46	troops	O
47	of	O
48	Charles	B-PER
49	V	I-PER
50	.	O

0	[	O
1	2	O
2	]	O
3	Over	O
4	the	O
5	last	O
6	twenty	O
7	years	O
8	,	O
9	use	O
10	of	O
11	the	O
12	term	O
13	has	O
14	been	O
15	frequently	O
16	criticized	O
17	by	O
18	academic	O
19	art	O
20	historians	O
21	for	O
22	over-simplifying	O
23	artistic	O
24	developments	O
25	,	O
26	ignoring	O
27	historical	O
28	context	O
29	,	O
30	and	O
31	focusing	O
32	only	O
33	on	O
34	a	O
35	few	O
36	iconic	O
37	works	O
38	.	O

0	[	O
1	2	O
2	]	O
3	Over	O
4	the	O
5	last	O
6	twenty	O
7	years	O
8	,	O
9	use	O
10	of	O
11	the	O
12	term	O
13	has	O
14	been	O
15	frequently	O
16	criticized	O
17	by	O
18	academic	O
19	art	O
20	historians	O
21	for	O
22	over-simplifying	O
23	artistic	O
24	developments	O
25	,	O
26	ignoring	O
27	historical	O
28	context	O
29	,	O
30	and	O
31	focusing	O
32	only	O
33	on	O
34	a	O
35	few	O
36	iconic	O
37	works	O
38	.	O

0	it	O
1	has	O
2	17	O
3	mega	O
4	pixel	O
5	camera	O
6	...	O
7	n	O
8	4	O
9	x	O
10	wide	O
11	optical	O
12	zoom	O
13	...	O

0	it	O
1	has	O
2	15	O
3	mega	O
4	pixel	O
5	camera	O
6	...	O
7	n	O
8	4	O
9	x	O
10	wide	O
11	optical	O
12	zoom	O
13	...	O

0	Olympus	B-ORG
1	X	O
2	-	O
3	868	O
4	14	O
5	Megapixel	O
6	Digital	O
7	Camera	O
8	has	O
9	filters	O
10	and	O
11	can	O
12	do	O
13	all	O
14	sorts	O
15	of	O
16	special	O
17	effects	O
18	.	O

0	Olympus	B-ORG
1	X	O
2	-	O
3	940	O
4	16	O
5	Megapixel	O
6	Digital	O
7	Camera	O
8	has	O
9	filters	O
10	and	O
11	can	O
12	do	O
13	all	O
14	sorts	O
15	of	O
16	special	O
17	effects	O
18	.	O

0	2	O
1	weeks	O
2	old	O
3	baby	O
4	budgie	O
5	alone	O
6	at	O
7	night	O
8	?	O

0	2	O
1	weeks	O
2	old	O
3	baby	O
4	budgie	O
5	alone	O
6	at	O
7	night	O
8	?	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	4	O
4	week	O
5	old	O
6	baby	O
7	budgie	O
8	and	O
9	I	O
10	noticed	O
11	that	O
12	his	O
13	/	O
14	her	O
15	mother	O
16	does	O
17	not	O
18	stay	O
19	with	O
20	him	O
21	in	O
22	the	O
23	nest	O
24	at	O
25	night	O
26	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	4	O
4	week	O
5	old	O
6	baby	O
7	budgie	O
8	and	O
9	I	O
10	noticed	O
11	that	O
12	his	O
13	/	O
14	her	O
15	mother	O
16	does	O
17	not	O
18	stay	O
19	with	O
20	him	O
21	in	O
22	the	O
23	nest	O
24	at	O
25	night	O
26	.	O

0	I	O
1	want	O
2	to	O
3	save	O
4	up	O
5	for	O
6	a	O
7	canon	B-ORG
8	t3i	O
9	,	O
10	around	O
11	684	O
12	-	O
13	800	O
14	+	O
15	:(	O

0	I	O
1	want	O
2	to	O
3	save	O
4	up	O
5	for	O
6	a	O
7	canon	B-ORG
8	t3i	O
9	,	O
10	around	O
11	870	O
12	-	O
13	800	O
14	+	O
15	:(	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	currently	O
3	14	O
4	and	O
5	I	O
6	get	O
7	about	O
8	20	O
9	dollars	O
10	a	O
11	week	O
12	for	O
13	lunch	O
14	,	O
15	sometimes	O
16	a	O
17	bit	O
18	more	O
19	,	O
20	I	O
21	plan	O
22	to	O
23	save	O
24	10	O
25	dollars	O
26	every	O
27	week	O
28	:)	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	currently	O
3	12	O
4	and	O
5	I	O
6	get	O
7	about	O
8	20	O
9	dollars	O
10	a	O
11	week	O
12	for	O
13	lunch	O
14	,	O
15	sometimes	O
16	a	O
17	bit	O
18	more	O
19	,	O
20	I	O
21	plan	O
22	to	O
23	save	O
24	12	O
25	dollars	O
26	every	O
27	week	O
28	:)	O

0	My	O
1	birthday	O
2	is	O
3	in	O
4	november	O
5	and	O
6	I	O
7	get	O
8	about	O
9	....	O
10	142	O
11	or	O
12	more	O
13	since	O
14	i	O
15	hate	O
16	my	O
17	dad	O
18	s	O
19	family	O
20	..	O
21	haha	O

0	My	O
1	birthday	O
2	is	O
3	in	O
4	november	O
5	and	O
6	I	O
7	get	O
8	about	O
9	....	O
10	152	O
11	or	O
12	more	O
13	since	O
14	i	O
15	hate	O
16	my	O
17	dad	O
18	s	O
19	family	O
20	..	O
21	haha	O

0	Chinese	O
1	new	O
2	year	O
3	~	O
4	331	O

0	Chinese	O
1	new	O
2	year	O
3	~	O
4	255	O

0	christmas	O
1	~	O
2	91	O

0	christmas	O
1	~	O
2	94	O

0	It	O
1	's	O
2	around	O
3	$	O
4	93	O
5	less	O
6	,	O
7	which	O
8	means	O
9	you	O
10	get	O
11	the	O
12	same	O
13	camera	O
14	but	O
15	quicker	O
16	!	O

0	It	O
1	's	O
2	around	O
3	$	O
4	85	O
5	less	O
6	,	O
7	which	O
8	means	O
9	you	O
10	get	O
11	the	O
12	same	O
13	camera	O
14	but	O
15	quicker	O
16	!	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	in	O
3	my	O
4	21's	O
5	and	O
6	currently	O
7	studying	O
8	in	O
9	France	B-LOC
10	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	in	O
3	my	O
4	16's	O
5	and	O
6	currently	O
7	studying	O
8	in	O
9	France	B-LOC
10	.	O

0	Best	O
1	way	O
2	to	O
3	change	O
4	35	O
5	mm	O
6	film	O
7	in	O
8	Holga	B-ORG
9	95	O
10	whilst	O
11	out	O
12	and	O
13	about	O
14	?	O

0	Best	O
1	way	O
2	to	O
3	change	O
4	30	O
5	mm	O
6	film	O
7	in	O
8	Holga	B-ORG
9	120	O
10	whilst	O
11	out	O
12	and	O
13	about	O
14	?	O

0	I	O
1	've	O
2	modified	O
3	my	O
4	Holga	B-ORG
5	120	O
6	to	O
7	take	O
8	34	O
9	mm	O
10	film	O
11	and	O
12	I	O
13	know	O
14	that	O
15	you	O
16	ca	O
17	n't	O
18	wind	O
19	the	O
20	film	O
21	back	O
22	,	O
23	you	O
24	have	O
25	to	O
26	open	O
27	the	O
28	back	O
29	of	O
30	the	O
31	camera	O
32	(	O
33	in	O
34	a	O
35	darkroom	O
36	)	O
37	to	O
38	rewind	O
39	the	O
40	film	O
41	.	O

0	I	O
1	've	O
2	modified	O
3	my	O
4	Holga	B-ORG
5	132	O
6	to	O
7	take	O
8	35	O
9	mm	O
10	film	O
11	and	O
12	I	O
13	know	O
14	that	O
15	you	O
16	ca	O
17	n't	O
18	wind	O
19	the	O
20	film	O
21	back	O
22	,	O
23	you	O
24	have	O
25	to	O
26	open	O
27	the	O
28	back	O
29	of	O
30	the	O
31	camera	O
32	(	O
33	in	O
34	a	O
35	darkroom	O
36	)	O
37	to	O
38	rewind	O
39	the	O
40	film	O
41	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	few	O
4	how	O
5	to	O
6	videos	O
7	for	O
8	DIY	O
9	35	O
10	mm	O
11	film	O
12	in	O
13	a	O
14	99	O
15	camera	O
16	on	O
17	my	O
18	YouTube	O
19	channel	O
20	:	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	few	O
4	how	O
5	to	O
6	videos	O
7	for	O
8	DIY	O
9	42	O
10	mm	O
11	film	O
12	in	O
13	a	O
14	120	O
15	camera	O
16	on	O
17	my	O
18	YouTube	O
19	channel	O
20	:	O

0	just	O
1	want	O
2	to	O
3	ask	O
4	..	O
5	i	O
6	have	O
7	an	O
8	nikon	B-ORG
9	dslr	O
10	..	O
11	i	O
12	m	O
13	wondering	O
14	why	O
15	if	O
16	i	O
17	zoom	O
18	my	O
19	picture	O
20	zoom	O
21	like	O
22	almost	O
23	200	O
24	-	O
25	280	O
26	percent	O
27	..	O
28	i	O
29	can	O
30	see	O
31	some	O
32	dead	O
33	pixel	O
34	...	O
35	is	O
36	there	O
37	something	O
38	wrong	O
39	with	O
40	my	O
41	camera	O
42	body	O
43	?	O

0	just	O
1	want	O
2	to	O
3	ask	O
4	..	O
5	i	O
6	have	O
7	an	O
8	nikon	B-ORG
9	dslr	O
10	..	O
11	i	O
12	m	O
13	wondering	O
14	why	O
15	if	O
16	i	O
17	zoom	O
18	my	O
19	picture	O
20	zoom	O
21	like	O
22	almost	O
23	212	O
24	-	O
25	300	O
26	percent	O
27	..	O
28	i	O
29	can	O
30	see	O
31	some	O
32	dead	O
33	pixel	O
34	...	O
35	is	O
36	there	O
37	something	O
38	wrong	O
39	with	O
40	my	O
41	camera	O
42	body	O
43	?	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Here	O
3	's	O
4	a	O
5	site	O
6	that	O
7	lists	O
8	world	O
9	cruises	O
10	including	O
11	prices	O
12	.	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Here	O
3	's	O
4	a	O
5	site	O
6	that	O
7	lists	O
8	world	O
9	cruises	O
10	including	O
11	prices	O
12	.	O

0	Various	O
1	world	O
2	cruises	O
3	from	O
4	most	O
5	of	O
6	the	O
7	major	O
8	cruise	O
9	lines	O
10	,	O
11	typically	O
12	102	O
13	days	O
14	in	O
15	duration	O
16	.	O

0	Various	O
1	world	O
2	cruises	O
3	from	O
4	most	O
5	of	O
6	the	O
7	major	O
8	cruise	O
9	lines	O
10	,	O
11	typically	O
12	94	O
13	days	O
14	in	O
15	duration	O
16	.	O

0	Prearranged	O
1	about	O
2	14	O
3	months	O
4	in	O
5	advance	O
6	as	O
7	the	O
8	cruise	O
9	lines	O
10	sell	O
11	segments	O
12	all	O
13	along	O
14	the	O
15	way	O
16	i.e	O
17	Transatlantic	O
18	to	O
19	London	B-LOC
20	(	O
21	England	B-LOC
22	)	O
23	,	O
24	England	B-LOC
25	to	O
26	Barcelona	B-LOC
27	(	O
28	Spain	B-LOC
29	)	O
30	,	O
31	Barcelona	B-LOC
32	to	O
33	Alexandria	B-LOC
34	(	O
35	Egypt	B-LOC
36	)	O
37	,	O
38	Egypt	B-LOC
39	to	O
40	India	B-LOC
41	via	O
42	Suez	B-LOC
43	canal	I-LOC
44	etc	O
45	.	O

0	Prearranged	O
1	about	O
2	22	O
3	months	O
4	in	O
5	advance	O
6	as	O
7	the	O
8	cruise	O
9	lines	O
10	sell	O
11	segments	O
12	all	O
13	along	O
14	the	O
15	way	O
16	i.e	O
17	Transatlantic	O
18	to	O
19	London	B-LOC
20	(	O
21	England	B-LOC
22	)	O
23	,	O
24	England	B-LOC
25	to	O
26	Barcelona	B-LOC
27	(	O
28	Spain	B-LOC
29	)	O
30	,	O
31	Barcelona	B-LOC
32	to	O
33	Alexandria	B-LOC
34	(	O
35	Egypt	B-LOC
36	)	O
37	,	O
38	Egypt	B-LOC
39	to	O
40	India	B-LOC
41	via	O
42	Suez	B-LOC
43	canal	I-LOC
44	etc	O
45	.	O

0	so	O
1	any	O
2	price	O
3	you	O
4	find	O
5	,	O
6	DOUBLE	O
7	IT	O
8	figure	O
9	,	O
10	$	O
11	47	O
12	K	O
13	at	O
14	least	O
15	.	O

0	so	O
1	any	O
2	price	O
3	you	O
4	find	O
5	,	O
6	DOUBLE	O
7	IT	O
8	figure	O
9	,	O
10	$	O
11	38	O
12	K	O
13	at	O
14	least	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	really	O
2	like	O
3	the	O
4	MIUI	O
5	,	O
6	but	O
7	a	O
8	process	O
9	crashes	O
10	repeatedly	O
11	about	O
12	every	O
13	4	O
14	seconds	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	really	O
2	like	O
3	the	O
4	MIUI	O
5	,	O
6	but	O
7	a	O
8	process	O
9	crashes	O
10	repeatedly	O
11	about	O
12	every	O
13	4	O
14	seconds	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	feel	O
2	X	O
3	-	O
4	BOX	O
5	is	O
6	a	O
7	very	O
8	smooth	O
9	system	O
10	i	O
11	own	O
12	it	O
13	like	O
14	2	O
15	years	O
16	,	O
17	it	O
18	s	O
19	very	O
20	compatible	O
21	to	O
22	previous	O
23	versions	O
24	and	O
25	mostly	O
26	important	O
27	i	O
28	was	O
29	very	O
30	comfortable	O
31	with	O
32	the	O
33	User	O
34	Interface	O
35	and	O
36	the	O
37	JOYSTICK	O
38	....	O
39	coz	O
40	you	O
41	do	O
42	nt	O
43	wan	O
44	a	O
45	hold	O
46	a	O
47	joystick	O
48	that	O
49	gives	O
50	you	O
51	discomfort	O
52	.	O

0	I	O
1	feel	O
2	X	O
3	-	O
4	BOX	O
5	is	O
6	a	O
7	very	O
8	smooth	O
9	system	O
10	i	O
11	own	O
12	it	O
13	like	O
14	2	O
15	years	O
16	,	O
17	it	O
18	s	O
19	very	O
20	compatible	O
21	to	O
22	previous	O
23	versions	O
24	and	O
25	mostly	O
26	important	O
27	i	O
28	was	O
29	very	O
30	comfortable	O
31	with	O
32	the	O
33	User	O
34	Interface	O
35	and	O
36	the	O
37	JOYSTICK	O
38	....	O
39	coz	O
40	you	O
41	do	O
42	nt	O
43	wan	O
44	a	O
45	hold	O
46	a	O
47	joystick	O
48	that	O
49	gives	O
50	you	O
51	discomfort	O
52	.	O

0	I	O
1	do	O
2	n't	O
3	know	O
4	about	O
5	the	O
6	playstation	O
7	situation	O
8	but	O
9	I	O
10	do	O
11	know	O
12	that	O
13	Microsoft	B-ORG
14	has	O
15	said	O
16	they	O
17	do	O
18	n't	O
19	see	O
20	the	O
21	Xbox	O
22	351	O
23	as	O
24	being	O
25	even	O
26	halfway	O
27	through	O
28	its	O
29	lifetime	O
30	.	O

0	I	O
1	do	O
2	n't	O
3	know	O
4	about	O
5	the	O
6	playstation	O
7	situation	O
8	but	O
9	I	O
10	do	O
11	know	O
12	that	O
13	Microsoft	B-ORG
14	has	O
15	said	O
16	they	O
17	do	O
18	n't	O
19	see	O
20	the	O
21	Xbox	O
22	361	O
23	as	O
24	being	O
25	even	O
26	halfway	O
27	through	O
28	its	O
29	lifetime	O
30	.	O

0	I	O
1	used	O
2	to	O
3	live	O
4	in	O
5	London	B-LOC
6	for	O
7	6	O
8	months	O
9	and	O
10	it	O
11	's	O
12	by	O
13	far	O
14	one	O
15	of	O
16	my	O
17	favorite	O
18	places	O
19	to	O
20	be	O
21	in	O
22	the	O
23	world	O
24	(	O
25	I	O
26	've	O
27	been	O
28	to	O
29	45	O
30	countries	O
31	in	O
32	4	O
33	years	O
34	)	O
35	.	O

0	I	O
1	used	O
2	to	O
3	live	O
4	in	O
5	London	B-LOC
6	for	O
7	6	O
8	months	O
9	and	O
10	it	O
11	's	O
12	by	O
13	far	O
14	one	O
15	of	O
16	my	O
17	favorite	O
18	places	O
19	to	O
20	be	O
21	in	O
22	the	O
23	world	O
24	(	O
25	I	O
26	've	O
27	been	O
28	to	O
29	44	O
30	countries	O
31	in	O
32	5	O
33	years	O
34	)	O
35	.	O

0	I	O
1	lived	O
2	there	O
3	for	O
4	7	O
5	months	O
6	.	O

0	I	O
1	lived	O
2	there	O
3	for	O
4	10	O
5	months	O
6	.	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	this	O
3	at	O
4	age	O
5	11	O
6	in	O
7	Champagne	B-LOC
8	,	O
9	France	B-LOC
10	and	O
11	it	O
12	was	O
13	the	O
14	most	O
15	amazing	O
16	experice	O
17	of	O
18	my	O
19	upbringing	O
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	this	O
3	at	O
4	age	O
5	12	O
6	in	O
7	Champagne	B-LOC
8	,	O
9	France	B-LOC
10	and	O
11	it	O
12	was	O
13	the	O
14	most	O
15	amazing	O
16	experice	O
17	of	O
18	my	O
19	upbringing	O
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	need	O
2	one	O
3	horse	O
4	transported	O
5	to	O
6	shows	O
7	throughout	O
8	the	O
9	2012	O
10	show	O
11	season	O
12	,	O
13	and	O
14	the	O
15	location	O
16	is	O
17	about	O
18	2	O
19	hours	O
20	away	O
21	from	O
22	where	O
23	I	O
24	live	O
25	.	O

0	I	O
1	need	O
2	one	O
3	horse	O
4	transported	O
5	to	O
6	shows	O
7	throughout	O
8	the	O
9	1949	O
10	show	O
11	season	O
12	,	O
13	and	O
14	the	O
15	location	O
16	is	O
17	about	O
18	3	O
19	hours	O
20	away	O
21	from	O
22	where	O
23	I	O
24	live	O
25	.	O

0	2	O

0	2	O

0	2	O

0	2	O

0	I	O
1	applied	O
2	to	O
3	get	O
4	a	O
5	student	O
6	visa	O
7	to	O
8	study	O
9	in	O
10	Canada	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	I	O
13	received	O
14	one	O
15	that	O
16	is	O
17	valid	O
18	until	O
19	October	O
20	of	O
21	1967	O
22	.	O

0	I	O
1	applied	O
2	to	O
3	get	O
4	a	O
5	student	O
6	visa	O
7	to	O
8	study	O
9	in	O
10	Canada	B-LOC
11	,	O
12	I	O
13	received	O
14	one	O
15	that	O
16	is	O
17	valid	O
18	until	O
19	October	O
20	of	O
21	1855	O
22	.	O

0	Problem	O
1	is	O
2	,	O
3	for	O
4	some	O
5	reason	O
6	,	O
7	the	O
8	visa	O
9	process	O
10	took	O
11	longer	O
12	than	O
13	it	O
14	should	O
15	,	O
16	thus	O
17	I	O
18	missed	O
19	school	O
20	this	O
21	semester	O
22	(	O
23	visa	O
24	was	O
25	issued	O
26	to	O
27	me	O
28	about	O
29	25	O
30	days	O
31	after	O
32	school	O
33	started	O
34	so	O
35	I	O
36	could	O
37	n't	O
38	attend	O
39	)	O
40	,	O
41	now	O
42	I	O
43	no	O
44	longer	O
45	want	O
46	to	O
47	go	O
48	into	O
49	that	O
50	school	O
51	(	O
52	because	O
53	they	O
54	only	O
55	would	O
56	accept	O
57	me	O
58	again	O
59	on	O
60	September	O
61	of	O
62	2181	O
63	)	O
64	,	O
65	I	O
66	found	O
67	a	O
68	school	O
69	that	O
70	accepted	O
71	me	O
72	for	O
73	may	O
74	2181	O
75	,	O
76	can	O
77	I	O
78	use	O
79	the	O
80	same	O
81	visa	O
82	that	O
83	was	O
84	issued	O
85	to	O
86	me	O
87	?	O

0	Problem	O
1	is	O
2	,	O
3	for	O
4	some	O
5	reason	O
6	,	O
7	the	O
8	visa	O
9	process	O
10	took	O
11	longer	O
12	than	O
13	it	O
14	should	O
15	,	O
16	thus	O
17	I	O
18	missed	O
19	school	O
20	this	O
21	semester	O
22	(	O
23	visa	O
24	was	O
25	issued	O
26	to	O
27	me	O
28	about	O
29	25	O
30	days	O
31	after	O
32	school	O
33	started	O
34	so	O
35	I	O
36	could	O
37	n't	O
38	attend	O
39	)	O
40	,	O
41	now	O
42	I	O
43	no	O
44	longer	O
45	want	O
46	to	O
47	go	O
48	into	O
49	that	O
50	school	O
51	(	O
52	because	O
53	they	O
54	only	O
55	would	O
56	accept	O
57	me	O
58	again	O
59	on	O
60	September	O
61	of	O
62	1752	O
63	)	O
64	,	O
65	I	O
66	found	O
67	a	O
68	school	O
69	that	O
70	accepted	O
71	me	O
72	for	O
73	may	O
74	1752	O
75	,	O
76	can	O
77	I	O
78	use	O
79	the	O
80	same	O
81	visa	O
82	that	O
83	was	O
84	issued	O
85	to	O
86	me	O
87	?	O

0	He	O
1	always	O
2	hugs	O
3	me	O
4	when	O
5	he	O
6	comes	O
7	,	O
8	but	O
9	he	O
10	gave	O
11	me	O
12	at	O
13	least	O
14	7	O
15	tight	O
16	,	O
17	long	O
18	,	O
19	back	O
20	rubbing	O
21	hugs	O
22	while	O
23	he	O
24	was	O
25	there	O
26	.	O

0	He	O
1	always	O
2	hugs	O
3	me	O
4	when	O
5	he	O
6	comes	O
7	,	O
8	but	O
9	he	O
10	gave	O
11	me	O
12	at	O
13	least	O
14	6	O
15	tight	O
16	,	O
17	long	O
18	,	O
19	back	O
20	rubbing	O
21	hugs	O
22	while	O
23	he	O
24	was	O
25	there	O
26	.	O

0	He	O
1	told	O
2	me	O
3	to	O
4	remember	O
5	to	O
6	call	O
7	like	O
8	4	O
9	times	O
10	before	O
11	he	O
12	left	O
13	.	O

0	He	O
1	told	O
2	me	O
3	to	O
4	remember	O
5	to	O
6	call	O
7	like	O
8	2	O
9	times	O
10	before	O
11	he	O
12	left	O
13	.	O

0	I	O
1	've	O
2	known	O
3	the	O
4	guy	O
5	for	O
6	about	O
7	7	O
8	years	O
9	.	O

0	I	O
1	've	O
2	known	O
3	the	O
4	guy	O
5	for	O
6	about	O
7	7	O
8	years	O
9	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	20	O
3	,	O
4	so	O
5	yeah	O
6	we	O
7	were	O
8	both	O
9	kids	O
10	when	O
11	we	O
12	knew	O
13	each	O
14	other	O
15	!	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	16	O
3	,	O
4	so	O
5	yeah	O
6	we	O
7	were	O
8	both	O
9	kids	O
10	when	O
11	we	O
12	knew	O
13	each	O
14	other	O
15	!	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	seen	O
3	horses	O
4	Loose	O
5	Nails	O
6	On	O
7	there	O
8	Own	O
9	And	O
10	do	O
11	just	O
12	fine	O
13	with	O
14	ONE	O
15	nail	O
16	gone	O
17	Now	O
18	if	O
19	he	O
20	had	O
21	left	O
22	out	O
23	2	O
24	or	O
25	4	O
26	I	O
27	would	O
28	be	O
29	wondering	O
30	to	O
31	...	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	seen	O
3	horses	O
4	Loose	O
5	Nails	O
6	On	O
7	there	O
8	Own	O
9	And	O
10	do	O
11	just	O
12	fine	O
13	with	O
14	ONE	O
15	nail	O
16	gone	O
17	Now	O
18	if	O
19	he	O
20	had	O
21	left	O
22	out	O
23	2	O
24	or	O
25	4	O
26	I	O
27	would	O
28	be	O
29	wondering	O
30	to	O
31	...	O

0	Well	O
1	8	O
2	weeks	O
3	Later	O
4	when	O
5	he	O
6	came	O
7	back	O
8	out	O
9	He	O
10	was	O
11	again	O
12	working	O
13	on	O
14	my	O
15	mare	O
16	s	O
17	front	O
18	Foot	O
19	and	O
20	I	O
21	looked	O
22	Down	O
23	and	O
24	Yeah	O
25	he	O
26	had	O
27	Wholes	O
28	In	O
29	his	O
30	pants	O
31	In	O
32	the	O
33	wrong	O
34	places	O
35	I	O
36	bust	O
37	out	O
38	Laughing	O
39	and	O
40	He	O
41	was	O
42	like	O
43	what	O
44	???	O

0	Well	O
1	8	O
2	weeks	O
3	Later	O
4	when	O
5	he	O
6	came	O
7	back	O
8	out	O
9	He	O
10	was	O
11	again	O
12	working	O
13	on	O
14	my	O
15	mare	O
16	s	O
17	front	O
18	Foot	O
19	and	O
20	I	O
21	looked	O
22	Down	O
23	and	O
24	Yeah	O
25	he	O
26	had	O
27	Wholes	O
28	In	O
29	his	O
30	pants	O
31	In	O
32	the	O
33	wrong	O
34	places	O
35	I	O
36	bust	O
37	out	O
38	Laughing	O
39	and	O
40	He	O
41	was	O
42	like	O
43	what	O
44	???	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	a	O
3	21	O
4	something	O
5	gay	O
6	black	O
7	male	O
8	and	O
9	I	O
10	am	O
11	looking	O
12	for	O
13	suggestions	O
14	on	O
15	neighborhoods	O
16	close	O
17	to	O
18	the	O
19	downtown	O
20	Toronto	B-LOC
21	area	O
22	.	O

0	I	O
1	am	O
2	a	O
3	17	O
4	something	O
5	gay	O
6	black	O
7	male	O
8	and	O
9	I	O
10	am	O
11	looking	O
12	for	O
13	suggestions	O
14	on	O
15	neighborhoods	O
16	close	O
17	to	O
18	the	O
19	downtown	O
20	Toronto	B-LOC
21	area	O
22	.	O

0	A	O
1	normal	O
2	processing	O
3	time	O
4	,	O
5	unless	O
6	you	O
7	have	O
8	an	O
9	advanced	O
10	degree	O
11	or	O
12	a	O
13	"	O
14	specified	O
15	"	O
16	skill	O
17	is	O
18	from	O
19	3	O
20	-	O
21	3	O
22	years	O
23	.	O

0	A	O
1	normal	O
2	processing	O
3	time	O
4	,	O
5	unless	O
6	you	O
7	have	O
8	an	O
9	advanced	O
10	degree	O
11	or	O
12	a	O
13	"	O
14	specified	O
15	"	O
16	skill	O
17	is	O
18	from	O
19	3	O
20	-	O
21	4	O
22	years	O
23	.	O

0	IF	O
1	you	O
2	have	O
3	NOT	O
4	begun	O
5	the	O
6	Application	O
7	process's	O
8	NOW	O
9	<	O
10	you	O
11	are	O
12	about	O
13	2	O
14	to	O
15	4	O
16	years	O
17	away	O
18	from	O
19	being	O
20	approved	O
21	by	O
22	Immigration	O
23	Canada	B-LOC
24	.	O

0	IF	O
1	you	O
2	have	O
3	NOT	O
4	begun	O
5	the	O
6	Application	O
7	process's	O
8	NOW	O
9	<	O
10	you	O
11	are	O
12	about	O
13	2	O
14	to	O
15	2	O
16	years	O
17	away	O
18	from	O
19	being	O
20	approved	O
21	by	O
22	Immigration	O
23	Canada	B-LOC
24	.	O

0	Can	O
1	somebody	O
2	give	O
3	me	O
4	the	O
5	names	O
6	some	O
7	collages	O
8	that	O
9	do	O
10	post	O
11	17	O
12	(	O
13	degrees	O
14	or	O
15	foundation	O
16	degrees	O
17	)	O
18	in	O
19	either	O
20	:	O

0	Can	O
1	somebody	O
2	give	O
3	me	O
4	the	O
5	names	O
6	some	O
7	collages	O
8	that	O
9	do	O
10	post	O
11	19	O
12	(	O
13	degrees	O
14	or	O
15	foundation	O
16	degrees	O
17	)	O
18	in	O
19	either	O
20	:	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	n't	O
3	know	O
4	that	O
5	I	O
6	did	O
7	n't	O
8	register	O
9	him	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	ridiculous	O
13	amount	O
14	of	O
15	paperwork	O
16	I	O
17	had	O
18	filled	O
19	out	O
20	in	O
21	the	O
22	hospital	O
23	and	O
24	was	O
25	supposed	O
26	to	O
27	go	O
28	to	O
29	city	O
30	hall	O
31	within	O
32	82	O
33	days	O
34	.	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	n't	O
3	know	O
4	that	O
5	I	O
6	did	O
7	n't	O
8	register	O
9	him	O
10	in	O
11	the	O
12	ridiculous	O
13	amount	O
14	of	O
15	paperwork	O
16	I	O
17	had	O
18	filled	O
19	out	O
20	in	O
21	the	O
22	hospital	O
23	and	O
24	was	O
25	supposed	O
26	to	O
27	go	O
28	to	O
29	city	O
30	hall	O
31	within	O
32	109	O
33	days	O
34	.	O

0	For	O
1	$	O
2	45	O
3	you	O
4	can	O
5	even	O
6	have	O
7	it	O
8	expedited	O
9	and	O
10	will	O
11	get	O
12	in	O
13	three	O
14	business	O
15	days	O
16	or	O
17	your	O
18	money	O
19	back	O
20	.	O

0	For	O
1	$	O
2	68	O
3	you	O
4	can	O
5	even	O
6	have	O
7	it	O
8	expedited	O
9	and	O
10	will	O
11	get	O
12	in	O
13	three	O
14	business	O
15	days	O
16	or	O
17	your	O
18	money	O
19	back	O
20	.	O

0	My	O
1	parents	O
2	did	O
3	n't	O
4	send	O
5	for	O
6	my	O
7	birth	O
8	certificate	O
9	until	O
10	I	O
11	was	O
12	14	O
13	and	O
14	needed	O
15	it	O
16	for	O
17	summer	O
18	employment	O
19	.	O

0	My	O
1	parents	O
2	did	O
3	n't	O
4	send	O
5	for	O
6	my	O
7	birth	O
8	certificate	O
9	until	O
10	I	O
11	was	O
12	18	O
13	and	O
14	needed	O
15	it	O
16	for	O
17	summer	O
18	employment	O
19	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	When	O
3	you	O
4	get	O
5	the	O
6	bird	O
7	,	O
8	place	O
9	him	O
10	or	O
11	her	O
12	or	O
13	them	O
14	in	O
15	the	O
16	cage	O
17	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	When	O
3	you	O
4	get	O
5	the	O
6	bird	O
7	,	O
8	place	O
9	him	O
10	or	O
11	her	O
12	or	O
13	them	O
14	in	O
15	the	O
16	cage	O
17	.	O

0	4	O
1	)	O
2	After	O
3	about	O
4	day	O
5	2	O
6	,	O
7	they	O
8	will	O
9	start	O
10	to	O
11	eating	O
12	the	O
13	millet	O
14	spray	O
15	from	O
16	your	O
17	hand	O
18	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	After	O
3	about	O
4	day	O
5	2	O
6	,	O
7	they	O
8	will	O
9	start	O
10	to	O
11	eating	O
12	the	O
13	millet	O
14	spray	O
15	from	O
16	your	O
17	hand	O
18	.	O

0	I	O
1	m	O
2	around	O
3	5	O
4	'	O
5	2	O
6	-	O
7	5	O
8	'	O
9	4	O
10	,	O
11	14	O
12	years	O
13	old	O
14	and	O
15	i	O
16	m	O
17	wondering	O
18	what	O
19	size	O
20	horse	O
21	i	O
22	'll	O
23	need	O
24	that	O
25	i	O
26	wo	O
27	nt	O
28	grow	O
29	out	O
30	of	O
31	quickly	O
32	?	O

0	I	O
1	m	O
2	around	O
3	5	O
4	'	O
5	2	O
6	-	O
7	5	O
8	'	O
9	4	O
10	,	O
11	14	O
12	years	O
13	old	O
14	and	O
15	i	O
16	m	O
17	wondering	O
18	what	O
19	size	O
20	horse	O
21	i	O
22	'll	O
23	need	O
24	that	O
25	i	O
26	wo	O
27	nt	O
28	grow	O
29	out	O
30	of	O
31	quickly	O
32	?	O

0	But	O
1	I	O
2	would	O
3	go	O
4	for	O
5	the	O
6	base	O
7	number	O
8	of	O
9	19	O
10	hh	O
11	.	O

0	But	O
1	I	O
2	would	O
3	go	O
4	for	O
5	the	O
6	base	O
7	number	O
8	of	O
9	11	O
10	hh	O
11	.	O

0	I	O
1	got	O
2	my	O
3	horse	O
4	when	O
5	I	O
6	was	O
7	12	O
8	and	O
9	I	O
10	was	O
11	already	O
12	5	O
13	'	O
14	11	O
15	-	O
16	5	O
17	'	O
18	10	O
19	,	O
20	thankfully	O
21	I	O
22	stopped	O
23	growing	O
24	when	O
25	I	O
26	hit	O
27	5	O
28	'	O
29	11	O
30	"	O
31	but	O
32	my	O
33	horse	O
34	is	O
35	about	O
36	16.2	O
37	or	O
38	16.3	O
39	hh	O
40	,	O
41	TB	O
42	.	O

0	I	O
1	got	O
2	my	O
3	horse	O
4	when	O
5	I	O
6	was	O
7	12	O
8	and	O
9	I	O
10	was	O
11	already	O
12	5	O
13	'	O
14	9	O
15	-	O
16	5	O
17	'	O
18	8	O
19	,	O
20	thankfully	O
21	I	O
22	stopped	O
23	growing	O
24	when	O
25	I	O
26	hit	O
27	5	O
28	'	O
29	11	O
30	"	O
31	but	O
32	my	O
33	horse	O
34	is	O
35	about	O
36	16.2	O
37	or	O
38	16.3	O
39	hh	O
40	,	O
41	TB	O
42	.	O

0	i	O
1	'm	O
2	3	O
3	'	O
4	3	O
5	-	O
6	4	O
7	"	O
8	and	O
9	am	O
10	21	O
11	well	O
12	will	O
13	be	O
14	in	O
15	Nov	O
16	and	O
17	my	O
18	horse	O
19	is	O
20	14.2	O
21	hh	O
22	and	O
23	she	O
24	's	O
25	perfect	O
26	size	O
27	for	O
28	me	O
29	i	O
30	can	O
31	hop	O
32	right	O
33	on	O
34	with	O
35	no	O
36	mounting	O
37	block	O
38	.....	O
39	only	O
40	with	O
41	a	O
42	saddle	O
43	though	O
44	haha	O
45	i	O
46	ca	O
47	n't	O
48	bareback	O
49	,	O
50	not	O
51	yet	O

0	i	O
1	'm	O
2	5	O
3	'	O
4	4	O
5	-	O
6	4	O
7	"	O
8	and	O
9	am	O
10	21	O
11	well	O
12	will	O
13	be	O
14	in	O
15	Nov	O
16	and	O
17	my	O
18	horse	O
19	is	O
20	14.2	O
21	hh	O
22	and	O
23	she	O
24	's	O
25	perfect	O
26	size	O
27	for	O
28	me	O
29	i	O
30	can	O
31	hop	O
32	right	O
33	on	O
34	with	O
35	no	O
36	mounting	O
37	block	O
38	.....	O
39	only	O
40	with	O
41	a	O
42	saddle	O
43	though	O
44	haha	O
45	i	O
46	ca	O
47	n't	O
48	bareback	O
49	,	O
50	not	O
51	yet	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	Do	O
3	n't	O
4	want	O
5	to	O
6	grow	O
7	out	O
8	of	O
9	it	O
10	quickly	O
11	get	O
12	a	O
13	17	O
14	'	O
15	2	O
16	..	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	Do	O
3	n't	O
4	want	O
5	to	O
6	grow	O
7	out	O
8	of	O
9	it	O
10	quickly	O
11	get	O
12	a	O
13	13	O
14	'	O
15	2	O
16	..	O

0	You	O
1	could	O
2	also	O
3	just	O
4	wait	O
5	until	O
6	the	O
7	rat	O
8	passes	O
9	out	O
10	for	O
11	about	O
12	2	O
13	minute	O
14	and	O
15	them	O
16	feed	O
17	it	O
18	-	O
19	at	O
20	this	O
21	point	O
22	,	O
23	it	O
24	could	O
25	still	O
26	have	O
27	a	O
28	bit	O
29	of	O
30	a	O
31	heart	O
32	beat	O
33	and	O
34	be	O
35	slightly	O
36	still	O
37	alive	O
38	.	O

0	You	O
1	could	O
2	also	O
3	just	O
4	wait	O
5	until	O
6	the	O
7	rat	O
8	passes	O
9	out	O
10	for	O
11	about	O
12	2	O
13	minute	O
14	and	O
15	them	O
16	feed	O
17	it	O
18	-	O
19	at	O
20	this	O
21	point	O
22	,	O
23	it	O
24	could	O
25	still	O
26	have	O
27	a	O
28	bit	O
29	of	O
30	a	O
31	heart	O
32	beat	O
33	and	O
34	be	O
35	slightly	O
36	still	O
37	alive	O
38	.	O

0	Yes	O
1	I	O
2	've	O
3	had	O
4	50	O
5	different	O
6	kinds	O
7	of	O
8	rodents	O
9	and	O
10	two	O
11	were	O
12	dwarf	O
13	hamsters	O
14	they	O
15	flatten	O
16	into	O
17	a	O
18	pancake	O
19	and	O
20	slide	O
21	right	O
22	through	O
23	the	O
24	bars	O
25	and	O
26	are	O
27	able	O
28	to	O
29	open	O
30	the	O
31	door	O
32	so	O
33	yes	O
34	a	O
35	plastic	O
36	cage	O
37	will	O
38	be	O
39	good	O

0	Yes	O
1	I	O
2	've	O
3	had	O
4	44	O
5	different	O
6	kinds	O
7	of	O
8	rodents	O
9	and	O
10	two	O
11	were	O
12	dwarf	O
13	hamsters	O
14	they	O
15	flatten	O
16	into	O
17	a	O
18	pancake	O
19	and	O
20	slide	O
21	right	O
22	through	O
23	the	O
24	bars	O
25	and	O
26	are	O
27	able	O
28	to	O
29	open	O
30	the	O
31	door	O
32	so	O
33	yes	O
34	a	O
35	plastic	O
36	cage	O
37	will	O
38	be	O
39	good	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	counted	O
3	around	O
4	25	O
5	of	O
6	them	O
7	and	O
8	they	O
9	currently	O
10	reside	O
11	in	O
12	a	O
13	19	O
14	gallon	O
15	tank	O
16	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	counted	O
3	around	O
4	25	O
5	of	O
6	them	O
7	and	O
8	they	O
9	currently	O
10	reside	O
11	in	O
12	a	O
13	23	O
14	gallon	O
15	tank	O
16	.	O

0	Feed	O
1	the	O
2	babies	O
3	2	O
4	-	O
5	4	O
6	times	O
7	a	O
8	day	O
9	with	O
10	flakes	O
11	.	O

0	Feed	O
1	the	O
2	babies	O
3	4	O
4	-	O
5	4	O
6	times	O
7	a	O
8	day	O
9	with	O
10	flakes	O
11	.	O

0	82	O
1	%	O
2	SCAM	O
3	.	O

0	96	O
1	%	O
2	SCAM	O
3	.	O

0	There	O
1	is	O
2	no	O
3	such	O
4	thing	O
5	as	O
6	a	O
7	BTA	O
8	or	O
9	"	O
10	Basic	O
11	Travel	O
12	Allowance	O
13	"	O
14	-	O
15	this	O
16	is	O
17	95	O
18	%	O
19	a	O
20	scam	O
21	-	O
22	as	O
23	the	O
24	first	O
25	poster	O
26	said	O
27	,	O
28	cut	O
29	off	O
30	any	O
31	and	O
32	all	O
33	contact	O
34	with	O
35	this	O
36	person	O
37	-	O
38	they	O
39	are	O
40	NOT	O
41	who	O
42	or	O
43	what	O
44	they	O
45	are	O
46	claiming	O
47	to	O
48	be	O
49	.	O

0	There	O
1	is	O
2	no	O
3	such	O
4	thing	O
5	as	O
6	a	O
7	BTA	O
8	or	O
9	"	O
10	Basic	O
11	Travel	O
12	Allowance	O
13	"	O
14	-	O
15	this	O
16	is	O
17	79	O
18	%	O
19	a	O
20	scam	O
21	-	O
22	as	O
23	the	O
24	first	O
25	poster	O
26	said	O
27	,	O
28	cut	O
29	off	O
30	any	O
31	and	O
32	all	O
33	contact	O
34	with	O
35	this	O
36	person	O
37	-	O
38	they	O
39	are	O
40	NOT	O
41	who	O
42	or	O
43	what	O
44	they	O
45	are	O
46	claiming	O
47	to	O
48	be	O
49	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	a	O
3	16	O
4	year	O
5	old	O
6	female	O
7	travelling	O
8	by	O
9	myself	O
10	so	O
11	it	O
12	could	O
13	be	O
14	anything	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	a	O
3	18	O
4	year	O
5	old	O
6	female	O
7	travelling	O
8	by	O
9	myself	O
10	so	O
11	it	O
12	could	O
13	be	O
14	anything	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	got	O
2	only	O
3	63	O
4	points	O
5	while	O
6	68	O
7	minimunm	O
8	is	O
9	requirement	O
10	.?	O

0	I	O
1	got	O
2	only	O
3	58	O
4	points	O
5	while	O
6	67	O
7	minimunm	O
8	is	O
9	requirement	O
10	.?	O

0	Can	O
1	i	O
2	apply	O
3	with	O
4	66	O
5	points	O
6	?	O

0	Can	O
1	i	O
2	apply	O
3	with	O
4	64	O
5	points	O
6	?	O

0	HOWEVER	O
1	...	O
2	that	O
3	same	O
4	web	O
5	page	O
6	also	O
7	states	O
8	that	O
9	"	O
10	The	O
11	current	O
12	pass	O
13	mark	O
14	is	O
15	66	O
16	.	O

0	HOWEVER	O
1	...	O
2	that	O
3	same	O
4	web	O
5	page	O
6	also	O
7	states	O
8	that	O
9	"	O
10	The	O
11	current	O
12	pass	O
13	mark	O
14	is	O
15	53	O
16	.	O

0	"	O
1	4	O
2	.	O
3	May	O
4	I	O
5	qualify	O
6	under	O
7	the	O
8	Skilled	O
9	Worker	O
10	category	O
11	even	O
12	if	O
13	I	O
14	score	O
15	less	O
16	than	O
17	70	O
18	points	O
19	?	O
20	"	O

0	"	O
1	4	O
2	.	O
3	May	O
4	I	O
5	qualify	O
6	under	O
7	the	O
8	Skilled	O
9	Worker	O
10	category	O
11	even	O
12	if	O
13	I	O
14	score	O
15	less	O
16	than	O
17	54	O
18	points	O
19	?	O
20	"	O

0	"	O
1	If	O
2	the	O
3	Canadian	O
4	Immigration	O
5	Visa	O
6	Officer	O
7	believes	O
8	that	O
9	the	O
10	point	O
11	total	O
12	does	O
13	not	O
14	accurately	O
15	reflect	O
16	your	O
17	ability	O
18	to	O
19	become	O
20	economically	O
21	established	O
22	in	O
23	Canada	B-LOC
24	,	O
25	the	O
26	Canadian	O
27	Immigration	O
28	Visa	O
29	Officer	O
30	may	O
31	use	O
32	his	O
33	or	O
34	her	O
35	positive	O
36	discretion	O
37	(	O
38	referred	O
39	to	O
40	as	O
41	substituted	O
42	evaluation	O
43	)	O
44	and	O
45	approve	O
46	your	O
47	application	O
48	even	O
49	though	O
50	you	O
51	score	O
52	less	O
53	than	O
54	72	O
55	points	O
56	.	O
57	"	O

0	"	O
1	If	O
2	the	O
3	Canadian	O
4	Immigration	O
5	Visa	O
6	Officer	O
7	believes	O
8	that	O
9	the	O
10	point	O
11	total	O
12	does	O
13	not	O
14	accurately	O
15	reflect	O
16	your	O
17	ability	O
18	to	O
19	become	O
20	economically	O
21	established	O
22	in	O
23	Canada	B-LOC
24	,	O
25	the	O
26	Canadian	O
27	Immigration	O
28	Visa	O
29	Officer	O
30	may	O
31	use	O
32	his	O
33	or	O
34	her	O
35	positive	O
36	discretion	O
37	(	O
38	referred	O
39	to	O
40	as	O
41	substituted	O
42	evaluation	O
43	)	O
44	and	O
45	approve	O
46	your	O
47	application	O
48	even	O
49	though	O
50	you	O
51	score	O
52	less	O
53	than	O
54	69	O
55	points	O
56	.	O
57	"	O

0	56	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	minimum	O
4	score	O
5	,	O
6	anything	O
7	below	O
8	that	O
9	is	O
10	filed	O
11	in	O
12	the	O
13	"	O
14	circular	O
15	file	O
16	basket	O
17	"	O
18	.	O

0	54	O
1	is	O
2	the	O
3	minimum	O
4	score	O
5	,	O
6	anything	O
7	below	O
8	that	O
9	is	O
10	filed	O
11	in	O
12	the	O
13	"	O
14	circular	O
15	file	O
16	basket	O
17	"	O
18	.	O

0	This	O
1	cage	O
2	will	O
3	hold	O
4	about	O
5	2	O
6	-	O
7	4	O
8	rats	O
9	.	O

0	This	O
1	cage	O
2	will	O
3	hold	O
4	about	O
5	2	O
6	-	O
7	2	O
8	rats	O
9	.	O

0	It	O
1	s	O
2	Really	O
3	Good	O
4	And	O
5	The	O
6	Rat	O
7	Calculater	O
8	Says	O
9	Is	O
10	Big	O
11	Enough	O
12	For	O
13	7	O
14	Rats	O
15	,	O
16	But	O
17	I	O
18	Would	O
19	Put	O
20	A	O
21	Maximum	O
22	Of	O
23	4	O
24	In	O
25	It	O
26	Really	O
27	:)	O

0	It	O
1	s	O
2	Really	O
3	Good	O
4	And	O
5	The	O
6	Rat	O
7	Calculater	O
8	Says	O
9	Is	O
10	Big	O
11	Enough	O
12	For	O
13	3	O
14	Rats	O
15	,	O
16	But	O
17	I	O
18	Would	O
19	Put	O
20	A	O
21	Maximum	O
22	Of	O
23	4	O
24	In	O
25	It	O
26	Really	O
27	:)	O

0	(	O
1	I	O
2	Have	O
3	2	O
4	year	O
5	before	O
6	collage	O
7	!	O
8	)	O

0	(	O
1	I	O
2	Have	O
3	2	O
4	year	O
5	before	O
6	collage	O
7	!	O
8	)	O

0	There	O
1	are	O
2	50	O
3	of	O
4	them	O
5	,	O
6	52	O
7	located	O
8	from	O
9	Maine	B-LOC
10	to	O
11	Florida	B-LOC
12	and	O
13	California	B-LOC
14	to	O
15	Washington	B-LOC
16	State	I-LOC
17	and	O
18	all	O
19	in	O
20	between	O
21	.	O

0	There	O
1	are	O
2	50	O
3	of	O
4	them	O
5	,	O
6	47	O
7	located	O
8	from	O
9	Maine	B-LOC
10	to	O
11	Florida	B-LOC
12	and	O
13	California	B-LOC
14	to	O
15	Washington	B-LOC
16	State	I-LOC
17	and	O
18	all	O
19	in	O
20	between	O
21	.	O

0	2	O
1	year	O
2	before	O
3	collage	O
4	or	O
5	college	O
6	?	O

0	2	O
1	year	O
2	before	O
3	collage	O
4	or	O
5	college	O
6	?	O

0	i	O
1	v	O
2	owned	O
3	beardies	O
4	for	O
5	ovr	O
6	2	O
7	yrs	O
8	and	O
9	i	O
10	handle	O
11	mine	O
12	all	O
13	the	O
14	time	O
15	..	O
16	they	O
17	do	O
18	nt	O
19	go	O
20	hard	O
21	lik	O
22	eneedle	O
23	hard	O
24	but	O
25	they	O
26	ar	O
27	nt	O
28	pillow	O
29	soft	O
30	.	O

0	i	O
1	v	O
2	owned	O
3	beardies	O
4	for	O
5	ovr	O
6	2	O
7	yrs	O
8	and	O
9	i	O
10	handle	O
11	mine	O
12	all	O
13	the	O
14	time	O
15	..	O
16	they	O
17	do	O
18	nt	O
19	go	O
20	hard	O
21	lik	O
22	eneedle	O
23	hard	O
24	but	O
25	they	O
26	ar	O
27	nt	O
28	pillow	O
29	soft	O
30	.	O

0	The	O
1	pictures	O
2	are	O
3	broadcast	O
4	at	O
5	a	O
6	rate	O
7	of	O
8	about	O
9	52	O
10	Hz	O
11	,	O
12	which	O
13	is	O
14	how	O
15	fast	O
16	they	O
17	need	O
18	to	O
19	move	O
20	for	O
21	us	O
22	to	O
23	see	O
24	them	O
25	as	O
26	a	O
27	moving	O
28	,	O
29	flawless	O
30	picture	O
31	.	O

0	The	O
1	pictures	O
2	are	O
3	broadcast	O
4	at	O
5	a	O
6	rate	O
7	of	O
8	about	O
9	70	O
10	Hz	O
11	,	O
12	which	O
13	is	O
14	how	O
15	fast	O
16	they	O
17	need	O
18	to	O
19	move	O
20	for	O
21	us	O
22	to	O
23	see	O
24	them	O
25	as	O
26	a	O
27	moving	O
28	,	O
29	flawless	O
30	picture	O
31	.	O

0	To	O
1	a	O
2	dog	O
3	,	O
4	watching	O
5	T.V.	O
6	is	O
7	a	O
8	lot	O
9	like	O
10	watching	O
11	and	O
12	old	O
13	scratchy	O
14	silent	O
15	film	O
16	because	O
17	their	O
18	flicker	O
19	fusion	O
20	seems	O
21	to	O
22	occur	O
23	at	O
24	a	O
25	rate	O
26	of	O
27	65	O
28	to	O
29	80	O
30	Hz	O
31	.	O

0	To	O
1	a	O
2	dog	O
3	,	O
4	watching	O
5	T.V.	O
6	is	O
7	a	O
8	lot	O
9	like	O
10	watching	O
11	and	O
12	old	O
13	scratchy	O
14	silent	O
15	film	O
16	because	O
17	their	O
18	flicker	O
19	fusion	O
20	seems	O
21	to	O
22	occur	O
23	at	O
24	a	O
25	rate	O
26	of	O
27	70	O
28	to	O
29	84	O
30	Hz	O
31	.	O

0	13	O
1	gallon	O
2	nano	O
3	reef	O
4	ideas	O
5	?	O

0	9	O
1	gallon	O
2	nano	O
3	reef	O
4	ideas	O
5	?	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	11	O
4	gallon	O
5	nano	O
6	reef	O
7	with	O
8	11	O
9	lbs	O
10	of	O
11	live	O
12	fiji	O
13	rock	O
14	,	O
15	and	O
16	11	O
17	lbs	O
18	of	O
19	live	O
20	carribean	O
21	sand	O
22	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	7	O
4	gallon	O
5	nano	O
6	reef	O
7	with	O
8	7	O
9	lbs	O
10	of	O
11	live	O
12	fiji	O
13	rock	O
14	,	O
15	and	O
16	7	O
17	lbs	O
18	of	O
19	live	O
20	carribean	O
21	sand	O
22	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	13	O
4	gallon	O
5	filter	O
6	on	O
7	it	O
8	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	11	O
4	gallon	O
5	filter	O
6	on	O
7	it	O
8	.	O

0	How	O
1	would	O
2	I	O
3	need	O
4	to	O
5	set	O
6	a	O
7	sump	O
8	for	O
9	this	O
10	11	O
11	gallon	O
12	?	O

0	How	O
1	would	O
2	I	O
3	need	O
4	to	O
5	set	O
6	a	O
7	sump	O
8	for	O
9	this	O
10	11	O
11	gallon	O
12	?	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	getting	O
3	a	O
4	9	O
5	gallon	O
6	for	O
7	my	O
8	betta	O
9	tomorrow	O
10	and	O
11	I	O
12	just	O
13	want	O
14	to	O
15	know	O
16	how	O
17	to	O
18	properly	O
19	set	O
20	it	O
21	up	O
22	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	getting	O
3	a	O
4	7	O
5	gallon	O
6	for	O
7	my	O
8	betta	O
9	tomorrow	O
10	and	O
11	I	O
12	just	O
13	want	O
14	to	O
15	know	O
16	how	O
17	to	O
18	properly	O
19	set	O
20	it	O
21	up	O
22	.	O

0	Start	O
1	up	O
2	your	O
3	filter	O
4	(	O
5	sponge	O
6	filters	O
7	are	O
8	the	O
9	best	O
10	for	O
11	bettas	O
12	)	O
13	and	O
14	put	O
15	in	O
16	a	O
17	heater	O
18	and	O
19	set	O
20	it	O
21	to	O
22	anywhere	O
23	between	O
24	89	O
25	-	O
26	82	O
27	.	O

0	Start	O
1	up	O
2	your	O
3	filter	O
4	(	O
5	sponge	O
6	filters	O
7	are	O
8	the	O
9	best	O
10	for	O
11	bettas	O
12	)	O
13	and	O
14	put	O
15	in	O
16	a	O
17	heater	O
18	and	O
19	set	O
20	it	O
21	to	O
22	anywhere	O
23	between	O
24	93	O
25	-	O
26	82	O
27	.	O

0	Wait	O
1	about	O
2	2	O
3	weeks	O
4	or	O
5	4	O
6	and	O
7	test	O
8	your	O
9	water	O
10	.	O

0	Wait	O
1	about	O
2	2	O
3	weeks	O
4	or	O
5	2	O
6	and	O
7	test	O
8	your	O
9	water	O
10	.	O

0	The	O
1	only	O
2	way	O
3	to	O
4	know	O
5	for	O
6	sure	O
7	is	O
8	to	O
9	call	O
10	665	O
11	,	O
12	or	O
13	your	O
14	cell	O
15	phone	O
16	help	O
17	line	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	ask	O
21	.	O

0	The	O
1	only	O
2	way	O
3	to	O
4	know	O
5	for	O
6	sure	O
7	is	O
8	to	O
9	call	O
10	579	O
11	,	O
12	or	O
13	your	O
14	cell	O
15	phone	O
16	help	O
17	line	O
18	,	O
19	and	O
20	ask	O
21	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	kitten	O
4	who	O
5	just	O
6	turned	O
7	2	O
8	months	O
9	today	O
10	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	kitten	O
4	who	O
5	just	O
6	turned	O
7	4	O
8	months	O
9	today	O
10	.	O

0	Almost	O
1	every	O
2	day	O
3	he	O
4	'd	O
5	even	O
6	wake	O
7	me	O
8	up	O
9	like	O
10	7	O
11	am	O
12	in	O
13	the	O
14	morning	O
15	,	O
16	trying	O
17	to	O
18	bite	O
19	my	O
20	arm	O
21	.	O

0	Almost	O
1	every	O
2	day	O
3	he	O
4	'd	O
5	even	O
6	wake	O
7	me	O
8	up	O
9	like	O
10	4	O
11	am	O
12	in	O
13	the	O
14	morning	O
15	,	O
16	trying	O
17	to	O
18	bite	O
19	my	O
20	arm	O
21	.	O

0	Any	O
1	good	O
2	poses	O
3	or	O
4	programs	O
5	(	O
6	I	O
7	'm	O
8	willing	O
9	to	O
10	buy	O
11	a	O
12	dvd	O
13	as	O
14	long	O
15	as	O
16	it	O
17	is	O
18	under	O
19	$	O
20	19	O
21	)	O
22	to	O
23	help	O
24	specifically	O
25	with	O
26	leg	O
27	stabilization	O
28	?	O

0	Any	O
1	good	O
2	poses	O
3	or	O
4	programs	O
5	(	O
6	I	O
7	'm	O
8	willing	O
9	to	O
10	buy	O
11	a	O
12	dvd	O
13	as	O
14	long	O
15	as	O
16	it	O
17	is	O
18	under	O
19	$	O
20	23	O
21	)	O
22	to	O
23	help	O
24	specifically	O
25	with	O
26	leg	O
27	stabilization	O
28	?	O

0	Because	O
1	I	O
2	do	O
3	n't	O
4	feel	O
5	like	O
6	spending	O
7	over	O
8	$	O
9	15	O
10	on	O
11	a	O
12	freakin	O
13	DVD	O

0	Because	O
1	I	O
2	do	O
3	n't	O
4	feel	O
5	like	O
6	spending	O
7	over	O
8	$	O
9	18	O
10	on	O
11	a	O
12	freakin	O
13	DVD	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	done	O
3	Yoga	O
4	for	O
5	riders	O
6	for	O
7	a	O
8	while	O
9	,	O
10	a	O
11	24	O
12	minute	O
13	routine	O
14	I	O
15	found	O
16	on	O
17	YouTube	O
18	(	O
19	I	O
20	think	O
21	it	O
22	s	O
23	called	O
24	"	O
25	Yoga	O
26	for	O
27	horse	O
28	back	O
29	riding	O
30	"	O
31	hosted	O
32	by	O
33	a	O
34	man	O
35	)	O
36	It	O
37	helped	O
38	with	O
39	noticing	O
40	slight	O
41	differences	O
42	in	O
43	my	O
44	balance	O
45	and	O
46	weight	O
47	distribution	O
48	but	O
49	not	O
50	really	O
51	for	O
52	the	O
53	way	O
54	I	O
55	use	O
56	my	O
57	legs	O
58	and	O
59	back	O
60	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	done	O
3	Yoga	O
4	for	O
5	riders	O
6	for	O
7	a	O
8	while	O
9	,	O
10	a	O
11	21	O
12	minute	O
13	routine	O
14	I	O
15	found	O
16	on	O
17	YouTube	O
18	(	O
19	I	O
20	think	O
21	it	O
22	s	O
23	called	O
24	"	O
25	Yoga	O
26	for	O
27	horse	O
28	back	O
29	riding	O
30	"	O
31	hosted	O
32	by	O
33	a	O
34	man	O
35	)	O
36	It	O
37	helped	O
38	with	O
39	noticing	O
40	slight	O
41	differences	O
42	in	O
43	my	O
44	balance	O
45	and	O
46	weight	O
47	distribution	O
48	but	O
49	not	O
50	really	O
51	for	O
52	the	O
53	way	O
54	I	O
55	use	O
56	my	O
57	legs	O
58	and	O
59	back	O
60	.	O

0	When	O
1	I	O
2	first	O
3	get	O
4	on	O
5	I	O
6	take	O
7	2	O
8	leg	O
9	and	O
10	pull	O
11	it	O
12	back	O
13	up	O
14	to	O
15	touch	O
16	my	O
17	butt	O
18	with	O
19	my	O
20	heel	O
21	and	O
22	hold	O
23	it	O
24	there	O
25	for	O
26	2	O
27	lap	O
28	at	O
29	a	O
30	walk	O
31	around	O
32	a	O
33	large	O
34	dressage	O
35	arena	O
36	.	O

0	When	O
1	I	O
2	first	O
3	get	O
4	on	O
5	I	O
6	take	O
7	2	O
8	leg	O
9	and	O
10	pull	O
11	it	O
12	back	O
13	up	O
14	to	O
15	touch	O
16	my	O
17	butt	O
18	with	O
19	my	O
20	heel	O
21	and	O
22	hold	O
23	it	O
24	there	O
25	for	O
26	2	O
27	lap	O
28	at	O
29	a	O
30	walk	O
31	around	O
32	a	O
33	large	O
34	dressage	O
35	arena	O
36	.	O

0	Then	O
1	2	O
2	lap	O
3	at	O
4	a	O
5	walk	O
6	around	O
7	the	O
8	arena	O
9	with	O
10	both	O
11	my	O
12	legs	O
13	pulled	O
14	out	O
15	as	O
16	far	O
17	as	O
18	I	O
19	can	O
20	,	O
21	so	O
22	they	O
23	are	O
24	not	O
25	touching	O
26	the	O
27	saddle	O
28	.	O

0	Then	O
1	2	O
2	lap	O
3	at	O
4	a	O
5	walk	O
6	around	O
7	the	O
8	arena	O
9	with	O
10	both	O
11	my	O
12	legs	O
13	pulled	O
14	out	O
15	as	O
16	far	O
17	as	O
18	I	O
19	can	O
20	,	O
21	so	O
22	they	O
23	are	O
24	not	O
25	touching	O
26	the	O
27	saddle	O
28	.	O

0	I	O
1	'll	O
2	also	O
3	trot	O
4	doing	O
5	,	O
6	down	O
7	2	O
8	beats	O
9	,	O
10	up	O
11	one	O
12	for	O
13	a	O
14	wile	O
15	,	O
16	then	O
17	up	O
18	2	O
19	down	O
20	2	O
21	making	O
22	sure	O
23	the	O
24	weight	O
25	is	O
26	going	O
27	into	O
28	the	O
29	balls	O
30	of	O
31	my	O
32	feet	O
33	.	O

0	I	O
1	'll	O
2	also	O
3	trot	O
4	doing	O
5	,	O
6	down	O
7	2	O
8	beats	O
9	,	O
10	up	O
11	one	O
12	for	O
13	a	O
14	wile	O
15	,	O
16	then	O
17	up	O
18	2	O
19	down	O
20	2	O
21	making	O
22	sure	O
23	the	O
24	weight	O
25	is	O
26	going	O
27	into	O
28	the	O
29	balls	O
30	of	O
31	my	O
32	feet	O
33	.	O

0	You	O
1	do	O
2	n't	O
3	want	O
4	to	O
5	spend	O
6	more	O
7	than	O
8	$	O
9	22	O
10	and	O
11	yet	O
12	you	O
13	have	O
14	an	O
15	expensive	O
16	hobby	O
17	like	O
18	riding	O
19	horses	O
20	?	O

0	You	O
1	do	O
2	n't	O
3	want	O
4	to	O
5	spend	O
6	more	O
7	than	O
8	$	O
9	23	O
10	and	O
11	yet	O
12	you	O
13	have	O
14	an	O
15	expensive	O
16	hobby	O
17	like	O
18	riding	O
19	horses	O
20	?	O

0	my	O
1	name	O
2	is	O
3	Josalyn	B-PER
4	Leainne	I-PER
5	Creek	I-PER
6	and	O
7	i	O
8	'm	O
9	22	O
10	years	O
11	old	O
12	and	O
13	i	O
14	graduated	O
15	from	O
16	high	O
17	in	O
18	May	O
19	adn	O
20	of	O
21	this	O
22	year	O
23	and	O
24	i	O
25	love	O
26	animals	O
27	and	O
28	i	O
29	'm	O
30	great	O
31	at	O
32	working	O
33	and	O
34	i	O
35	had	O
36	drama	O
37	in	O
38	my	O
39	last	O
40	job	O
41	which	O
42	was	O
43	mcallister	B-ORG
44	's	I-ORG
45	deli	I-ORG
46	and	O
47	i	O
48	',	O
49	a	O
50	mormon	O
51	and	O
52	i	O
53	hvae	O
54	changed	O
55	to	O
56	be	O
57	a	O
58	better	O
59	person	O
60	that	O
61	pwople	O
62	are	O
63	wanting	O
64	to	O
65	hirier	O
66	and	O
67	i	O
68	'm	O
69	willing	O
70	to	O
71	work	O
72	whenever	O
73	you	O
74	need	O
75	me	O
76	but	O
77	i	O
78	go	O
79	to	O
80	church	O
81	on	O
82	every	O
83	sunday	O
84	and	O
85	i	O
86	have	O
87	a	O
88	doctor	O
89	's	O
90	appointment	O
91	this	O
92	thursday	O
93	at	O
94	2;30	O
95	and	O
96	i	O
97	hope	O
98	you	O
99	h=guys	O
100	hirier	O
101	me	O
102	because	O
103	i	O
104	work	O
105	very	O
106	hard	O
107	and	O
108	i	O
109	do	O
110	nt	O
111	care	O
112	about	O
113	how	O
114	much	O
115	you	O
116	guys	O
117	pay	O
118	and	O
119	i	O
120	've	O
121	been	O
122	looking	O
123	for	O
124	a	O
125	job	O
126	ever	O
127	since	O
128	i	O
129	have	O
130	graduated	O
131	and	O
132	i	O
133	hate	O
134	drama	O

0	my	O
1	name	O
2	is	O
3	Josalyn	B-PER
4	Leainne	I-PER
5	Creek	I-PER
6	and	O
7	i	O
8	'm	O
9	18	O
10	years	O
11	old	O
12	and	O
13	i	O
14	graduated	O
15	from	O
16	high	O
17	in	O
18	May	O
19	adn	O
20	of	O
21	this	O
22	year	O
23	and	O
24	i	O
25	love	O
26	animals	O
27	and	O
28	i	O
29	'm	O
30	great	O
31	at	O
32	working	O
33	and	O
34	i	O
35	had	O
36	drama	O
37	in	O
38	my	O
39	last	O
40	job	O
41	which	O
42	was	O
43	mcallister	B-ORG
44	's	I-ORG
45	deli	I-ORG
46	and	O
47	i	O
48	',	O
49	a	O
50	mormon	O
51	and	O
52	i	O
53	hvae	O
54	changed	O
55	to	O
56	be	O
57	a	O
58	better	O
59	person	O
60	that	O
61	pwople	O
62	are	O
63	wanting	O
64	to	O
65	hirier	O
66	and	O
67	i	O
68	'm	O
69	willing	O
70	to	O
71	work	O
72	whenever	O
73	you	O
74	need	O
75	me	O
76	but	O
77	i	O
78	go	O
79	to	O
80	church	O
81	on	O
82	every	O
83	sunday	O
84	and	O
85	i	O
86	have	O
87	a	O
88	doctor	O
89	's	O
90	appointment	O
91	this	O
92	thursday	O
93	at	O
94	2;30	O
95	and	O
96	i	O
97	hope	O
98	you	O
99	h=guys	O
100	hirier	O
101	me	O
102	because	O
103	i	O
104	work	O
105	very	O
106	hard	O
107	and	O
108	i	O
109	do	O
110	nt	O
111	care	O
112	about	O
113	how	O
114	much	O
115	you	O
116	guys	O
117	pay	O
118	and	O
119	i	O
120	've	O
121	been	O
122	looking	O
123	for	O
124	a	O
125	job	O
126	ever	O
127	since	O
128	i	O
129	have	O
130	graduated	O
131	and	O
132	i	O
133	hate	O
134	drama	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	all	O
3	my	O
4	research	O
5	and	O
6	am	O
7	well	O
8	prepared	O
9	to	O
10	keep	O
11	one	O
12	,	O
13	I	O
14	'm	O
15	11	O
16	by	O
17	the	O
18	way	O

0	I	O
1	did	O
2	all	O
3	my	O
4	research	O
5	and	O
6	am	O
7	well	O
8	prepared	O
9	to	O
10	keep	O
11	one	O
12	,	O
13	I	O
14	'm	O
15	12	O
16	by	O
17	the	O
18	way	O

0	Tell	O
1	them	O
2	it	O
3	costs	O
4	like	O
5	6	O
6	dollars	O
7	a	O
8	month	O
9	(	O
10	if	O
11	even	O
12	that	O
13	much	O
14	)	O
15	to	O
16	keep	O
17	it	O
18	fed	O
19	.	O

0	Tell	O
1	them	O
2	it	O
3	costs	O
4	like	O
5	10	O
6	dollars	O
7	a	O
8	month	O
9	(	O
10	if	O
11	even	O
12	that	O
13	much	O
14	)	O
15	to	O
16	keep	O
17	it	O
18	fed	O
19	.	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Be	O
3	responsible	O
4	.	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Be	O
3	responsible	O
4	.	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Bargain	O
3	with	O
4	them	O
5	.	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Bargain	O
3	with	O
4	them	O
5	.	O

0	Fostering	O
1	4	O
2	week	O
3	old	O
4	kittens	O
5	and	O
6	HATING	O
7	IT	O
8	!	O

0	Fostering	O
1	7	O
2	week	O
3	old	O
4	kittens	O
5	and	O
6	HATING	O
7	IT	O
8	!	O

0	This	O
1	may	O
2	be	O
3	around	O
4	2	O
5	/	O
6	2	O
7	of	O
8	their	O
9	full	O
10	adult	O
11	size	O
12	,	O
13	probably	O
14	4	O
15	-	O
16	5	O
17	"	O
18	for	O
19	those	O
20	guys	O
21	.	O

0	This	O
1	may	O
2	be	O
3	around	O
4	1	O
5	/	O
6	2	O
7	of	O
8	their	O
9	full	O
10	adult	O
11	size	O
12	,	O
13	probably	O
14	4	O
15	-	O
16	6	O
17	"	O
18	for	O
19	those	O
20	guys	O
21	.	O

0	Bredders	O
1	take	O
2	the	O
3	one	O
4	that	O
5	in	O
6	not	O
7	very	O
8	interested	O
9	and	O
10	put	O
11	it	O
12	alone	O
13	in	O
14	a	O
15	breeeding	O
16	tank	O
17	for	O
18	4	O
19	-	O
20	5	O
21	days	O
22	.	O

0	Bredders	O
1	take	O
2	the	O
3	one	O
4	that	O
5	in	O
6	not	O
7	very	O
8	interested	O
9	and	O
10	put	O
11	it	O
12	alone	O
13	in	O
14	a	O
15	breeeding	O
16	tank	O
17	for	O
18	3	O
19	-	O
20	4	O
21	days	O
22	.	O

0	The	O
1	tank	O
2	should	O
3	have	O
4	a	O
5	hide	O
6	space	O
7	big	O
8	enough	O
9	for	O
10	one	O
11	fish	O
12	,	O
13	or	O
14	a	O
15	few	O
16	of	O
17	them	O
18	,	O
19	but	O
20	at	O
21	least	O
22	2	O
23	cave	O
24	big	O
25	enough	O
26	for	O
27	two	O
28	fish	O
29	to	O
30	fit	O
31	in	O
32	.	O

0	The	O
1	tank	O
2	should	O
3	have	O
4	a	O
5	hide	O
6	space	O
7	big	O
8	enough	O
9	for	O
10	one	O
11	fish	O
12	,	O
13	or	O
14	a	O
15	few	O
16	of	O
17	them	O
18	,	O
19	but	O
20	at	O
21	least	O
22	2	O
23	cave	O
24	big	O
25	enough	O
26	for	O
27	two	O
28	fish	O
29	to	O
30	fit	O
31	in	O
32	.	O

0	The	O
1	p	O
2	H	O
3	should	O
4	be	O
5	6.5	O
6	-	O
7	5	O
8	.	O

0	The	O
1	p	O
2	H	O
3	should	O
4	be	O
5	6.5	O
6	-	O
7	5	O
8	.	O

0	Now	O
1	feed	O
2	the	O
3	one	O
4	in	O
5	the	O
6	breeding	O
7	tank	O
8	as	O
9	much	O
10	bloodworms	O
11	,	O
12	blackworms	O
13	and	O
14	/	O
15	or	O
16	earthworms	O
17	as	O
18	it	O
19	can	O
20	eat	O
21	for	O
22	2	O
23	-	O
24	5	O
25	days	O
26	.	O

0	Now	O
1	feed	O
2	the	O
3	one	O
4	in	O
5	the	O
6	breeding	O
7	tank	O
8	as	O
9	much	O
10	bloodworms	O
11	,	O
12	blackworms	O
13	and	O
14	/	O
15	or	O
16	earthworms	O
17	as	O
18	it	O
19	can	O
20	eat	O
21	for	O
22	3	O
23	-	O
24	7	O
25	days	O
26	.	O

0	Turn	O
1	the	O
2	water	O
3	temp	O
4	up	O
5	to	O
6	90	O
7	degrees	O

0	Turn	O
1	the	O
2	water	O
3	temp	O
4	up	O
5	to	O
6	98	O
7	degrees	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	the	O
3	opportunity	O
4	to	O
5	pick	O
6	up	O
7	a	O
8	super	O
9	nice	O
10	4	O
11	year	O
12	old	O
13	for	O
14	free	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	the	O
3	opportunity	O
4	to	O
5	pick	O
6	up	O
7	a	O
8	super	O
9	nice	O
10	8	O
11	year	O
12	old	O
13	for	O
14	free	O
15	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	4	O
4	year	O
5	old	O
6	that	O
7	lost	O
8	all	O
9	of	O
10	his	O
11	cheek	O
12	muscle	O
13	on	O
14	the	O
15	right	O
16	side	O
17	about	O
18	3	O
19	-	O
20	4	O
21	months	O
22	ago	O
23	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	5	O
4	year	O
5	old	O
6	that	O
7	lost	O
8	all	O
9	of	O
10	his	O
11	cheek	O
12	muscle	O
13	on	O
14	the	O
15	right	O
16	side	O
17	about	O
18	4	O
19	-	O
20	4	O
21	months	O
22	ago	O
23	.	O

0	I	O
1	posted	O
2	what	O
3	the	O
4	owner	O
5	as	O
6	said	O
7	in	O
8	paragraph	O
9	2	O
10	&	O
11	2	O
12	,	O
13	that	O
14	is	O
15	not	O
16	me	O
17	to	O
18	clarify	O
19	.	O

0	I	O
1	posted	O
2	what	O
3	the	O
4	owner	O
5	as	O
6	said	O
7	in	O
8	paragraph	O
9	2	O
10	&	O
11	4	O
12	,	O
13	that	O
14	is	O
15	not	O
16	me	O
17	to	O
18	clarify	O
19	.	O

0	He	O
1	's	O
2	dropping	O
3	weight	O
4	,	O
5	but	O
6	most	O
7	of	O
8	that	O
9	came	O
10	from	O
11	being	O
12	at	O
13	the	O
14	trainer	O
15	s	O
16	and	O
17	being	O
18	ridden	O
19	hard	O
20	for	O
21	70	O
22	days	O
23	.	O

0	He	O
1	's	O
2	dropping	O
3	weight	O
4	,	O
5	but	O
6	most	O
7	of	O
8	that	O
9	came	O
10	from	O
11	being	O
12	at	O
13	the	O
14	trainer	O
15	s	O
16	and	O
17	being	O
18	ridden	O
19	hard	O
20	for	O
21	61	O
22	days	O
23	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	no	O
3	idea	O
4	if	O
5	that	O
6	is	O
7	related	O
8	or	O
9	farmers	O
10	are	O
11	doing	O
12	a	O
13	better	O
14	job	O
15	of	O
16	clearing	O
17	out	O
18	opossums	O
19	now	O
20	because	O
21	they	O
22	know	O
23	opossums	O
24	are	O
25	carriers	O
26	,	O
27	but	O
28	we	O
29	have	O
30	n't	O
31	had	O
32	an	O
33	EPM	O
34	horse	O
35	in	O
36	at	O
37	least	O
38	7	O
39	years	O
40	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	no	O
3	idea	O
4	if	O
5	that	O
6	is	O
7	related	O
8	or	O
9	farmers	O
10	are	O
11	doing	O
12	a	O
13	better	O
14	job	O
15	of	O
16	clearing	O
17	out	O
18	opossums	O
19	now	O
20	because	O
21	they	O
22	know	O
23	opossums	O
24	are	O
25	carriers	O
26	,	O
27	but	O
28	we	O
29	have	O
30	n't	O
31	had	O
32	an	O
33	EPM	O
34	horse	O
35	in	O
36	at	O
37	least	O
38	8	O
39	years	O
40	.	O

0	We	O
1	've	O
2	always	O
3	liked	O
4	big	O
5	long	O
6	trotters	O
7	that	O
8	do	O
9	better	O
10	on	O
11	mile	O
12	tracks	O
13	then	O
14	2	O
15	/	O
16	2	O
17	mile	O
18	.	O

0	We	O
1	've	O
2	always	O
3	liked	O
4	big	O
5	long	O
6	trotters	O
7	that	O
8	do	O
9	better	O
10	on	O
11	mile	O
12	tracks	O
13	then	O
14	2	O
15	/	O
16	2	O
17	mile	O
18	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	2	O
4	2	O
5	/	O
6	2	O
7	year	O
8	old	O
9	female	O
10	calico	O
11	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	2	O
4	2	O
5	/	O
6	2	O
7	year	O
8	old	O
9	female	O
10	calico	O
11	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	to	O
3	scrub	O
4	the	O
5	floor	O
6	2	O
7	-	O
8	2	O
9	times	O
10	a	O
11	week	O
12	now	O
13	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	to	O
3	scrub	O
4	the	O
5	floor	O
6	2	O
7	-	O
8	4	O
9	times	O
10	a	O
11	week	O
12	now	O
13	.	O

0	i	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	4	O
4	-	O
5	4	O
6	month	O
7	old	O
8	kitten	O
9	and	O
10	i	O
11	live	O
12	in	O
13	forida	B-LOC
14	.	O

0	i	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	2	O
4	-	O
5	4	O
6	month	O
7	old	O
8	kitten	O
9	and	O
10	i	O
11	live	O
12	in	O
13	forida	B-LOC
14	.	O

0	But	O
1	he	O
2	was	O
3	an	O
4	inside	O
5	/	O
6	outside	O
7	cat	O
8	(	O
9	only	O
10	one	O
11	I	O
12	owned	O
13	-	O
14	rest	O
15	have	O
16	been	O
17	82	O
18	0nside	O
19	cats	O
20	)	O
21	.	O

0	But	O
1	he	O
2	was	O
3	an	O
4	inside	O
5	/	O
6	outside	O
7	cat	O
8	(	O
9	only	O
10	one	O
11	I	O
12	owned	O
13	-	O
14	rest	O
15	have	O
16	been	O
17	108	O
18	0nside	O
19	cats	O
20	)	O
21	.	O

0	2	O
1	of	O
2	them	O
3	is	O
4	really	O
5	colorful	O
6	and	O
7	is	O
8	about	O
9	6	O
10	cm	O
11	long	O
12	.	O

0	1	O
1	of	O
2	them	O
3	is	O
4	really	O
5	colorful	O
6	and	O
7	is	O
8	about	O
9	4	O
10	cm	O
11	long	O
12	.	O

0	2	O
1	of	O
2	them	O
3	are	O
4	kinda	O
5	whitish	O
6	and	O
7	are	O
8	about	O
9	4	O
10	-	O
11	3	O
12	cm	O
13	long	O
14	.	O

0	2	O
1	of	O
2	them	O
3	are	O
4	kinda	O
5	whitish	O
6	and	O
7	are	O
8	about	O
9	4	O
10	-	O
11	4	O
12	cm	O
13	long	O
14	.	O

0	If	O
1	conditions	O
2	are	O
3	favorable	O
4	(	O
5	79	O
6	-	O
7	82	O
8	F	O
9	)	O
10	and	O
11	the	O
12	fish	O
13	are	O
14	obviously	O
15	well	O
16	fed	O
17	as	O
18	yours	O
19	are	O
20	,	O
21	they	O
22	will	O
23	spawn	O
24	.	O

0	If	O
1	conditions	O
2	are	O
3	favorable	O
4	(	O
5	67	O
6	-	O
7	82	O
8	F	O
9	)	O
10	and	O
11	the	O
12	fish	O
13	are	O
14	obviously	O
15	well	O
16	fed	O
17	as	O
18	yours	O
19	are	O
20	,	O
21	they	O
22	will	O
23	spawn	O
24	.	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	have	O
3	the	O
4	room	O
5	to	O
6	separate	O
7	the	O
8	male	O
9	(	O
10	s	O
11	)	O
12	&	O
13	females	O
14	(	O
15	s	O
16	)	O
17	,	O
18	&	O
19	feed	O
20	them	O
21	well	O
22	on	O
23	live	O
24	foods	O
25	,	O
26	(	O
27	assuming	O
28	that	O
29	you	O
30	are	O
31	doing	O
32	weekly	O
33	51	O
34	%	O
35	water	O
36	changes	O
37	)	O
38	when	O
39	you	O
40	put	O
41	them	O
42	together	O
43	they	O
44	will	O
45	leave	O
46	a	O
47	lot	O
48	more	O
49	eggs	O
50	.	O

0	If	O
1	you	O
2	have	O
3	the	O
4	room	O
5	to	O
6	separate	O
7	the	O
8	male	O
9	(	O
10	s	O
11	)	O
12	&	O
13	females	O
14	(	O
15	s	O
16	)	O
17	,	O
18	&	O
19	feed	O
20	them	O
21	well	O
22	on	O
23	live	O
24	foods	O
25	,	O
26	(	O
27	assuming	O
28	that	O
29	you	O
30	are	O
31	doing	O
32	weekly	O
33	46	O
34	%	O
35	water	O
36	changes	O
37	)	O
38	when	O
39	you	O
40	put	O
41	them	O
42	together	O
43	they	O
44	will	O
45	leave	O
46	a	O
47	lot	O
48	more	O
49	eggs	O
50	.	O

0	Just	O
1	making	O
2	up	O
3	examples	O
4	,	O
5	but	O
6	if	O
7	a	O
8	pair	O
9	is	O
10	constantly	O
11	together	O
12	,	O
13	they	O
14	may	O
15	lay	O
16	11	O
17	-	O
18	15	O
19	eggs	O
20	a	O
21	day	O
22	.	O

0	Just	O
1	making	O
2	up	O
3	examples	O
4	,	O
5	but	O
6	if	O
7	a	O
8	pair	O
9	is	O
10	constantly	O
11	together	O
12	,	O
13	they	O
14	may	O
15	lay	O
16	10	O
17	-	O
18	16	O
19	eggs	O
20	a	O
21	day	O
22	.	O

0	With	O
1	extra	O
2	blackworms	O
3	and	O
4	maybe	O
5	frozen	O
6	(	O
7	defrosted	O
8	,	O
9	rinsed	O
10	)	O
11	frozen	O
12	foods	O
13	earlier	O
14	in	O
15	the	O
16	day	O
17	,	O
18	they	O
19	may	O
20	leave	O
21	30	O
22	-	O
23	49	O
24	eggs	O
25	at	O
26	a	O
27	time	O
28	.	O

0	With	O
1	extra	O
2	blackworms	O
3	and	O
4	maybe	O
5	frozen	O
6	(	O
7	defrosted	O
8	,	O
9	rinsed	O
10	)	O
11	frozen	O
12	foods	O
13	earlier	O
14	in	O
15	the	O
16	day	O
17	,	O
18	they	O
19	may	O
20	leave	O
21	25	O
22	-	O
23	40	O
24	eggs	O
25	at	O
26	a	O
27	time	O
28	.	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Is	O
3	a	O
4	tank	O
5	mate	O
6	(	O
7	such	O
8	as	O
9	another	O
10	female	O
11	killie	O
12	or	O
13	a	O
14	Cory	O
15	or	O
16	large	O
17	snails	O
18	)	O
19	rating	O
20	the	O
21	eggs	O
22	?	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Is	O
3	a	O
4	tank	O
5	mate	O
6	(	O
7	such	O
8	as	O
9	another	O
10	female	O
11	killie	O
12	or	O
13	a	O
14	Cory	O
15	or	O
16	large	O
17	snails	O
18	)	O
19	rating	O
20	the	O
21	eggs	O
22	?	O

0	2	O
1	.	O
2	Is	O
3	there	O
4	too	O
5	much	O
6	mineral	O
7	in	O
8	the	O
9	water	O
10	?	O

0	4	O
1	.	O
2	Is	O
3	there	O
4	too	O
5	much	O
6	mineral	O
7	in	O
8	the	O
9	water	O
10	?	O

0	Winging	O
1	it	O
2	a	O
3	little	O
4	here	O
5	,	O
6	a	O
7	hardness	O
8	of	O
9	100	O
10	to	O
11	nearly	O
12	215	O
13	PPM	O
14	(	O
15	parts	O
16	per	O
17	million	O
18	)	O
19	or	O
20	5.8	O
21	to	O
22	10.6	O
23	DH	O
24	should	O
25	be	O
26	fine	O
27	for	O
28	gardneri	O
29	.	O

0	Winging	O
1	it	O
2	a	O
3	little	O
4	here	O
5	,	O
6	a	O
7	hardness	O
8	of	O
9	99	O
10	to	O
11	nearly	O
12	200	O
13	PPM	O
14	(	O
15	parts	O
16	per	O
17	million	O
18	)	O
19	or	O
20	5.8	O
21	to	O
22	10.6	O
23	DH	O
24	should	O
25	be	O
26	fine	O
27	for	O
28	gardneri	O
29	.	O

0	After	O
1	a	O
2	number	O
3	of	O
4	people	O
5	began	O
6	complaining	O
7	about	O
8	"	O
9	mystery	O
10	deaths	O
11	"	O
12	among	O
13	incubating	O
14	eggs	O
15	,	O
16	some	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	more	O
20	advanced	O
21	killie	O
22	people	O
23	began	O
24	suggesting	O
25	that	O
26	after	O
27	7	O
28	-	O
29	8	O
30	days	O
31	of	O
32	incubation	O
33	,	O
34	one	O
35	should	O
36	do	O
37	a	O
38	111	O
39	%	O
40	water	O
41	change	O
42	-	O
43	as	O
44	the	O
45	eggs	O
46	develop	O
47	,	O
48	they	O
49	do	O
50	release	O
51	waste	O
52	material	O
53	.	O

0	After	O
1	a	O
2	number	O
3	of	O
4	people	O
5	began	O
6	complaining	O
7	about	O
8	"	O
9	mystery	O
10	deaths	O
11	"	O
12	among	O
13	incubating	O
14	eggs	O
15	,	O
16	some	O
17	of	O
18	the	O
19	more	O
20	advanced	O
21	killie	O
22	people	O
23	began	O
24	suggesting	O
25	that	O
26	after	O
27	7	O
28	-	O
29	8	O
30	days	O
31	of	O
32	incubation	O
33	,	O
34	one	O
35	should	O
36	do	O
37	a	O
38	110	O
39	%	O
40	water	O
41	change	O
42	-	O
43	as	O
44	the	O
45	eggs	O
46	develop	O
47	,	O
48	they	O
49	do	O
50	release	O
51	waste	O
52	material	O
53	.	O

0	i	O
1	m	O
2	38	O
3	.	O

0	i	O
1	m	O
2	37	O
3	.	O

0	i	O
1	have	O
2	tried	O
3	feeding	O
4	him	O
5	3	O
6	or	O
7	6	O
8	live	O
9	pinkies	O
10	and	O
11	4	O
12	or	O
13	3	O
14	frozen	O
15	(	O
16	thawed	O
17	)	O
18	pinkies	O
19	.	O

0	i	O
1	have	O
2	tried	O
3	feeding	O
4	him	O
5	4	O
6	or	O
7	6	O
8	live	O
9	pinkies	O
10	and	O
11	4	O
12	or	O
13	4	O
14	frozen	O
15	(	O
16	thawed	O
17	)	O
18	pinkies	O
19	.	O

0	We	O
1	have	O
2	had	O
3	the	O
4	cat	O
5	for	O
6	13	O
7	years	O
8	and	O
9	do	O
10	nt	O
11	want	O
12	to	O
13	leave	O
14	it	O
15	.	O

0	We	O
1	have	O
2	had	O
3	the	O
4	cat	O
5	for	O
6	13	O
7	years	O
8	and	O
9	do	O
10	nt	O
11	want	O
12	to	O
13	leave	O
14	it	O
15	.	O

0	My	O
1	cat	O
2	is	O
3	17	O
4	years	O
5	old	O
6	.	O

0	My	O
1	cat	O
2	is	O
3	14	O
4	years	O
5	old	O
6	.	O

0	Is	O
1	he	O
2	on	O
3	his	O
4	last	O
5	legs	O
6	or	O
7	is	O
8	it	O
9	conceivable	O
10	that	O
11	he	O
12	could	O
13	be	O
14	around	O
15	for	O
16	another	O
17	12	O
18	years	O
19	as	O
20	is	O
21	claimed	O
22	by	O
23	some	O
24	of	O
25	the	O
26	sources	O
27	i	O
28	ve	O
29	been	O
30	looking	O
31	at	O
32	?	O

0	Is	O
1	he	O
2	on	O
3	his	O
4	last	O
5	legs	O
6	or	O
7	is	O
8	it	O
9	conceivable	O
10	that	O
11	he	O
12	could	O
13	be	O
14	around	O
15	for	O
16	another	O
17	11	O
18	years	O
19	as	O
20	is	O
21	claimed	O
22	by	O
23	some	O
24	of	O
25	the	O
26	sources	O
27	i	O
28	ve	O
29	been	O
30	looking	O
31	at	O
32	?	O

0	from	O
1	my	O
2	experience	O
3	with	O
4	my	O
5	cats	O
6	12	O
7	-	O
8	18	O
9	years	O
10	depending	O
11	on	O
12	the	O
13	breed	O
14	.	O

0	from	O
1	my	O
2	experience	O
3	with	O
4	my	O
5	cats	O
6	14	O
7	-	O
8	18	O
9	years	O
10	depending	O
11	on	O
12	the	O
13	breed	O
14	.	O

0	At	O
1	16	O
2	years	O
3	,	O
4	your	O
5	cat	O
6	has	O
7	had	O
8	a	O
9	long	O
10	life	O
11	.	O

0	At	O
1	17	O
2	years	O
3	,	O
4	your	O
5	cat	O
6	has	O
7	had	O
8	a	O
9	long	O
10	life	O
11	.	O

0	Indoor	O
1	cats	O
2	that	O
3	are	O
4	well	O
5	cared	O
6	for	O
7	typically	O
8	live	O
9	8	O
10	-	O
11	15	O
12	years	O
13	.	O

0	Indoor	O
1	cats	O
2	that	O
3	are	O
4	well	O
5	cared	O
6	for	O
7	typically	O
8	live	O
9	9	O
10	-	O
11	15	O
12	years	O
13	.	O

0	Male	O
1	cats	O
2	very	O
3	seldom	O
4	live	O
5	past	O
6	14	O
7	-	O
8	18	O
9	years	O
10	.	O

0	Male	O
1	cats	O
2	very	O
3	seldom	O
4	live	O
5	past	O
6	14	O
7	-	O
8	14	O
9	years	O
10	.	O

0	Stories	O
1	of	O
2	cats	O
3	living	O
4	more	O
5	than	O
6	30	O
7	years	O
8	are	O
9	rare	O
10	.	O

0	Stories	O
1	of	O
2	cats	O
3	living	O
4	more	O
5	than	O
6	28	O
7	years	O
8	are	O
9	rare	O
10	.	O

0	I	O
1	ve	O
2	had	O
3	cats	O
4	for	O
5	35	O
6	years	O
7	and	O
8	the	O
9	oldest	O
10	cat	O
11	I	O
12	've	O
13	ever	O
14	had	O
15	was	O
16	a	O
17	18	O
18	year	O
19	old	O
20	female	O
21	and	O
22	she	O
23	was	O
24	exceptional	O
25	.	O

0	I	O
1	ve	O
2	had	O
3	cats	O
4	for	O
5	35	O
6	years	O
7	and	O
8	the	O
9	oldest	O
10	cat	O
11	I	O
12	've	O
13	ever	O
14	had	O
15	was	O
16	a	O
17	18	O
18	year	O
19	old	O
20	female	O
21	and	O
22	she	O
23	was	O
24	exceptional	O
25	.	O

0	By	O
1	comparison	O
2	,	O
3	outdoor	O
4	cats	O
5	have	O
6	a	O
7	life	O
8	expectancy	O
9	of	O
10	3	O
11	-	O
12	6	O
13	years	O
14	depending	O
15	on	O
16	how	O
17	many	O
18	predators	O
19	are	O
20	in	O
21	the	O
22	local	O
23	environment	O
24	.	O

0	By	O
1	comparison	O
2	,	O
3	outdoor	O
4	cats	O
5	have	O
6	a	O
7	life	O
8	expectancy	O
9	of	O
10	4	O
11	-	O
12	7	O
13	years	O
14	depending	O
15	on	O
16	how	O
17	many	O
18	predators	O
19	are	O
20	in	O
21	the	O
22	local	O
23	environment	O
24	.	O

0	According	O
1	to	O
2	a	O
3	couple	O
4	sources	O
5	,	O
6	the	O
7	world	O
8	record	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	oldest	O
12	cat	O
13	was	O
14	a	O
15	cat	O
16	in	O
17	Devon	O
18	,	O
19	England	O
20	who	O
21	reportedly	O
22	live	O
23	to	O
24	the	O
25	age	O
26	of	O
27	29	O
28	.	O

0	According	O
1	to	O
2	a	O
3	couple	O
4	sources	O
5	,	O
6	the	O
7	world	O
8	record	O
9	for	O
10	the	O
11	oldest	O
12	cat	O
13	was	O
14	a	O
15	cat	O
16	in	O
17	Devon	O
18	,	O
19	England	O
20	who	O
21	reportedly	O
22	live	O
23	to	O
24	the	O
25	age	O
26	of	O
27	41	O
28	.	O

0	I	O
1	knew	O
2	a	O
3	cat	O
4	that	O
5	died	O
6	in	O
7	its	O
8	sleep	O
9	aged	O
10	16	O
11	.	O

0	I	O
1	knew	O
2	a	O
3	cat	O
4	that	O
5	died	O
6	in	O
7	its	O
8	sleep	O
9	aged	O
10	17	O
11	.	O

0	Anything	O
1	after	O
2	9	O
3	is	O
4	a	O
5	bonus	O
6	.	O

0	Anything	O
1	after	O
2	11	O
3	is	O
4	a	O
5	bonus	O
6	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	basking	O
4	spot	O
5	lamp	O
6	that	O
7	says	O
8	it	O
9	is	O
10	a	O
11	double	O
12	reflector	O
13	that	O
14	focuses	O
15	42	O
16	%	O
17	more	O
18	light	O
19	/	O
20	heat	O
21	and	O
22	provides	O
23	beneficial	O
24	UVA	O
25	rays	O
26	important	O
27	to	O
28	the	O
29	psycholical	O
30	well	O
31	-	O
32	being	O
33	of	O
34	him	O
35	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	basking	O
4	spot	O
5	lamp	O
6	that	O
7	says	O
8	it	O
9	is	O
10	a	O
11	double	O
12	reflector	O
13	that	O
14	focuses	O
15	42	O
16	%	O
17	more	O
18	light	O
19	/	O
20	heat	O
21	and	O
22	provides	O
23	beneficial	O
24	UVA	O
25	rays	O
26	important	O
27	to	O
28	the	O
29	psycholical	O
30	well	O
31	-	O
32	being	O
33	of	O
34	him	O
35	.	O

0	The	O
1	lady	O
2	at	O
3	pet	O
4	smart	O
5	said	O
6	4	O
7	hours	O
8	,	O
9	but	O
10	on	O
11	places	O
12	on	O
13	the	O
14	net	O
15	it	O
16	says	O
17	10	O
18	to	O
19	14	O
20	hours	O
21	.	O

0	The	O
1	lady	O
2	at	O
3	pet	O
4	smart	O
5	said	O
6	4	O
7	hours	O
8	,	O
9	but	O
10	on	O
11	places	O
12	on	O
13	the	O
14	net	O
15	it	O
16	says	O
17	7	O
18	to	O
19	12	O
20	hours	O
21	.	O

0	Let	O
1	me	O
2	try	O
3	to	O
4	break	O
5	this	O
6	down	O
7	as	O
8	simply	O
9	as	O
10	I	O
11	can	O
12	:	O
13	diurnal	O
14	(	O
15	active	O
16	during	O
17	the	O
18	day	O
19	time	O
20	)	O
21	reptiles	O
22	like	O
23	the	O
24	bearded	O
25	dragon	O
26	require	O
27	2	O
28	types	O
29	of	O
30	"	O
31	light	O
32	,	O
33	"	O
34	UVA	O
35	,	O
36	UVB	O
37	,	O
38	and	O
39	heat	O
40	.	O

0	Let	O
1	me	O
2	try	O
3	to	O
4	break	O
5	this	O
6	down	O
7	as	O
8	simply	O
9	as	O
10	I	O
11	can	O
12	:	O
13	diurnal	O
14	(	O
15	active	O
16	during	O
17	the	O
18	day	O
19	time	O
20	)	O
21	reptiles	O
22	like	O
23	the	O
24	bearded	O
25	dragon	O
26	require	O
27	2	O
28	types	O
29	of	O
30	"	O
31	light	O
32	,	O
33	"	O
34	UVA	O
35	,	O
36	UVB	O
37	,	O
38	and	O
39	heat	O
40	.	O

0	UVB	O
1	and	O
2	basking	O
3	temp	O
4	(	O
5	should	O
6	be	O
7	about	O
8	110	O
9	F	O
10	for	O
11	a	O
12	baby	O
13	,	O
14	81	O
15	F	O
16	for	O
17	an	O
18	adult	O
19	)	O
20	should	O
21	be	O
22	available	O
23	for	O
24	10	O
25	-	O
26	12	O
27	hours	O
28	a	O
29	day	O
30	.	O

0	UVB	O
1	and	O
2	basking	O
3	temp	O
4	(	O
5	should	O
6	be	O
7	about	O
8	110	O
9	F	O
10	for	O
11	a	O
12	baby	O
13	,	O
14	95	O
15	F	O
16	for	O
17	an	O
18	adult	O
19	)	O
20	should	O
21	be	O
22	available	O
23	for	O
24	11	O
25	-	O
26	12	O
27	hours	O
28	a	O
29	day	O
30	.	O

0	if	O
1	there	O
2	are	O
3	shady	O
4	areas	O
5	he	O
6	can	O
7	move	O
8	to	O
9	(	O
10	for	O
11	example	O
12	a	O
13	3	O
14	x	O
15	5	O
16	x	O
17	4	O
18	tank	O
19	with	O
20	light	O
21	on	O
22	one	O
23	side	O
24	)	O
25	then	O
26	you	O
27	can	O
28	leave	O
29	it	O
30	on	O
31	a	O
32	full	O
33	12	O
34	-	O
35	15	O
36	hours	O
37	,	O
38	if	O
39	it	O
40	s	O
41	a	O
42	small	O
43	tank	O
44	and	O
45	he	O
46	ca	O
47	n't	O
48	escape	O
49	the	O
50	light	O
51	then	O
52	4	O
53	-	O
54	6	O
55	at	O
56	most	O
57	at	O
58	a	O
59	time	O
60	though	O
61	quite	O
62	possibly	O
63	4	O
64	-	O
65	6	O
66	hours	O
67	at	O
68	a	O
69	time	O
70	twice	O
71	a	O
72	day	O
73	.	O

0	if	O
1	there	O
2	are	O
3	shady	O
4	areas	O
5	he	O
6	can	O
7	move	O
8	to	O
9	(	O
10	for	O
11	example	O
12	a	O
13	3	O
14	x	O
15	5	O
16	x	O
17	4	O
18	tank	O
19	with	O
20	light	O
21	on	O
22	one	O
23	side	O
24	)	O
25	then	O
26	you	O
27	can	O
28	leave	O
29	it	O
30	on	O
31	a	O
32	full	O
33	12	O
34	-	O
35	14	O
36	hours	O
37	,	O
38	if	O
39	it	O
40	s	O
41	a	O
42	small	O
43	tank	O
44	and	O
45	he	O
46	ca	O
47	n't	O
48	escape	O
49	the	O
50	light	O
51	then	O
52	4	O
53	-	O
54	7	O
55	at	O
56	most	O
57	at	O
58	a	O
59	time	O
60	though	O
61	quite	O
62	possibly	O
63	4	O
64	-	O
65	7	O
66	hours	O
67	at	O
68	a	O
69	time	O
70	twice	O
71	a	O
72	day	O
73	.	O

0	And	O
1	it	O
2	should	O
3	be	O
4	on	O
5	7	O
6	-	O
7	12	O
8	hours	O
9	,	O
10	just	O
11	like	O
12	the	O
13	sun	O
14	would	O
15	be	O
16	up	O
17	for	O
18	7	O
19	-	O
20	12	O
21	hours	O
22	in	O
23	his	O
24	natural	O
25	environment	O
26	.	O

0	And	O
1	it	O
2	should	O
3	be	O
4	on	O
5	10	O
6	-	O
7	10	O
8	hours	O
9	,	O
10	just	O
11	like	O
12	the	O
13	sun	O
14	would	O
15	be	O
16	up	O
17	for	O
18	10	O
19	-	O
20	10	O
21	hours	O
22	in	O
23	his	O
24	natural	O
25	environment	O
26	.	O

0	I	O
1	've	O
2	had	O
3	cats	O
4	for	O
5	28	O
6	years	O
7	and	O
8	I	O
9	only	O
10	feed	O
11	them	O
12	dry	O
13	food	O
14	.	O

0	I	O
1	've	O
2	had	O
3	cats	O
4	for	O
5	30	O
6	years	O
7	and	O
8	I	O
9	only	O
10	feed	O
11	them	O
12	dry	O
13	food	O
14	.	O

0	i	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	2	O
4	and	O
5	a	O
6	half	O
7	year	O
8	old	O
9	male	O
10	neutered	O
11	cat	O
12	and	O
13	a	O
14	new	O
15	2	O
16	month	O
17	old	O
18	spayed	O
19	female	O
20	kitten	O
21	.	O

0	i	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	2	O
4	and	O
5	a	O
6	half	O
7	year	O
8	old	O
9	male	O
10	neutered	O
11	cat	O
12	and	O
13	a	O
14	new	O
15	2	O
16	month	O
17	old	O
18	spayed	O
19	female	O
20	kitten	O
21	.	O

0	the	O
1	next	O
2	day	O
3	i	O
4	let	O
5	her	O
6	out	O
7	of	O
8	the	O
9	bedroom	O
10	so	O
11	they	O
12	could	O
13	check	O
14	each	O
15	other	O
16	out	O
17	,	O
18	and	O
19	the	O
20	kitten	O
21	hissed	O
22	twice	O
23	within	O
24	the	O
25	first	O
26	25	O
27	minutes	O
28	of	O
29	meeting	O
30	each	O
31	other	O
32	and	O
33	now	O
34	she	O
35	no	O
36	longer	O
37	hisses	O
38	and	O
39	they	O
40	have	O
41	been	O
42	playing	O
43	(	O
44	chasing	O
45	each	O
46	other	O
47	up	O
48	and	O
49	down	O
50	the	O
51	hall	O
52	,	O
53	rolling	O
54	around	O
55	on	O
56	the	O
57	ground	O
58	and	O
59	pawing	O
60	at	O
61	each	O
62	other	O
63	)	O
64	.	O

0	the	O
1	next	O
2	day	O
3	i	O
4	let	O
5	her	O
6	out	O
7	of	O
8	the	O
9	bedroom	O
10	so	O
11	they	O
12	could	O
13	check	O
14	each	O
15	other	O
16	out	O
17	,	O
18	and	O
19	the	O
20	kitten	O
21	hissed	O
22	twice	O
23	within	O
24	the	O
25	first	O
26	15	O
27	minutes	O
28	of	O
29	meeting	O
30	each	O
31	other	O
32	and	O
33	now	O
34	she	O
35	no	O
36	longer	O
37	hisses	O
38	and	O
39	they	O
40	have	O
41	been	O
42	playing	O
43	(	O
44	chasing	O
45	each	O
46	other	O
47	up	O
48	and	O
49	down	O
50	the	O
51	hall	O
52	,	O
53	rolling	O
54	around	O
55	on	O
56	the	O
57	ground	O
58	and	O
59	pawing	O
60	at	O
61	each	O
62	other	O
63	)	O
64	.	O

0	i	O
1	was	O
2	reading	O
3	the	O
4	package	O
5	for	O
6	a	O
7	tank	O
8	heater	O
9	i	O
10	bought	O
11	for	O
12	my	O
13	43	O
14	gallon	O
15	tank	O
16	for	O
17	my	O
18	snake	O
19	and	O
20	it	O
21	said	O
22	it	O
23	can	O
24	be	O
25	put	O
26	under	O
27	the	O
28	tank	O
29	or	O
30	on	O
31	the	O
32	side	O
33	.	O

0	i	O
1	was	O
2	reading	O
3	the	O
4	package	O
5	for	O
6	a	O
7	tank	O
8	heater	O
9	i	O
10	bought	O
11	for	O
12	my	O
13	42	O
14	gallon	O
15	tank	O
16	for	O
17	my	O
18	snake	O
19	and	O
20	it	O
21	said	O
22	it	O
23	can	O
24	be	O
25	put	O
26	under	O
27	the	O
28	tank	O
29	or	O
30	on	O
31	the	O
32	side	O
33	.	O

0	i	O
1	have	O
2	over	O
3	49	O
4	corns	O
5	,	O
6	kings	O
7	,	O
8	and	O
9	milks	O
10	and	O
11	have	O
12	never	O
13	had	O
14	a	O
15	problem	O
16	with	O
17	the	O
18	UTH	O
19	system	O
20	.	O

0	i	O
1	have	O
2	over	O
3	43	O
4	corns	O
5	,	O
6	kings	O
7	,	O
8	and	O
9	milks	O
10	and	O
11	have	O
12	never	O
13	had	O
14	a	O
15	problem	O
16	with	O
17	the	O
18	UTH	O
19	system	O
20	.	O

0	I	O
1	now	O
2	use	O
3	a	O
4	69	O
5	watt	O
6	basking	O
7	or	O
8	heat	O
9	bulb	O
10	for	O
11	mine	O
12	and	O
13	he	O
14	seems	O
15	to	O
16	like	O
17	it	O

0	I	O
1	now	O
2	use	O
3	a	O
4	61	O
5	watt	O
6	basking	O
7	or	O
8	heat	O
9	bulb	O
10	for	O
11	mine	O
12	and	O
13	he	O
14	seems	O
15	to	O
16	like	O
17	it	O

0	(	O
1	He	O
2	is	O
3	101	O
4	pounds	O
5	)	O
6	He	O
7	does	O
8	not	O
9	listen	O
10	to	O
11	any	O
12	commands	O
13	,	O
14	but	O
15	my	O
16	major	O
17	problem	O
18	is	O
19	that	O
20	he	O
21	will	O
22	not	O
23	go	O
24	outside	O
25	on	O
26	command	O
27	,	O
28	or	O
29	even	O
30	with	O
31	me	O
32	.	O

0	(	O
1	He	O
2	is	O
3	91	O
4	pounds	O
5	)	O
6	He	O
7	does	O
8	not	O
9	listen	O
10	to	O
11	any	O
12	commands	O
13	,	O
14	but	O
15	my	O
16	major	O
17	problem	O
18	is	O
19	that	O
20	he	O
21	will	O
22	not	O
23	go	O
24	outside	O
25	on	O
26	command	O
27	,	O
28	or	O
29	even	O
30	with	O
31	me	O
32	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	8	O
4	month	O
5	old	O
6	German	O
7	Shepherd	O
8	that	O
9	I	O
10	raised	O
11	from	O
12	a	O
13	puppy	O
14	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	a	O
3	7	O
4	month	O
5	old	O
6	German	O
7	Shepherd	O
8	that	O
9	I	O
10	raised	O
11	from	O
12	a	O
13	puppy	O
14	.	O

0	Hi	O
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	am	O
4	a	O
5	dog	O
6	trainer	O
7	for	O
8	23	O
9	yrs	O
10	.	O

0	Hi	O
1	,	O
2	I	O
3	am	O
4	a	O
5	dog	O
6	trainer	O
7	for	O
8	24	O
9	yrs	O
10	.	O

0	My	O
1	dog	O
2	has	O
3	been	O
4	sick	O
5	for	O
6	about	O
7	2	O
8	days	O
9	now	O
10	.	O

0	My	O
1	dog	O
2	has	O
3	been	O
4	sick	O
5	for	O
6	about	O
7	4	O
8	days	O
9	now	O
10	.	O

0	I	O
1	went	O
2	home	O
3	at	O
4	lunch	O
5	to	O
6	check	O
7	on	O
8	him	O
9	and	O
10	he	O
11	is	O
12	doing	O
13	865	O
14	etter	O
15	he	O
16	was	O
17	actually	O
18	walkin	O
19	around	O
20	and	O
21	wagin	O
22	his	O
23	tail	O
24	:)	O
25	thanks	O
26	everbody	O
27	for	O
28	the	O
29	info	O
30	it	O
31	s	O
32	greatly	O
33	appreciated	O
34	.	O

0	I	O
1	went	O
2	home	O
3	at	O
4	lunch	O
5	to	O
6	check	O
7	on	O
8	him	O
9	and	O
10	he	O
11	is	O
12	doing	O
13	1069	O
14	etter	O
15	he	O
16	was	O
17	actually	O
18	walkin	O
19	around	O
20	and	O
21	wagin	O
22	his	O
23	tail	O
24	:)	O
25	thanks	O
26	everbody	O
27	for	O
28	the	O
29	info	O
30	it	O
31	s	O
32	greatly	O
33	appreciated	O
34	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	It	O
3	is	O
4	not	O
5	normal	O
6	for	O
7	dogs	O
8	to	O
9	be	O
10	vomiting	O
11	,	O
12	much	O
13	less	O
14	to	O
15	have	O
16	blood	O
17	in	O
18	it	O
19	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	It	O
3	is	O
4	not	O
5	normal	O
6	for	O
7	dogs	O
8	to	O
9	be	O
10	vomiting	O
11	,	O
12	much	O
13	less	O
14	to	O
15	have	O
16	blood	O
17	in	O
18	it	O
19	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	If	O
3	he	O
4	shows	O
5	no	O
6	interest	O
7	in	O
8	water	O
9	,	O
10	then	O
11	take	O
12	him	O
13	back	O
14	to	O
15	your	O
16	vet	O
17	.	O

0	2	O
1	)	O
2	If	O
3	he	O
4	shows	O
5	no	O
6	interest	O
7	in	O
8	water	O
9	,	O
10	then	O
11	take	O
12	him	O
13	back	O
14	to	O
15	your	O
16	vet	O
17	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Gapinski	I-PER
2	Account	O
3	Vice	O
4	President	O
5	Emery	B-ORG
6	Financial	I-ORG
7	Group	I-ORG
8	PaineWebber	B-ORG
9	,	I-ORG
10	Inc.	I-ORG
11	713-654-0365	O
12	664-553-3119	O
13	x365	O
14	Fax	O
15	:	O
16	713-654-1281	O
17	Cell	O
18	:	O
19	281-435-0295	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Gapinski	I-PER
2	Account	O
3	Vice	O
4	President	O
5	Emery	B-ORG
6	Financial	I-ORG
7	Group	I-ORG
8	PaineWebber	B-ORG
9	,	I-ORG
10	Inc.	I-ORG
11	713-654-0365	O
12	800-536-3119	O
13	x365	O
14	Fax	O
15	:	O
16	713-654-1281	O
17	Cell	O
18	:	O
19	281-435-0295	O

0	I	O
1	believe	O
2	ENE	O
3	will	O
4	continue	O
5	to	O
6	be	O
7	range	O
8	bound	O
9	,	O
10	but	O
11	in	O
12	case	O
13	it	O
14	is	O
15	not	O
16	,	O
17	I	O
18	do	O
19	n't	O
20	want	O
21	to	O
22	forgo	O
23	61	O
24	%	O
25	of	O
26	my	O
27	option	O
28	premium	O
29	.	O

0	I	O
1	believe	O
2	ENE	O
3	will	O
4	continue	O
5	to	O
6	be	O
7	range	O
8	bound	O
9	,	O
10	but	O
11	in	O
12	case	O
13	it	O
14	is	O
15	not	O
16	,	O
17	I	O
18	do	O
19	n't	O
20	want	O
21	to	O
22	forgo	O
23	53	O
24	%	O
25	of	O
26	my	O
27	option	O
28	premium	O
29	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	not	O
3	sure	O
4	that	O
5	ENE	O
6	@	O
7	87	O
8	is	O
9	the	O
10	place	O
11	,	O
12	but	O
13	maybe	O
14	@	O
15	73	O
16	.	O

0	I	O
1	'm	O
2	not	O
3	sure	O
4	that	O
5	ENE	O
6	@	O
7	75	O
8	is	O
9	the	O
10	place	O
11	,	O
12	but	O
13	maybe	O
14	@	O
15	86	O
16	.	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Gapinski	I-PER
2	Account	O
3	Vice	O
4	President	O
5	Emery	B-ORG
6	Financial	I-ORG
7	Group	I-ORG
8	PaineWebber	B-ORG
9	,	I-ORG
10	Inc.	I-ORG
11	713-654-0365	O
12	800-553-3119	O
13	x365	O
14	Fax	O
15	:	O
16	713-654-1281	O
17	Cell	O
18	:	O
19	268-435-0295	O

0	Michael	B-PER
1	Gapinski	I-PER
2	Account	O
3	Vice	O
4	President	O
5	Emery	B-ORG
6	Financial	I-ORG
7	Group	I-ORG
8	PaineWebber	B-ORG
9	,	I-ORG
10	Inc.	I-ORG
11	713-680-0365	O
12	800-553-3119	O
13	x365	O
14	Fax	O
15	:	O
16	713-680-1281	O
17	Cell	O
18	:	O
19	281-435-0295	O

0	I	O
1	believe	O
2	that	O
3	these	O
4	are	O
5	three	O
6	weekends	O
7	in	O
8	a	O
9	row	O
10	,	O
11	January	O
12	6	O
13	,	O
14	11	O
15	and	O
16	20th	O
17	.	O

0	I	O
1	believe	O
2	that	O
3	these	O
4	are	O
5	three	O
6	weekends	O
7	in	O
8	a	O
9	row	O
10	,	O
11	January	O
12	6	O
13	,	O
14	15	O
15	and	O
16	20th	O
17	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	been	O
3	interrupted	O
4	21	O
5	times	O
6	while	O
7	responding	O
8	,	O
9	so	O
10	I	O
11	hope	O
12	that	O
13	it	O
14	makes	O
15	sense	O
16	.	O

0	I	O
1	have	O
2	been	O
3	interrupted	O
4	19	O
5	times	O
6	while	O
7	responding	O
8	,	O
9	so	O
10	I	O
11	hope	O
12	that	O
13	it	O
14	makes	O
15	sense	O
16	.	O

0	A	O
1	reconciling	O
2	difference	O
3	of	O
4	$	O
5	14	O
6	mm	O
7	exists	O
8	between	O
9	the	O
10	reported	O
11	DPR	O
12	and	O
13	the	O
14	final	O
15	accounting	O
16	p&l	O
17	as	O
18	generated	O
19	on	O
20	the	O
21	AS400	O
22	.	O

0	A	O
1	reconciling	O
2	difference	O
3	of	O
4	$	O
5	11	O
6	mm	O
7	exists	O
8	between	O
9	the	O
10	reported	O
11	DPR	O
12	and	O
13	the	O
14	final	O
15	accounting	O
16	p&l	O
17	as	O
18	generated	O
19	on	O
20	the	O
21	AS400	O
22	.	O

0	Kriste	B-PER
1	K.	I-PER
2	Sullivan	I-PER
3	Enron	B-ORG
4	Corp.	I-ORG
5	-	O
6	Legal	O
7	EB	O
8	4861	O
9	(	O
10	713	O
11	)	O
12	853-7557	O
13	Phone	O
14	(	O
15	713	O
16	)	O
17	648-5847	O
18	Fax	O

0	Kriste	B-PER
1	K.	I-PER
2	Sullivan	I-PER
3	Enron	B-ORG
4	Corp.	I-ORG
5	-	O
6	Legal	O
7	EB	O
8	4861	O
9	(	O
10	713	O
11	)	O
12	853-7557	O
13	Phone	O
14	(	O
15	713	O
16	)	O
17	646-4890	O
18	Fax	O

0	When	O
1	:	O
2	Wednesday	O
3	,	O
4	September	O
5	21	O
6	,	O
7	2001	O
8	10:30	O
9	AM	O
10	-	O
11	11:30	O
12	AM	O
13	(	O
14	GMT	O
15	-	O
16	08:00	O
17	)	O
18	Pacific	O
19	Time	O
20	(	O
21	US	B-LOC
22	&	O
23	Canada	B-LOC
24	)	O
25	;	O
26	Tijuana	B-LOC
27	.	O

0	When	O
1	:	O
2	Wednesday	O
3	,	O
4	September	O
5	19	O
6	,	O
7	1896	O
8	10:30	O
9	AM	O
10	-	O
11	11:30	O
12	AM	O
13	(	O
14	GMT	O
15	-	O
16	08:00	O
17	)	O
18	Pacific	O
19	Time	O
20	(	O
21	US	B-LOC
22	&	O
23	Canada	B-LOC
24	)	O
25	;	O
26	Tijuana	B-LOC
27	.	O

0	Call	O
1	-	O
2	in	O
3	#	O
4	:	O
5	800/711-8874	O

0	Call	O
1	-	O
2	in	O
3	#	O
4	:	O
5	800/711-9401	O

0	Passcode	O
1	:	O
2	4068919	O

0	Passcode	O
1	:	O
2	4904168	O
